<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!--===================== Concepts taught through the learning readout, when opportunities arise ===================-->
  <ReformCaravan.label>Re caravan</ReformCaravan.label><ReformCaravan.helpText>Now if you want to be and the new recently offered a map of the world. "Business restoring," you will be able to send a convoy.</ReformCaravan.helpText><Rescuing.label>release</Rescuing.label><Rescuing.helpText>Help those who were injured, and choose healthy life, choose 'save', and then right-click on the victim.\n\nIf not always used to the colony of their own, but there are public safety. Once you have made, just to go out. In order to protect citizens, and jail program by selecting the "catch".</Rescuing.helpText><Capturing.label>ten</Capturing.label><Capturing.helpText>enemy of appropriately. You can mark pow\n\nPrison, and, "decided to organize, select and right-click to accept the disabled enemy," was arrested in jail.\n\nDetainees have been set, if you have a special bed.</Capturing.helpText><ShieldBelts.label>shield band</ShieldBelts.label><ShieldBelts.helpText>Shield with close military and
    weapons from outside. No impact on any attack near the range.\n\nThe task force focused on the zone or face to face with the enemy to attack, or mounted on the buffet.</ShieldBelts.helpText>  <InteractingWithTraders.label>Trader relationships</InteractingWithTraders.label><InteractingWithTraders.helpText>At the top mark (?) To select retailers conversation is over.\n\nChoose a job, click the button and then the () mark.</InteractingWithTraders.helpText><Drafting.label>general</Drafting.label><Drafting.helpText>Work directly with the settlers on the field of battle, choose immigration that "conscript.".\n\nWork on the employment of immigrants in the right direction, and I can tell you. Jihad and armed with a gun.\n\nLet's licensing grace delivered - and even if they are washed and starve them out.</Drafting.helpText><BuildOrbitalTradeBeacon.label>With your brand</BuildOrbitalTradeBeacon.label><BuildOrbitalTradeBeacon.helpText>Especially on the streets in residential home sales,
    regional stack "means a change.".</BuildOrbitalTradeBeacon.helpText><AnimalsDontAttackDoors.label>Pets not really</AnimalsDontAttackDoors.label><AnimalsDontAttackDoors.helpText>Animals attack people in general and the door did not affect the space does not work.\n\nIf you run back into the house, if you enter, but they can not, they are waiting for you.</AnimalsDontAttackDoors.helpText><BillsTab.label>By using this</BillsTab.label><BillsTab.helpText>Damage computer choose the table and open transition tab. Then you can in the kitchen, but one that you can, or food or meat.</BillsTab.helpText><OpeningComms.label>relationship with</OpeningComms.label><OpeningComms.helpText>Once you flip the call using a communication device, right-click on the device connection.</OpeningComms.helpText><DrugAddiction.label>Addicted to pull</DrugAddiction.label><DrugAddiction.helpText>We are expensive to investigate the appropriate settlement of the "requirements".\n\nIf set to 0 in the final stages
    to avoid "withdrawal" is it equivalent to the government, offers a variety of results.\n\nBut as Haitai rest of the time, there is abuse of compassionate, it will disappear.</DrugAddiction.helpText><DrugPolicies.label>Applied drag Terms and Conditions</DrugPolicies.label><DrugPolicies.helpText>You can program the residents, such as drugs or appoint a special drag peneakisirin happy day to drink beer regularly and teak.\n\nYou "of -rok" menu, click "Apply dress policy." Create a new policy program. Then you need this app immigration policies.\n\nYou can still take some time to move against the current policy of the settlers. But you can tell them what to do, what follows, but your own</DrugPolicies.helpText><TVForSickPeople.label>entertainment television in the hospital room</TVForSickPeople.label><TVForSickPeople.helpText>The patient, even just a bed, you can watch TV.</TVForSickPeople.helpText><PrisonerTab.label>tab prisoner</PrisonerTab.label><PrisonerTab.helpText>"Closed"
    suppression of the tab when a car, which you can write.\n\nThem, or treatment, or seek, or indifference or body or diet is not enough.\n\nSome immigrants only "maintenance" of the working class who, prisoners in question.</PrisonerTab.helpText><SetGrowingZonePlant.label>Plants do not grow</SetGrowingZonePlant.label><SetGrowingZonePlant.helpText>Agricultural areas or plant training itself. You can also trees\n\nagricultural area, and select the '' key ''.</SetGrowingZonePlant.helpText><DrugBurning.label>Gushing out</DrugBurning.label><DrugBurning.helpText>The practice sometimes it may be helpful, but the cause of the accident.\n\nIf you live if you do not want to be a burden to them, the fire seemed to be an option in this area.</DrugBurning.helpText><DoorOpenSpeed.label>The door opened and closed faster</DoorOpenSpeed.label><DoorOpenSpeed.helpText>Door and the door closed, and the flying speed is different, that is.\n\n(Note) to open the door very slowly and dignity. For all these
    people, so you will see that it moves slowly.</DoorOpenSpeed.helpText><QueueOrders.label>They accumulate in the direction of rotation</QueueOrders.label><QueueOrders.helpText>The settlers and the "Shift" while holding the instructions, you can get a lot of standing instructions.</QueueOrders.helpText></LanguageData>
