<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <!--===================== Concepts taught through the learning readout, with no opportunity needed ===================-->
  <CameraDolly.label>motion Camera</CameraDolly.label>
  <CameraDolly.helpText>Move the camera or mouse button 3 {keyword: MapDolly_Up} - {important: MapDolly_Left} - {important: MapDolly_Down} - {important: MapDolly_Right} key.</CameraDolly.helpText>
  <CameraZoom.label>always remember</CameraZoom.label>
  <CameraZoom.helpText>A MapZoom_Out {}, {} or with the mouse wheel zooms the camera MapZoom_In:</CameraZoom.helpText>
  <TimeControls.label>memory speed</TimeControls.label>
  <TimeControls.helpText>Click {text: TimeSpeed_Fast}, {text: TimeSpeed_Superfast} The primary use: the game a long time, fast, slow, single screen icon bottom right, text TimeSpeed_Normal} {.</TimeControls.helpText>
  <Pause.label>stop</Pause.label>
  <Pause.helpText> {} togglepause key or you leave the game will continue.\n\nAs long as you do not stop, you might say.\n\n{The main activities that most fears: togglePause} key, do not forget.</Pause.helpText>
  <Stockpiles.label>Protection plan</Stockpiles.label>
  <Stockpiles.helpText>Then, they have to store the material in one place to create a colony. Create an attic to store items.\n\nArchitect storage area "in the lower left corner of the menu" is located in this area.</Stockpiles.helpText>
  <Forbidding.label>related publications</Forbidding.label>
  <Forbidding.helpText>Yes, all that, which is marked "restricted".\n\n"Prohibited" objects, a small red "x". Menu, "banned" from the screen, "enable" on the bottom of control permissions and restrictions.</Forbidding.helpText>
  <GrowingFood.label>Order of agricultural areas</GrowingFood.label>
  <GrowingFood.helpText>You must have land, cattle in value. "Zone" and "plans", "agricultural area" Select.\n\nAgriculture, can only take place with the earth.</GrowingFood.helpText>
  <EquippingWeapons.label>they</EquippingWeapons.label>
  <EquippingWeapons.helpText>The first immigrants of military weapons. Take over\n\nWith the soldiers to rest, and rest the mouse button and select the correct right-click the weapon.</EquippingWeapons.helpText>
  <Alerts.label>[Warning]</Alerts.label>
  <Alerts.helpText>Mail alert from the right side of the screen, you see the problem, you need to pay attention.\n\nE-mail notifications are always cautious.</Alerts.helpText>
  <Mining.label>mining</Mining.label>
  <Mining.helpText>right "direct puuone" "payment number" Instructions, "" my, you might say.\n\nIron, gold, plastic, steel, and other metals, and convenient in use.</Mining.helpText>
  <WorkTab.label>Review of priority</WorkTab.label>
  <WorkTab.helpText>"Value" and then check the work of a man who lived there.\n\nIt was always working from the top to the lowest priority\n\nIf, as a person, place, or as a high priority on preventive work, the work will stand.</WorkTab.helpText>
  <ForbiddingDoors.label>banned</ForbiddingDoors.label>
  <ForbiddingDoors.helpText>If you do not restrict the door with the door now, people and culture will be.\n\n[Note] This door is locked different. Because the door is always locked intruders may pass freely. Restrictions on the use of the door of the establishment is found not long. Mad transplant may be the only entrance door.</ForbiddingDoors.helpText>
  <CoverAndShooting.label>tactical shooting</CoverAndShooting.label>
  <CoverAndShooting.helpText>Shot to put too much importance to that.\n\nWine Trojan migrants are true, that are not in the midst of his enemies, and 'eventually get to cover your gun.\n\nIn addition, covered the regulations set in the corner of the wall in the background. When tilting the solution had been shot.\n\nYou can cover the use of the devices, but some things are better than others as a cover. It is better to use a wooden deck in the shade of the trees, there is nothing that can be hidden in sacks of sand in the underground, is fantastic, it is.</CoverAndShooting.helpText>
  <FormCaravan.label>Aside Corps</FormCaravan.label>
  <FormCaravan.helpText>In addition to planetary movements can organize a fleet!\n\nFrom the tab "World", and then click on your home, you can select the "Caravan of organization" button.</FormCaravan.helpText>
  <AnimalTaming.label>a tame wild animal</AnimalTaming.label>
  <AnimalTaming.helpText>In order to purchase a wild beast, "Yin" instantly.\n\nIf wild animals have settled in the diet to try and tame.\n\n[Note] Some animals, their efforts failed to react violently when possible, and pigs.</AnimalTaming.helpText>
  <AnimalTraining.label>train</AnimalTraining.label>
  <AnimalTraining.helpText>Thus specific skills "training" in animal husbandry.\n\nTA TA series among the animals that can not continue, we need at this time.</AnimalTraining.helpText>
  <InfoCard.label>To activate the screen</InfoCard.label>
  <InfoCard.helpText>As the surface of the data structures, men seem to statistics.\n\nAfter you click the display unit in the developing "information" at least one member, or something.</InfoCard.helpText>
  <StorageTab.label>Remember the list of storage installation</StorageTab.label>
  <StorageTab.helpText>An open closet, window "shopping" tab on the bottom left corner of the selection inheritance, you can put the details.\n\nAdvanced Settings screen, click to expand the triangle to the left of the group name, you can create a permission and non-permission elements of each group.\n\nIn addition, if possible, meet the inhabitants of the land, the site of the former top priority, and low priority, and the priority changes.</StorageTab.helpText>
  <HomeArea.label>In order to make urban areas</HomeArea.label>
  <HomeArea.helpText>Firefighters brought the wee urban areas clean.\n\nBookmark "architect" of the "zone" may "zone" okay colony.</HomeArea.helpText>
  <SpoilageAndFreezers.label>Frozen and stored, causing decay</SpoilageAndFreezers.label>
  <SpoilageAndFreezers.helpText>Most of the food to rot in a short period of time.\n\nTo prevent this, the refrigerator.\n\nTo create the freezer in a confined space and one or two in a cool wall. Set the temperature freezer refrigeration.\n\nfrozen food is not circumcised.</SpoilageAndFreezers.helpText>
  <Deterioration.label>natural</Deterioration.label>
  <Deterioration.helpText>If you are out of the left will continue to slowly deteriorate\n\nWhen storing items in a long time more than he wants to choose a place on the boat.</Deterioration.helpText>
  <HostilityResponse.label>How disaster response</HostilityResponse.label>
  <HostilityResponse.helpText>As he released the animal, and to determine the steps to receive a combination of risk.\n\nSelect attack "Escape", "go" menu "and" transfer.</HostilityResponse.helpText>
  <AllowedAreas.label>Ltd. domain</AllowedAreas.label>
  <AllowedAreas.helpText>Settlers and cattle which may enter the closed area. He left the restricted area is forbidden.\n\nFor this example, it is useful to stay in business rambizwe leave the nest.\n\nYou can create a number of limitations in contrast to the belt and has the essence of an infinite number of colonists, Trojan horses and other animals that have occurred.\n\nCreate, delete the specified area available in "limited".\n\n"Avatar", the "Area" in the "regions" and "Forbidden Zone" that restrictions on the map of the region.</AllowedAreas.helpText>
  <MedicalOperations.label>Remember surgery</MedicalOperations.label>
  <MedicalOperations.helpText>Chest, institutions, training programs, Geeta, and "sub-tab of Health to open open" in the "new system", "time worked" label to the media lived ,.</MedicalOperations.helpText>
  <TimeAssignments.label>時間割</TimeAssignments.label>
  <TimeAssignments.helpText>Politicians of his work is done colonies, open the symbol 'B'.</TimeAssignments.helpText>
  <ManualWorkPriorities.label>Manual change that behavior patterns</ManualWorkPriorities.label>
  <ManualWorkPriorities.helpText>The most important part of a being, which is the greatest duty and RimWorld conditions corresponding to the fact that many were in the body was brought in.\n\nIn poor working, setting time is important for those without work, it is important work left unfinished, still long.\n\nProvide additional colonists could use a "priority", "Advanced settings".\n\nIn this mode, the settlement for each priority. Replace "1" priority immigration, the right job, left after priority "2", from left to right, are conducted in the same way.\n\nSense and decided in advance and it is very important colony.</ManualWorkPriorities.helpText>
  <GettingMoreTraders.label>came dealer</GettingMoreTraders.label>
  <GettingMoreTraders.helpText>Kijukere friendly and better quality sales saw you. if.\n\nIf the arrival of the friendship group with the merchant caravan\n\nTo blame the use of communications equipment, send that they pay a call, you can ask the merchant caravan.</GettingMoreTraders.helpText>
  <InspectRoomStats.label>See the room status</InspectRoomStats.label>
  <InspectRoomStats.helpText>The climate, the good kind, indulgent, see the beauty, the use of a visible change in the fourth picture bottom right corner.</InspectRoomStats.helpText>
  <Outfits.label>服装</Outfits.label>
  <Outfits.helpText>They live in automatically fresher, everybody is trying to buy more high level material.\n\nYou're crazy, you did not tell people to dress up any position (if you do not want to do this).\n\nDialogue "Kimono» Edit », developed an open line of clothes set, they put their feet, so to create a new clothing and shelter.</Outfits.helpText>
  <FirePreparation.label>fire spread</FirePreparation.label>
  <FirePreparation.helpText>Flammable region. So that will be prepared before what happens.\nFire damage to the colony will reduce\n\nHis own first major building types of buildings and floor space.\nvery easy to burn - 2. Changes are happy to burn wood all easy, however.\nTo prevent fire from spreading 3 Create a firebreak. 1-4 cells wide cement generally prevents fire spreading.</FirePreparation.helpText>
  <HistoryTab.label>Get the History tab</HistoryTab.label>
  <HistoryTab.helpText>"History" tab at the bottom of the "Unity", to show you the fate of the colony, which was recorded in a long time can see.</HistoryTab.helpText>
  <ClickingMessages.label>Click Messenger</ClickingMessages.label>
  <ClickingMessages.helpText>When you click the notification in the upper left corner of the screen, the object is displayed in such a way that in the middle of the screen.</ClickingMessages.helpText>
  <ShotAccuracyTooltip.label>shooting trick</ShotAccuracyTooltip.label>
  <ShotAccuracyTooltip.helpText>You can see just the kind of list of song, will help clear shot.\n\nIn case of confirmation, select mouse to fire people; Then came the javelin suction cup. After that, and with the environment, such as standing, to see the speed class DISCLAIMS liked.</ShotAccuracyTooltip.helpText>
  <FriendlyFireSafety.label>After the fire aloha</FriendlyFireSafety.label>
  <FriendlyFireSafety.helpText>there happens shoot friends and allies on fire.\n\nFor example, before the shooter, you can safely settlers melee weapon. In this case, the test will be on the shoulders of his friends as well.\n\nThis approach combat the archers and melee, which is a combination of a good way.</FriendlyFireSafety.helpText>
</LanguageData>
