<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <OrbitalTargeterBombardment.label>Orbital bombing scene</OrbitalTargeterBombardment.label>
  <OrbitalTargeterBombardment.description>Existing systems are needed to track the navigation system bomb.Impact and explosion mulrijeokneun provides the coordinates of the target in the field of satellite communications equipment.When the information device to reproduce and approve the use of netefaditswa, the network will detect unauthorized and will be cut off once and for all.</OrbitalTargeterBombardment.description>
  <OrbitalTargeterBombardment.verbs.Verb_Bombardment.label>The bombardment eyes</OrbitalTargeterBombardment.verbs.Verb_Bombardment.label>
  <OrbitalTargeterPowerBeam.label>beam track Vision</OrbitalTargeterPowerBeam.label>
  <OrbitalTargeterPowerBeam.description>And guiding systems meet the car.Then you will see the old satellite targets will begin radiation stops the lungs.This energy, of course, you can collect a lot Vader absorption.If you this parable first series do, can also lead to aimed, in the case of the power, it is a few thousand degrees warmer burns.To detect the presence of harmful radiation from the target satellite when the satellite is not always die out in good faith.</OrbitalTargeterPowerBeam.description>
  <OrbitalTargeterPowerBeam.verbs.Verb_PowerBeam.label>Keep track logs to see</OrbitalTargeterPowerBeam.verbs.Verb_PowerBeam.label>
  <TornadoGenerator.label>Tornado Generator</TornadoGenerator.label>
  <TornadoGenerator.description>Satellite network, the old-time control of operations of the device.How to save manufacturers and steel; Animation You can create a wave, select a location, it may fall into a large-scale air from the atmosphere.Weather Network, available to unauthorized uses as its tool bars.But tornadoes energy will be Released as normal.</TornadoGenerator.description>
  <TornadoGenerator.verbs.Verb_Spawn.label>storm generator</TornadoGenerator.verbs.Verb_Spawn.label>
</LanguageData>
