<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<BackstoryTranslations>
  <ColonySettler53>
    <title>Residential Colony</title>
    <titleShort>Settlers</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] new settlers.

Life, protection of fundamental activities that do not need to do anything.</desc>
  </ColonySettler53>
  <MedievalFarmOaf58>
    <title>Mean time farmers</title>
    <titleShort>farmer</titleShort>
    <desc>pulling the oxcart, he worked driving a shovel and wheelbarrow. Construction Digging ditches had pork, predicted.\n\nTraining medieval peasant did not exist in nature, not to grow food without the use of technology. However, intellectual property and technologies, including back to life, you can.</desc>
  </MedievalFarmOaf58>
  <MedievalLord57>
    <title>medieval nobility</title>
    <titleShort>charity</titleShort>
    <desc>With [PAWN_pronoun], gentle hand, can not finish and is still working .[PAWN_pronoun] tools, we believe that it is not compatible with you.</desc>
  </MedievalLord57>
  <UrbworldEntrepreneur14>
    <title>Urbworld</title>
    <titleShort>director</titleShort>
    <desc>Urbworld difficulties. [PAWN_nameDef] marketing skills (and fraudulent transactions, technical analysis) .[PAWN_pronoun] technical device that was placed in the company.</desc>
  </UrbworldEntrepreneur14>
  <DeepSpaceMiner3>
    <title>miners space</title>
    <titleShort>miner</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] excavation depth was covered with sweat, and every day the earth .[PAWN_pronoun] sad to dig a powerful force in the field of space, the store is aware of the war.</desc>
  </DeepSpaceMiner3>
  <NavyScientist46>
    <title>Marine science</title>
    <titleShort>science</titleShort>
    <desc>determined by the difference between winning and get technology called interstellar, the Navy and the new technology to learn more. Navy ministry works [PAWN_nameDef].</desc>
  </NavyScientist46>
  <MilitaryCommissar49>
    <title>Commissars</title>
    <titleShort>Political administration</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] is .[PAWN_pronoun] ordered a secret investigation of the imperial army soldiers or honest or do not oppose the manual, I was wary. [PAWN_objective] mission is hateful, on the other hand, it is [PAWN_pronoun], a little see through great skill lies.</desc>
  </MilitaryCommissar49>
  <MidworldChef92>
    <title>Kitchen midworld</title>
    <titleShort>foods</titleShort>
    <desc>To help [PAWN_nameDef] .[PAWN_pronoun] restaurant served delicious food midworld term, but he tricked the disease asong- [PAWN_possessive] food has earned a reputation for creative [PAWN_possessive] kitchen is popular with his colleagues.</desc>
  </MidworldChef92>
  <MedievalMinstrel95>
    <title>medieval musician</title>
    <titleShort>crowd</titleShort>
    <desc>Medieval [PAWN_nameDef] wandering comedians.

i always look at the history of [PAWN_pronoun] hands, sing a poem, you have the opportunity to follow the dangerous there. However, at the end of the hard work it has always been unclear impressive [PAWN_pronoun].</desc>
  </MedievalMinstrel95>
  <Housemate8>
    <title>Housewife / househusband</title>
    <titleShort>Homemaker / housewife</titleShort>
    <desc>Adult [PAWN_nameDef], go to work, take care of all the workers and [PAWN_possessive] wife.</desc>
  </Housemate8>
  <GlitterworldEmpath26>
    <title>Glitterworld enpasu</title>
    <titleShort>Enpasu</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] other reading your mind, it is also possible to choose in the way of drama, conflict .[PAWN_pronoun] enpasu for its awesome power. This was hurt [PAWN_possessive], however, such as training, capacity building, and he can no longer [PAWN_pronoun].</desc>
  </GlitterworldEmpath26>
  <MedievalDoctor40>
    <title>medieval doctors</title>
    <titleShort>healer</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun] medical director of anesthesia, the experience opened up a cut in our special events.</desc>
  </MedievalDoctor40>
  <Inventor6>
    <title>created by elevating</title>
    <titleShort>brolly</titleShort>
    <desc>As the inventor of the world [PAWN_possessive] [PAWN_nameDef] .[PAWN_pronoun] a large part of the technical work was a very successful development.</desc>
  </Inventor6>
  <Teacher20>
    <title>why</title>
    <titleShort>the teacher</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] .[PAWN_pronoun] [PAWN_possessive] student, appeared in person from public schools to provide a range of information packed with the usual school education, it is a simple concept.</desc>
  </Teacher20>
  <JoywireArtist8>
    <title>Joy artist thread</title>
    <titleShort>Joy</titleShort>
    <desc>Urbworld [PAWN_nameDef] modern state programming wire, the maximum for the benefit of laboratory development, installation, and users, he said.

The joy of the government, and to impose strict restrictions on domestic production of wire, [PAWN_pronoun], which began in the products that carry [PAWN_possessive] Urisaba on the black market.</desc>
  </JoywireArtist8>
  <ConceptualArtist39>
    <title>artists Avant-Garde</title>
    <titleShort>Artist</titleShort>
    <desc>You can create the highest in the world [PAWN_nameDef] unique work of art, popular art.\n\n[PAWN_pronoun] but no one was trying to make it a very respectable collection of the house or we express [PAWN_possessive] work he believed would be.</desc>
  </ConceptualArtist39>
  <GlitterworldSurgeon15>
    <title>Surgeons glitter world</title>
    <titleShort>doctor</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] it is more disease and illness in their land, working as a surgeon.

[PAWN_pronoun] at work, more is required of modern plastic surgery and innovative .[PAWN_pronoun] familiar with the ecology of the people, but cancer is not any cut. Even a bullet.</desc>
  </GlitterworldSurgeon15>
  <LudditeRebel43>
    <title>mechanical movement of</title>
    <titleShort>The movement of the car</titleShort>
    <desc>People on the ground [PAWN_possessive] cost, human biological characteristic, within the number of each human person, your hivemind (mesh) or even a connection to another network, [PAWN_nameDef] this type can be registered there are a select group.</desc>
  </LudditeRebel43>
  <Bartender55>
    <title>english bartender</title>
    <titleShort>barman</titleShort>
    <desc>He worked as a bartender at the station around [PAWN_nameDef]. Drink friendly, so workers have to act, not to beat mix.</desc>
  </Bartender55>
  <HiveworldDrone0>
    <title>Drone hive life</title>
    <titleShort>Elaborated</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] large beehive civilized world is now considered extinct .[PAWN_pronoun] drone, standing as innovation devastating cruel social experiments published, it can take the public authorities.</desc>
  </HiveworldDrone0>
  <Evangelist39>
    <title>propagator</title>
    <titleShort>and Mubashsh</titleShort>
    <desc>I like to spread the unique cultural traditions, [PAWN_nameDef] .[PAWN_pronoun] God and I believe in God and the teachings of my life, relax and wake up around [PAWN_possessive], and decided to spend a glorious childhood.</desc>
  </Evangelist39>
  <CaveworldIlluminator23>
    <title>lead caveworld</title>
    <titleShort>Management-hand</titleShort>
    <desc>People in general, especially as a philosopher and prayed many excavations C Caveman, bear [PAWN_nameDef] .[PAWN_pronoun], as well as the opening of a mushroom or something dangerous.</desc>
  </CaveworldIlluminator23>
  <Herbalist54>
    <title>plants Collection</title>
    <titleShort>period</titleShort>
    <desc>He lives in the woods near the village called [PAWN_nameDef]. The most expensive - however, many of the villages are afraid [PAWN_objective], source of disease [PAWN_objective], [PAWN_pronoun] bitter inhabitants, patch, or ointment from the Herb Garden, I was willing to modify habits [PAWN_pronoun] [PAWN_possessive] where to look for help.</desc>
  </Herbalist54>
  <CivilServant2>
    <title>official</title>
    <titleShort>employee</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] .[PAWN_pronoun] served as a minister under the government's bureaucracy and the written document, we have a sophisticated technique of people are familiar with at home.</desc>
  </CivilServant2>
  <AsceticPriest11>
    <title>acquisition priest</title>
    <titleShort>display</titleShort>
    <desc>Found herbs image [PAWN_pronoun] and joy or opportunities or garden monastery chizi.</desc>
  </AsceticPriest11>
  <EscapedConvict10>
    <title>completed Escape</title>
    <titleShort>Escapee</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef], but denied that he was involved in the crime, was secretly canalization use a spoon and fork, as well as convict colony to keep .[PAWN_pronoun] hand.</desc>
  </EscapedConvict10>
  <StarshipJanitor33>
    <title>Starship Crew</title>
    <titleShort>Train Staff</titleShort>
    <desc>The other passengers when a cold sleep, lying [PAWN_nameDef] equipment, and make sure that the navigation system is lubricated regularly Mekanoido for reference while walking back and forth to the stars, to be sure.</desc>
  </StarshipJanitor33>
  <Nurse53>
    <title>nurse</title>
    <titleShort>or</titleShort>
    <desc>Industrial thermal [PAWN_nameDef] old body, dressed in a hospital to perform everyday activities.

It makes the office is busy, but the patient's voice [PAWN_pronoun] found the time.</desc>
  </Nurse53>
  <HouseServant35>
    <title>employee</title>
    <titleShort>employee</titleShort>
    <desc>And [PAWN_pronoun] rich servants, aristocrats were abducted in [PAWN_nameDef].\n\nWithout any [PAWN_pronoun] and a lot of the kitchen of the house in the basement now.</desc>
  </HouseServant35>
  <Bodyguard26>
    <title>bodyguard</title>
    <titleShort>Be on the body</titleShort>
    <desc>And fight with many, prince [PAWN_pronoun] dangerous, and it is always good cruel nature to protect the value of the economic activity and .[PAWN_pronoun] midworld, [PAWN_nameDef] in.</desc>
  </Bodyguard26>
  <Novelist7>
    <title>novelist</title>
    <titleShort>writer</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] glittervorld immersed in the novel, .[PAWN_pronoun] ... akekure, happy life of the party during the day, nighttime [PAWN_possessive] author bozorgir wire.</desc>
  </Novelist7>
  <Mathematician6>
    <title>mathematicians</title>
    <titleShort>Math teacher</titleShort>
    <desc>However, often shooting free [PAWN_pronoun] attackers, [PAWN_pronoun] other players, often laughing dedicated end.</desc>
  </Mathematician6>
  <Paramedic45>
    <title>emergency servers</title>
    <titleShort>instant</titleShort>
    <desc>For many years, [PAWN_pronoun] we see the gun, the bullet wound was treated [PAWN_objective] problem.</desc>
  </Paramedic45>
  <Castaway57>
    <title>unworthy</title>
    <titleShort>castaway</titleShort>
    <desc>A typical cruise ship to destroy the planet many years of driving in such a way .[PAWN_possessive] [PAWN_nameDef] unmanned shipwrecked settlement systems.</desc>
  </Castaway57>
  <Gardener31>
    <title>farmer</title>
    <titleShort>park</titleShort>
    <desc>As the industrial business, sales .[PAWN_nameDef] business houses rich and expensive, and the family gathered, the people.</desc>
  </Gardener31>
  <MafiaBoss17>
    <title>Mafia</title>
    <titleShort>head</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun] give them bribe officials to keep their faith in our collection agent - if necessary using the</desc>
  </MafiaBoss17>
  <Torturer92>
    <title>haranahara administration</title>
    <titleShort>sentence performer</titleShort>
    <desc>World authoritarian reign serve as king. [PAWN_nameDef] 'convince' reputation as a master. He was detained in prison, it can be displayed on a secret - laugh [PAWN_nameDef] plan, constantly dangerous nightmare.</desc>
  </Torturer92>
  <ConstructionEngineer94>
    <title>architect</title>
    <titleShort>carpenter</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun] work had just eaten, so cooking [PAWN_pronoun].</desc>
  </ConstructionEngineer94>
  <Blacksmith72>
    <title>Smith</title>
    <titleShort>blacksmith</titleShort>
    <desc>In the Middle Ages, an architect, .[PAWN_pronoun] [PAWN_nameDef] in obtaining a reputation for quality service [PAWN_possessive] a blacksmith, is excellent, and the sword, not bad for users.</desc>
  </Blacksmith72>
  <CharityWorker36>
    <title>thankless</title>
    <titleShort>you</titleShort>
    <desc>Glittervorld hour, who live here, but the ease and comfort, because people in heaven, [PAWN_nameDef], people suffering from poverty, .[PAWN_pronoun] agree not around the world, from the use of, complain of donations and help people in need.</desc>
  </CharityWorker36>
  <Defector78>
    <title>gunfire</title>
    <titleShort>Earth</titleShort>
    <desc>becoming an adult in the early days, [PAWN_nameDef] [PAWN_pronoun] [PAWN_pronoun] oppressive dictatorship [PAWN_objective] Otte living in exile in the country do not have the intelligence to decide to leave the country.

[PAWN_pronoun] time because of its treatment of trauma, even many years nonexistent disciples fled the countryside because doctors do not [PAWN_objective]: The temptation [PAWN_objective], hateful, they do not believe.</desc>
  </Defector78>
  <FactoryWorker27>
    <title>plant worker</title>
    <titleShort>staff</titleShort>
    <desc>Felix said in the industrial core businesses.

Some left, a short supply of food in [PAWN_pronoun] [PAWN_pronoun] of them have a piece of work and income can not. We had a comfortable life, such as hard work, but Felik.</desc>
  </FactoryWorker27>
  <RanchOwner43>
    <title>farmer</title>
    <titleShort>Rancher</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun] for each job is different, it was no one else.</desc>
  </RanchOwner43>
  <LowWageWorker7>
    <title>Layer salaried workers</title>
    <titleShort>Adding</titleShort>
    <desc>After [PAWN_nameDef] to know the basis of different part-time jobs for supporting their families [PAWN_possessive] bag.</desc>
  </LowWageWorker7>
  <Model99>
    <title>sampling</title>
    <titleShort>model</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef], that pattern jewelry agriculture and customs, as a model for 3d characters in a virtual world, open background information.</desc>
  </Model99>
  <Taxonomist0>
    <title>to learn</title>
    <titleShort>takonomists</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef], stars, and if the diagnosis is a big secret and images of flora and fauna.</desc>
  </Taxonomist0>
  <Geologist66>
    <title>geologist</title>
    <titleShort>geologist</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] of the miners, workers hit a hole is to create a geological and mineral appraiser.

Metro will, [PAWN_pronoun] and digging machines that are set the same experience with other industrial applications.</desc>
  </Geologist66>
  <Sailor60>
    <title>mariners</title>
    <titleShort>sailor</titleShort>
    <desc>In some cases, rude, at least out of the land who .[PAWN_pronoun] .[PAWN_pronoun] sea water in plants and animals, and a lot of love for the exploitation of the country, to work hard to collect samples [PAWN_nameDef], waste disposal than all the other resources [PAWN_pronoun].</desc>
  </Sailor60>
  <Jailbird40>
    <title>relapse</title>
    <titleShort>Repeat case</titleShort>
    <desc>As a prisoner [PAWN_nameDef] [PAWN_possessive] life, [PAWN_pronoun] .[PAWN_pronoun] food retailers that a madman who are looking to war was announced, is financially sound ndosh.</desc>
  </Jailbird40>
  <Actor42>
    <title>actor</title>
    <titleShort>Employee</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef], with star actors [PAWN_possessive] colleagues and you are returned to the theater perfection from us, he .[PAWN_pronoun] or tribal community will be surprised, some of these can not be used, what kind of props and costumes,</desc>
  </Actor42>
  <Tactician37>
    <title>a piece</title>
    <titleShort>strategy</titleShort>
    <desc>This latter way the matter of the planets and the world as the first one of the troops of .[PAWN_pronoun] [PAWN_nameDef] was looking for war with fierce and absurd it is to the ability of the players he had commanded the army.</desc>
  </Tactician37>
  <GlitterworldOfficer60>
    <title>Officer glitterworld</title>
    <titleShort>loon</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun] it, but pursue interests in art, is governed [PAWN_possessive] choose to attend martial arts [PAWN_nameDef] satisfied battle.</desc>
  </GlitterworldOfficer60>
  <Taster16>
    <title>Main commitment</title>
    <titleShort>Enrollment key</titleShort>
    <desc>Central to the idea of the world, all the dishes of the Council, .[PAWN_pronoun] [PAWN_nameDef], due to the style of the Royal Palace corner, and who just finished a little work to confirm, you are fat.</desc>
  </Taster16>
  <BiosphereManager95>
    <title>Bacteria Work</title>
    <titleShort>botanist</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] the work attractive to work, people live in peace glitterworld mac kurer break .[PAWN_pronoun] division scoured the park management, the face of the landscape, plants and animals.</desc>
  </BiosphereManager95>
  <Veterinarian8>
    <title>vet</title>
    <titleShort>veterinary</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef], in life should be or injured animals. Images of suffering, [PAWN_possessive] few years later, the meat, bear [PAWN_pronoun] plants, insects, carnivorous plants [PAWN_possessive] traditionally lived in a house in the middle of the world agree.</desc>
  </Veterinarian8>
  <ExplosivesExpert26>
    <title>professional bomb</title>
    <titleShort>blaster</titleShort>
    <desc>How [PAWN_pronoun] there [PAWN_pronoun] are carefully calculated - [PAWN_nameDef] .[PAWN_pronoun] engineer environment art, I was engaged in mining experience to go against a lot of knowledge, [PAWN_possessive], 'bleach explosion they need help, not less quality.</desc>
  </ExplosivesExpert26>
  <Counselor26>
    <title>consultant</title>
    <titleShort>member</titleShort>
    <desc>Terrible shock when he was a teenager [PAWN_nameDef], I decided [PAWN_objective] bulimia. Meeting [PAWN_pronoun] which explores the relationship between diet and health, it is essential [PAWN_pronoun] to help overcome emotional problems, I decided to use [PAWN_possessive] new skills.</desc>
  </Counselor26>
  <Recruiter4>
    <title>An obligation</title>
    <titleShort>Participation in</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun] want to [PAWN_possessive] parent star, young people met in [PAWN_pronoun] and proof that the person is determined to be suitable for training.</desc>
  </Recruiter4>
  <PsychiatricPatient94>
    <title>Bedbugs have suffered</title>
    <titleShort>patient</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] adult life spent more than a mental hospital. The production of disease in the brain, to understand what Mr. Murphy said star beast blooming human hometown that got treatment [PAWN_pronoun] instead.\n\nBut when he finally released the basic skills of life significantly reduced.</desc>
  </PsychiatricPatient94>
  <Drifter67>
    <title>Nenashigusa</title>
    <titleShort>Nenashigusa</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] what life was arrested, I was connected to a short-term work in view of the path he thought was .[PAWN_pronoun].\n\nSometimes, [PAWN_pronoun], but be sure of the best-selling author is writing new - to all visitors, even now.</desc>
  </Drifter67>
  <VRDesigner87>
    <title>VR</title>
    <titleShort>creators</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef], the earth simulator of virtual reality are being developed in the citizens of the world. As a more immediate nature, I learned as much as possible to focus on the details of the plant.</desc>
  </VRDesigner87>
  <HumanComputer7>
    <title>Computer people</title>
    <titleShort>computer</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] this brain tumor, was diagnosed with the natural law, which is complex, the best skills and memory. Mid-World dictator, and the cost to the economy of the country and decided to rent [PAWN_nameDef]. Due to the risk of computer enthusiasts.</desc>
  </HumanComputer7>
  <Architect28>
    <title>author</title>
    <titleShort>Architects</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] on design and architecture of the building steps. [PAWN_possessive] shine in his house in the world, AI players on the technical aspects of construction. This was the result of an act of increasing employment in the maximum [PAWN_possessive] art, but at the same time, I think, also, that there is no need [PAWN_pronoun] your dirty hands to enter the site.</desc>
  </Architect28>
  <MessageCarrier77>
    <title>delivery person</title>
    <titleShort>delivery Man</titleShort>
    <desc>In the Middle Ages the best way to send a message, Tadoritsukeru lives in each of the other world, then wanted .[PAWN_nameDef] riders, this is a is.</desc>
  </MessageCarrier77>
  <Sculptor63>
    <title>Engraver</title>
    <titleShort>expert</titleShort>
    <desc>He went on stone cutting [PAWN_nameDef] soon started making a big hand. Along with the drilling robot, but in the case [PAWN_pronoun] learned most northern flavor. As soon as a nature park, which remains [PAWN_pronoun] Glitterworld, the big picture.</desc>
  </Sculptor63>
  <MachineCollector55>
    <title>machine collectors</title>
    <titleShort>Collection</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun], [PAWN_possessive] collection, had to listen to it.</desc>
  </MachineCollector55>
  <Sheriff52>
    <title>Tabish</title>
    <titleShort>ruling</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef], police can .[PAWN_pronoun] factory different city, .[PAWN_pronoun] which was known as the bad boy behavior, temperature, destination, it is a cult, not revenge, has so far refused to say you're taking.</desc>
  </Sheriff52>
  <ConArtist80>
    <title>false</title>
    <titleShort>perfidious</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] is [PAWN_possessive] world. But some naturally occurring [PAWN_pronoun] been received.</desc>
  </ConArtist80>
  <MedievalSlave49>
    <title>Slavery in the Middle Ages</title>
    <titleShort>Slave</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] medievalworld wagon bridge, dig a hole in my life. [PAWN_pronoun] does not learn to write and read, and up to nine years.</desc>
  </MedievalSlave49>
  <MedievalLordling19>
    <title>Small medieval king</title>
    <titleShort>little Prince</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] the nobles of the ancient roman .[PAWN_pronoun] of the reign of the building of the lessons in the second or to the idea of a stone.

Real life, health, and all without the inherent reluctance to learn skills and hand - on the other hand, [PAWN_nameDef] to learn how to drive them begins.</desc>
  </MedievalLordling19>
  <UrbworldUrchin61>
    <title>Enemy urbworld</title>
    <titleShort>spoof</titleShort>
    <desc>Live in the poor neighborhoods of black urbworld world. Neglect it, [PAWN_pronoun], fight for food your eyes, in the way the clothes alone.

In the end, talent [PAWN_possessive] runners [PAWN_pronoun] purchased under the dark surface of the Earth. And behind her mother.</desc>
  </UrbworldUrchin61>
  <VatgrownSoldier8>
    <title>Soldiers vatgrown</title>
    <titleShort>Vatgrown</titleShort>
    <desc>A man is approved. in place of the destroyed [PAWN_nameDef] ,. Biological growth zero growth. [PAWN_possessive] While the development of learning combat techniques still have the habit. [PAWN_nameDef] Fight reluctance to be in human relations.</desc>
  </VatgrownSoldier8>
  <SicklyChild72>
    <title>sick children</title>
    <titleShort>Baby disease</titleShort>
    <desc>I was a kid, and they were wonderful [PAWN_nameDef] disease. It is separated from the hospital research centers, [PAWN_pronoun] only minimum requirements, not much, not related to the group. However, the hospital is very common in the desert of life science and the Pharmaceutical [PAWN_pronoun].</desc>
  </SicklyChild72>
  <ShelterChild50>
    <title>Children's TV</title>
    <titleShort>the protection of children on board</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef], we can not be blessed in the education of the toxic deep .[PAWN_pronoun] the largest in the world of the world of manual labor.</desc>
  </ShelterChild50>
  <IndustrialOrphan13>
    <title>industry orphans</title>
    <titleShort>Orphans</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] you what you need to know a lot .[PAWN_pronoun] childhood memories of parents, and labor to mine, it is only the industrial world [PAWN_possessive] nursing home.

 [PAWN_pronoun] not find a suitable education.</desc>
  </IndustrialOrphan13>
  <Scout94>
    <title>human</title>
    <titleShort>personnel information</titleShort>
    <desc>Nate seems natural. parents, plan to test your knowledge of military research, allowed to join him. You can not leave them in the wilderness; do good.

The [PAWN_nameDef] art, such as the aging of the others, such as saving as followed.</desc>
  </Scout94>
  <FrightenedChild43>
    <title>Fear of children</title>
    <titleShort>fear</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef], neurosis yalayala fear, on behalf of the list of diseases for a long time to raise funds .[PAWN_pronoun], doctors worry prepared illusion, and food.

As a result, even when wearing [PAWN_pronoun] process of preparing conditions, it is the growth of the most disadvantaged target [PAWN_objective].</desc>
  </FrightenedChild43>
  <CaveworldTender20>
    <title>The supervisor Cave</title>
    <titleShort>his children</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] deep beneath the earth's only, its complexity .[PAWN_pronoun] proposed working with the other boys fungus is a plant species.</desc>
  </CaveworldTender20>
  <CaveworldTunneler48>
    <title>Bolivians cavevorld</title>
    <titleShort>Miner</titleShort>
    <desc>There are about [PAWN_pronoun] forward in a cave from the center was also good to see the stone.</desc>
  </CaveworldTunneler48>
  <ComaChild57>
    <title>Children vegetative state</title>
    <titleShort>vegetable kingdom</titleShort>
    <desc>In the event of an accident, children [PAWN_nameDef] .[PAWN_pronoun], who fell into a coma not to wake young people. [PAWN_possessive] run healthy body and a lack of exercise, but good people will [PAWN_possessive].</desc>
  </ComaChild57>
  <Pyromaniac18>
    <title>Firebug</title>
    <titleShort>Firebug</titleShort>
    <desc>the stars and the fire burned flame or excessive violation of the flame will be interesting garbage I felt I was young, [PAWN_nameDef] .[PAWN_pronoun] mountains.\n\nIf the game ODI [PAWN_pronoun] we have the right to accidental burning house.</desc>
  </Pyromaniac18>
  <Mute34>
    <title>loss of speech</title>
    <titleShort>loss statement</titleShort>
    <desc>Trauma [PAWN_nameDef], strongly influenced by the program [PAWN_possessive] early in life. Now, at the end of [PAWN_pronoun] to talk for a few years, but went to play with the animals.</desc>
  </Mute34>
  <WarRefugee51>
    <title>War Refugees</title>
    <titleShort>them that have escaped</titleShort>
    <desc>War, and the destruction of [PAWN_nameDef] world.

Little collect food and property, father [PAWN_nameDef], ship to escape the planet.</desc>
  </WarRefugee51>
  <MusicLover86>
    <title>Favorite music ~~ POS = TRUNC ~~ POS = HEAD progressive</title>
    <titleShort>musician</titleShort>
    <desc>Children, [PAWN_nameDef] or music playback, .[PAWN_pronoun] want to sing a song, he received professional training, opened the concert or a recital. So much is not allowed because [PAWN_pronoun] proud man who was generous with praise.</desc>
  </MusicLover86>
  <ChildStar74>
    <title>m a child actor</title>
    <titleShort>popular</titleShort>
    <desc>And television and children by [PAWN_nameDef], movies [PAWN_possessive] .[PAWN_pronoun] reputation is well known throughout the world, not only was a different kind of training on both sides of the mouth [PAWN_objective] contact person, I was invited to [PAWN_possessive] results.</desc>
  </ChildStar74>
  <ChildSpy53>
    <title>spy kids</title>
    <titleShort>spies</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun] infiltration in enemy territory era, world war [PAWN_possessive] [PAWN_pronoun] to destroy the essence of the meaning is, only within a limited range given an opportunity.</desc>
  </ChildSpy53>
  <Shopkeeper36>
    <title>Commerce store</title>
    <titleShort>trade</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] reduce sick mother, a family store, fill only source of income, hanging on the shoulders [PAWN_pronoun] .[PAWN_pronoun] operations are highly dependent on foreign trade crafts in the country, with a little knowledge and education.</desc>
  </Shopkeeper36>
  <OrganFarm67>
    <title>plant organ</title>
    <titleShort>Organ factory</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] is .[PAWN_possessive] illegal body in dark industrial groups but .[PAWN_possessive] education, which is used as a means to promote organic part for wounded soldiers scar left on the heart and results in a unique understanding of the human body.</desc>
  </OrganFarm67>
  <ConventChild16>
    <title>Religious children</title>
    <titleShort>infidelity</titleShort>
    <desc>The monastery obedient, a child born in the medieval world [PAWN_nameDef], not .[PAWN_pronoun] learned about hard, but in this case the result is that the price at once, this is heresy to learn the technology.</desc>
  </ConventChild16>
  <TestSubject15>
    <title>experimental body</title>
    <titleShort>test body</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] test of quantum mechanics of the geometry of the hopes, sometimes without injury.

"Test and the red door on the other side, for example, at the end, although the sound was heard, and I will be with you." One day he said to me</desc>
  </TestSubject15>
  <MedicalAssistant82>
    <title>Sisters</title>
    <titleShort>sister</titleShort>
    <desc>Napalm together with two other army [PAWN_nameDef] [PAWN_pronoun] catastrophic war, the parents of burns and open a hospital [PAWN_pronoun] the war, life was born in the midst of the fire to the hospital.</desc>
  </MedicalAssistant82>
  <CultChild3>
    <title>The popular Children</title>
    <titleShort>premieres children</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] just the latest science, "the disease of religious art will be enhanced by the refinement of the spirit of" strong religious cult faith was born.

Outside, for the first time, and from the look of a snapshot, [PAWN_pronoun] decide.</desc>
  </CultChild3>
  <WreckageExplorer8>
    <title>wreck shift</title>
    <titleShort>experts</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] even two generations before the birth, at the end of the last century of war .[PAWN_nameDef] home hikizurikomi earth disorganized year [PAWN_possessive] problem, an ox to keep pushing [PAWN_possessive] but kept powerful computer frequently, and threw the [PAWN_possessive] services, estimated broken spaceship it began on earth.</desc>
  </WreckageExplorer8>
  <ApocalypseSurvivor23>
    <title>ceases to exist</title>
    <titleShort>protection</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] problem was born at a time when that star is astonished. City .[PAWN_pronoun] as the presence of large numbers of climate change and extreme hunger increases and flooding caused by the reduction - hundreds of millions of people in the country still in conditions of turbulence. parents can live [PAWN_nameDef] nothing.</desc>
  </ApocalypseSurvivor23>
  <StoryWriter67>
    <title>Author</title>
    <titleShort>writer</titleShort>
    <desc>I was a child, every day immersed in reading books [PAWN_nameDef] .[PAWN_pronoun] reading in libraries across the area. If you are working budget of the library, which is closed to reduce [PAWN_nameDef] .[PAWN_pronoun] is badly mistaken, the difference in the heart, just to write a story, I decided to fulfill.</desc>
  </StoryWriter67>
  <Hermit12>
    <title>hermit</title>
    <titleShort>rabbi</titleShort>
    <desc>people who fled conflict [PAWN_nameDef] wide rustic life, this is the place to live [PAWN_pronoun], I left the city of Midworld dirty, or easy-care garden [PAWN_possessive] only one time in their lives.</desc>
  </Hermit12>
  <SpacePirate55>
    <title>Chuzoku</title>
    <titleShort>Chuzoku</titleShort>
    <desc>Where is the humanity gives you .[PAWN_nameDef] border fraud increases, out of ideas at any time, access to this section to destroy, steal gold merchant ship.</desc>
  </SpacePirate55>
  <PitBrawler76>
    <title>army</title>
    <titleShort>Gladiator</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] .[PAWN_pronoun] for the first time at the age of nine fight winning experience is very important to be able to enjoy conversations [PAWN_possessive]. Gladiators job, because you live a long time and found a lot of 'gold. In most cases, it is his position.</desc>
  </PitBrawler76>
  <IllegalShipwright76>
    <title>IamI shipbuilding industry</title>
    <titleShort>shipbuilding industry</titleShort>
    <desc>"Automotive Scoop is set to" rights and gamma must be equipped with a terawatt laser Tham each other. tools of communication devices, such as, if not, have a particularly .[PAWN_nameDef] can wait, but the people and the law of God to the production environment, only those who do not.</desc>
  </IllegalShipwright76>
  <Courtesean30>
    <title>prostitute</title>
    <titleShort>prostitute</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef], the star system, some brothels, many of 100 customers, [PAWN_pronoun] are made in the body, as found in some of the psychological characteristics and operations specific foods.</desc>
  </Courtesean30>
  <SpaceMarine16>
    <title>Coleoptera Marine</title>
    <titleShort>the sea</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_possessive] knowledge, sociability disease is about people, not rude, but do not know how to fight.</desc>
  </SpaceMarine16>
  <Assassin20>
    <title>Killer</title>
    <titleShort>deadly</titleShort>
    <desc>Robin has been training specifically to kill a high risk for the celebration. timeless followed by others, has become a matter of shooting ..

Since the objective of the program killed his arm has been issued, and vowed to never trust anyone .Robin funding has been allocated in the future.</desc>
  </Assassin20>
  <Gatherer40>
    <title>home</title>
    <titleShort>home collection</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef], plant crops [PAWN_possessive] in-depth with knowledge of the ground, roots may not be the largest in, buying food, as strawberries, storage master .[PAWN_pronoun] can find.</desc>
  </Gatherer40>
  <Loner40>
    <title>insulation</title>
    <titleShort>loneliness</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun], but in some cases, or visit [PAWN_possessive] usually take care of their viability.</desc>
  </Loner40>
  <Healer0>
    <title>doctor</title>
    <titleShort>doctor</titleShort>
    <desc>Mac and [PAWN_nameDef] not take the time to admire the beauty of the world.

He was restrained aggression full time, but he worked for some time has been struggling to adapt to the changed way of life.</desc>
  </Healer0>
  <Scout17>
    <title>Scout</title>
    <titleShort>scout</titleShort>
    <desc>Foreigners in the race for the local [PAWN_possessive] ,, [PAWN_nameDef] a local leader of the service contract. I [PAWN_objective], is very familiar with the old technology that allows permanent contact with remnants of the old.</desc>
  </Scout17>
  <Digger69>
    <title>Get to know the holes</title>
    <titleShort>Experts drilling</titleShort>
    <desc>I [PAWN_nameDef] [PAWN_possessive] tribe, dug deep into his village [PAWN_nameDef] reduction in mountainous areas, I think, that this excavation, and to get the best out of a hole dug in the cave support.</desc>
  </Digger69>
  <MuffaloShaman1>
    <title>Faro Map Sherman</title>
    <titleShort>sorcerer</titleShort>
    <desc>Sherman nomadic barbarians [PAWN_possessive] and control of high-growth stocks maffaro [PAWN_nameDef] smart display.</desc>
  </MuffaloShaman1>
  <LoreKeeper51>
    <title>think</title>
    <titleShort>Laure</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was educated first in a [PAWN_possessive]. Every night, around the fire, [PAWN_pronoun], legend, ancient wisdom and practical knowledge.</desc>
  </LoreKeeper51>
  <Weaver80>
    <title>expert knitting</title>
    <titleShort>expert in knitting</titleShort>
    <desc>For [PAWN_nameDef] brother [PAWN_possessive] natural death of plants [PAWN_pronoun] beautiful handmade objects in a professional clean clothes, hair die maffaro between local people say that most of the work.</desc>
  </Weaver80>
  <CaveTender66>
    <title>why paradise</title>
    <titleShort>Sponsors</titleShort>
    <desc>When someone is hunting lutanare [PAWN_nameDef], or stay at home to cook, put patient care.</desc>
  </CaveTender66>
  <Warrior94>
    <title>a hero who bravely</title>
    <titleShort>Military</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] .[PAWN_pronoun] it was a hero of world war i, which took place on the planet [PAWN_possessive], among others, the thread tension is due to the freezing deadlock helped prevent the firing of nuclear weapons.</desc>
  </Warrior94>
  <TribeChild68>
    <title>The Lion Children</title>
    <titleShort>race</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun] ancient ruins, for the car, except that you have seen and heard.</desc>
  </TribeChild68>
  <AbandonedChild60>
    <title>abandoned children</title>
    <titleShort>Sorry</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] .[PAWN_pronoun] born just looked sickly burden on the family and the parents great, and of course [PAWN_objective] points. No, he survived</desc>
  </AbandonedChild60>
  <ReclusiveChild82>
    <title>Insulation children</title>
    <titleShort>Separation children</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] [PAWN_pronoun] was wearing her even think about five years, and even at that age, not .[PAWN_pronoun] komori call home first youth, but [PAWN_pronoun] city, a few weeks now now roam wild.</desc>
  </ReclusiveChild82>
  <Herder58>
    <title>nurse</title>
    <titleShort>many</titleShort>
    <desc>Childhood, protect [PAWN_nameDef] month group Maffaro beauty and keep them that piracy "depends Hermitage, so taken care of. Although it seems quiet, inconspicuous, [PAWN_pronoun] live in one.</desc>
  </Herder58>
  <Scavenger22>
    <title>dump</title>
    <titleShort>scavenger</titleShort>
    <desc>He [PAWN_pronoun] clean technology and assistance, and how they live on earth.</desc>
  </Scavenger22>
  <CaveChild30>
    <title>Children</title>
    <titleShort>slot</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] season tundra day alcohol, "a move experts called" capture the agreement. After the trip, the crew met [PAWN_objective] amazing stories about the universe.

Scanning does not come from the master. After years of waiting, [PAWN_nameDef], it became clear that watching the same area.</desc>
  </CaveChild30>
  <SoleSurvivor9>
    <title>Only successful</title>
    <titleShort>graduates</titleShort>
    <desc>Hawke's relatives killed by the disease is difficult.

The child is only one person was found, but said the decision of tired of people like indigenous [PAWN_pronoun], it can not be attached emotionally to a new location during the absence or walks in the woods, I do not care about the animals.</desc>
  </SoleSurvivor9>
  <VengefulChild43>
    <title>orphans Revenge</title>
    <titleShort>revenge</titleShort>
    <desc>When I had children, [PAWN_nameDef] Thief .[PAWN_pronoun], urban [PAWN_possessive] Massacre was returned villain swears revenge attacks on troops in the desert.</desc>
  </VengefulChild43>
  <FireKeeper22>
    <title>fire</title>
    <titleShort>fire brigade</titleShort>
    <desc>We were responsible [PAWN_nameDef], .[PAWN_pronoun] is responsible for a significant source of the fire.</desc>
  </FireKeeper22>
  <FallenProdigy79>
    <title>fallen in children</title>
    <titleShort>monster</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] .[PAWN_pronoun] umareochi father died in the world beauty spot.

[PAWN_pronoun] utmaior university scholarships to fight or to prove worthy of the list. [PAWN_pronoun] substrate, such as children in the house, the child will not be able to make friends.</desc>
  </FallenProdigy79>
  <MadScientist36>
    <title>University</title>
    <titleShort>scientists</titleShort>
    <desc>After completion of training, is hired by a small seed [PAWN_nameDef] organization. Later, inhuman encountered during the trial illegal.

If convicted of influential people in the family, has been sentenced to forced labor in prison.</desc>
  </MadScientist36>
  <FarmKid40>
    <title>Children's Ranch</title>
    <titleShort>Kindergarten</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] grows in the fields. He or she is responsible for the cattle, hay and enjoyment in work.</desc>
  </FarmKid40>
  <CivilEngineer23>
    <title>engineer</title>
    <titleShort>engineer</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] is .[PAWN_pronoun] this work was popular .[PAWN_pronoun] maintains a complex system, established stone as a building engineer given sufficient statistical analysis in order to keep the mind sharp.</desc>
  </CivilEngineer23>
  <FarmerBoy63>
    <title>young farmers</title>
    <titleShort>Farmhouse</titleShort>
    <desc>Benjamin's parents died in a fire when he was seven years. He was on his uncle's farm: physical work, or work in the fields.

Due to their parents communicating Instead, he could not bear to answer questions about working diligently company.</desc>
  </FarmerBoy63>
  <ArmyCook51>
    <title>army cooks</title>
    <titleShort>cooking soldiers</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef], when employees ranks in the army, and spent much time cooking repair. dangerous planet, [PAWN_pronoun] weight and balance of basic surgical training.</desc>
  </ArmyCook51>
  <UrbworldCriminal64>
    <title>Urbworld of criminals</title>
    <titleShort>thieves</titleShort>
    <desc>overpopulation environment Urbworld born poor, hungry and cold Shomonai Vladimir escape sin.

Vladimir theft and murder, for it to survive, I learned that it was an everyday occurrence, you will not be able to win.</desc>
  </UrbworldCriminal64>
  <UrbworldPolitican16>
    <title>Urbvorld system</title>
    <titleShort>Policy</titleShort>
    <desc>With urbworld, a group company that owns most .vladimir and bribery, which is no secret, is one of the president.

He said that when I was living in a penthouse comfort, and how to do it, dreams and hopes, I learned how to deal with them skillfully.</desc>
  </UrbworldPolitican16>
  <OptimisticChild43>
    <title>A new brain-child</title>
    <titleShort>noticeable</titleShort>
    <desc>Kees loving parents blessed, wonderful life midworld sent. She welcomed her beloved son, friend, friends, date, friend heard. He said he could not imagine an island in the views according to the questions.</desc>
  </OptimisticChild43>
  <GraphicDesigner99>
    <title>design</title>
    <titleShort>The designer</titleShort>
    <desc>Kees impressed innovation creator. It is about raising Mezato artists are well-known on the planet, but its size often more time to work perfectly.</desc>
  </GraphicDesigner99>
  <UrbworldHooligan72>
    <title>Nelly urbworld</title>
    <titleShort>Harry</titleShort>
    <desc>Crime [PAWN_nameDef] food ... more dangerous urbworld .[PAWN_pronoun]. So there is room for cooking and development capabilities there.</desc>
  </UrbworldHooligan72>
  <SpaceTechnician1>
    <title>space engineers</title>
    <titleShort>text</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] is located near the space station, can not agree to support the work, and it's just a criminal nigedase life. He's the amendment, and activists said. And basic research activities, and in a discussion with his colleagues quietly participated. Do not fiction.</desc>
  </SpaceTechnician1>
  <IndworldUrchin73>
    <title>No indworld</title>
    <titleShort>thief</titleShort>
    <desc>The industrial revolution in the past raised the farm laborers and theft [PAWN_nameDef] .[PAWN_pronoun], he is always looking for people to escape poverty, and pray that the day after the abandoned equipment.</desc>
  </IndworldUrchin73>
  <DoomsdayPariah24>
    <title>Drifters last day</title>
    <titleShort>Hobo</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef], then drilled .[PAWN_pronoun] cleaning technology fails, the error that all life on earth can clean the gun that you have to pull the trigger to open the cellar. In addition, people are very interested in this technology, [PAWN_pronoun] on board the spacecraft, which is in the basement, while others began to seek shelter.</desc>
  </DoomsdayPariah24>
  <ChildScientist25>
    <title>scientists for children</title>
    <titleShort>Scientist</titleShort>
    <desc>Young graduated from college, because that David was [PAWN_nameDef] [PAWN_possessive] lifeblood. He wanted to know the reasons for arrest.

Authorities announced the first [PAWN_objective] under certain conditions. A state that is working at the Institute of Technology of government to travel between the stars. Free time can be allowed to continue to pursue personal.</desc>
  </ChildScientist25>
  <CombatEngineer30>
    <title>engineer</title>
    <titleShort>engineer</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] combat, army engineers in order to create firearms use and maintenance of vehicles .[PAWN_pronoun] place - when people photography, who do not [PAWN_pronoun]</desc>
  </CombatEngineer30>
  <MechanoidNerd10>
    <title>Computer Methods isoprenoid</title>
    <titleShort>Geek Technical isoprenoid</titleShort>
    <desc>Urbworld [PAWN_nameDef] izoprenoidovym mechanical designer for a child. The abandoned and slowly-slowly Rate mechanism, and finally, [PAWN_pronoun] now and I think I can only [PAWN_possessive] machines.

Unfortunately, my friends, technical books, [PAWN_objective] be brought to you.</desc>
  </MechanoidNerd10>
  <MilitaryEngineer45>
    <title>military engineer</title>
    <titleShort>engineer</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] is .[PAWN_pronoun] lower engineers as a colony guns, robots and other weapons work was related.

[PAWN_pronoun] worn with mekanoido tools specializes in repairing it. And sometimes, I try them yourself.</desc>
  </MilitaryEngineer45>
  <ColiseumCleaner54>
    <title>Shula Colosseum</title>
    <titleShort>white</titleShort>
    <desc>Nuclear Civil War, [PAWN_possessive] [PAWN_pronoun] not born into slavery. After gold, in the Great Hall to wash blood with blood, fighting, were given fresh energy. Just know the gym, [PAWN_pronoun], anywhere. One night, while cleaning the Coliseum, family [PAWN_possessive] was completely dead.</desc>
  </ColiseumCleaner54>
  <ColiseumFighter12>
    <title>gladiators</title>
    <titleShort>woodman</titleShort>
    <desc>After that year, they are skilled fighters to use that knowledge. [PAWN_pronoun] Coliseum now successfully Jones.</desc>
  </ColiseumFighter12>
  <OfficerCadet81>
    <title>graduate</title>
    <titleShort>IPL</titleShort>
    <desc>From a young Bashkire, we have learned to be a leader. He signed the National Defense Academy wadding I was a kid, now it was a long-range weapons and survival training.</desc>
  </OfficerCadet81>
  <FighterController64>
    <title>air control officer</title>
    <titleShort>management team</titleShort>
    <desc>Zartha during the crisis, the war is to fight for bashkir, the control authorities citizens between the soil and air. During the war, we have just seen, or injured slaves were killed. Today, this dream is a blow. Now, less existing.</desc>
  </FighterController64>
  <ReclusiveProdigy98>
    <title>even now</title>
    <titleShort>genius</titleShort>
    <desc>Holly focus on the study to whitewash the world of development and prosperity.

Since I was a child, I grew up with manipulation and culture of nerve cells genetic.</desc>
  </ReclusiveProdigy98>
  <FerventResearcher44>
    <title>investigator read it carefully and</title>
    <titleShort>researcher</titleShort>
    <desc>For the young, Holly, people have believed that the world is very close to the time and transcends time.

Now his research is more concerned with shield and bioethics committees to be able to encourage lobbying of humor as a community that is a burden as a test of confidence.</desc>
  </FerventResearcher44>
  <WarRefugee81>
    <title>war refugees</title>
    <titleShort>refugees</titleShort>
    <desc>The war destroyed home planet [PAWN_nameDef].

Father of the empty part [PAWN_nameDef] atmosphere robber fled with boat.</desc>
  </WarRefugee81>
  <VengefulExplorer27>
    <title>Coping and sales</title>
    <titleShort>actor</titleShort>
    <desc>If there .[PAWN_pronoun] homeless vagrants, [PAWN_nameDef] and his father, one hundred years of salt and pepper Shooting capital now has fought many wars.

After the death of his father the war [PAWN_nameDef] father to take revenge on opponents, and they began to explore.</desc>
  </VengefulExplorer27>
  <WorkCampSlave49>
    <title>To go back to the worship service</title>
    <titleShort>Sindhis</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] increasing showers especially around the middle of the evil of slavery.

It is difficult, it is difficult to study the issue of work, we decided to harden his body.</desc>
  </WorkCampSlave49>
  <BanishedSoldier76>
    <title>the captured soldiers</title>
    <titleShort>Outlaw</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] it was because his body to a fire slave tattoos everywhere, is made, and spend a little time to spare. King supervisory body work and effort is [PAWN_possessive] a reward at the end.

After killing the king, and tried to use his position to escape slavery. The program, but it was Nigedase one way or slave life.</desc>
  </BanishedSoldier76>
  <DisciplinedFarmer44>
    <title>Trained farmers money</title>
    <titleShort>grandfather</titleShort>
    <desc>Yes, the children of two brothers. To discipline their children a successful family farm .Drew people who adhere strictly to the border area and obedience Umidaso thoroughly searched. For handmade, as long as there is life, it is time to try to make breakfast in a dangerous time.</desc>
  </DisciplinedFarmer44>
  <StalwartFarmer89>
    <title>strong farmer</title>
    <titleShort>farmer</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun] time is an attempt to drive home, he wrote something not just duck.</desc>
  </StalwartFarmer89>
  <VoyagerChild94>
    <title>child passengers</title>
    <titleShort>passenger</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] this was, I spent much of his childhood in space travel.

My ship, following .[PAWN_possessive] serious damage is completely secret hand repair, which of course, out of the asteroid's orbit ,, he said. [PAWN_pronoun] long before I was interested in the scientific study of the paranormal.</desc>
  </VoyagerChild94>
  <SpaceResearcher56>
    <title>experts vacancy rate</title>
    <titleShort>researchers</titleShort>
    <desc>Childhood variety [PAWN_pronoun] once-laden culture, although most of his life isolated in space, it was that he did not lose heart.</desc>
  </SpaceResearcher56>
  <VatgrownMedic46>
    <title>Operation vatgrown</title>
    <titleShort>surgeon</titleShort>
    <desc>This rose to battalion level, [PAWN_nameDef] drugs, of course, that weapons qualifying. When soldiers suffered injuries, the popular phrase, "life and death?" It may be that most of the soldiers, but I choose life</desc>
  </VatgrownMedic46>
  <GeneticScientist4>
    <title>Talivijnanigalu</title>
    <titleShort>gene</titleShort>
    <desc>After the war, he joined the genetically engineered agriculture. Ie, goods and animals is necessary. Besides the care consumer champions opened the useful work of black humor. However, if you make the most of the area.</desc>
  </GeneticScientist4>
  <CoreDilettante99>
    <title>hobby</title>
    <titleShort>Amateur</titleShort>
    <desc>Candice took years glitterworld central. His friend, able to, pursued a childhood salts.

He said that a peaceful life, he began to rise. I offered during the dispute.</desc>
  </CoreDilettante99>
  <Reporter51>
    <title>report</title>
    <titleShort>correspondent</titleShort>
    <desc>Dewayne and i, we spent most of the year as a reporter for details. This is the surgical site, it is also known, reported m.

It was seen by critics as absurd intensive investigation unnecessary, they say, Yaritog articles.</desc>
  </Reporter51>
  <AspiringPopIdol61>
    <title>Daydreaming eggs</title>
    <titleShort>Idol</titleShort>
    <desc>At least, the statue of singing her to sing the next great generation, and received instruction in dance. Asked the nurse care management.

It is to learn about music and mobile homes at the same time, you can not</desc>
  </AspiringPopIdol61>
  <PopIdol50>
    <title>idol</title>
    <titleShort>idol</titleShort>
    <desc>Mingo was a meeting I can not remember. This is to hone the skills of singers and dance became captain.</desc>
  </PopIdol50>
  <FarmBoy56>
    <title>farmer kids</title>
    <titleShort>children Farmers</titleShort>
    <desc>John and contribute to the injured, take care of the animals, working in the home. Work light is hidden in the house, I like to go with the hand.

The game was just at the point where you wish to work in silence.</desc>
  </FarmBoy56>
  <UnstableButcher98>
    <title>meat Zuma</title>
    <titleShort>butcher</titleShort>
    <desc>John whisper hear, began. Something that offended them and their animals. He was a hairy old friend he had killed now, finally, I hate them. She sells meat, people began to tell the time.</desc>
  </UnstableButcher98>
  <LogicalChild2>
    <title>Mr. Geek</title>
    <titleShort>Mr. Geek</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun] this argument as a personal computer, it was ready. Because it is in the team for the Arts.

Because dealing with a difficult, [PAWN_possessive] friends like, that is, except for a bit.</desc>
  </LogicalChild2>
  <Archaeologist85>
    <title>Archeology</title>
    <titleShort>display</titleShort>
    <desc>There is no incentive [PAWN_pronoun] was still alive. One day, as the galaxy [PAWN_pronoun] study of archeology, and we jumped out into space to look around.\n\n[PAWN_pronoun] also learned to survive. In addition, I also learned that people - but real [PAWN_pronoun] you think the death of life.</desc>
  </Archaeologist85>
  <StationWhelp45>
    <title>old</title>
    <titleShort>brat</titleShort>
    <desc>Cathy [PAWN_nameDef] .[PAWN_pronoun] spaceport and education for orphans, which cost a red cent or shabby treatment [PAWN_pronoun] sometimes dirty work, "welcome," as well as to eat in a very good pass was stolen, and thrown out of the spaceport, but a copy of the air.</desc>
  </StationWhelp45>
  <PirateKing6>
    <title>Chuzoku Director</title>
    <titleShort>tshuzoku</titleShort>
    <desc>Fill Ship Pirates Paradise favor [PAWN_nameDef]. any time after the director, was one of the few [PAWN_nameDef] and start killing their own way, even staff.</desc>
  </PirateKing6>
  <ConstructionGrunt79>
    <title>construction workers</title>
    <titleShort>architect</titleShort>
    <desc>Jackson grew up in the laboratories of our fathers, who lives intellectual elite. What they wanted to, we could go without worrying about the cost.

However, where luxury is not ready to share. On the other hand, it is true - the father of control - this house is haunted.</desc>
  </ConstructionGrunt79>
  <MilitaryInventor44>
    <title>the army of the inventor</title>
    <titleShort>inventors</titleShort>
    <desc>Jackson, at the end of the uprising, the army laboratory local rekvisityoned empire.

It is also the ability to produce a weapon in the battle. This is also one of the most intelligent people on the planet.</desc>
  </MilitaryInventor44>
  <StudentEngineer68>
    <title>engineers eggs</title>
    <titleShort>engineers</titleShort>
    <desc>This is murwakala child [PAWN_nameDef] win weapons and Aerospace technology called special training.

One day you put a bracelet on the list, work hard and be a good friend. [PAWN_nameDef], it refers to the hand, I believe that this is unlikely.</desc>
  </StudentEngineer68>
  <EngineeredPilot9>
    <title>qualified counselors</title>
    <titleShort>pilot</titleShort>
    <desc>The update is provided for emergency, after their local neighborhood [PAWN_nameDef] neighbors, but also for voluntary testing in production. innovation program, but not the driver, which is to reduce the interest of the people around you.

His "squirrel" is a code.</desc>
  </EngineeredPilot9>
  <StreetKid98>
    <title>Street Kid</title>
    <titleShort>Street Child</titleShort>
    <desc>He grew up in the wild, a dog will not be limited to [PAWN_nameDef] holiday. To avoid looking for food with a two-man final, lively way.

When he was 13 years of age, crime interplanetary organization, group.</desc>
  </StreetKid98>
  <BanditLeader36>
    <title>head criminals</title>
    <titleShort>outlaw</titleShort>
    <desc>A noshiag [PAWN_nameDef] that "a criminal organization, in the end, the organization's leader outer layer will become one. Another friend buckwheat.</desc>
  </BanditLeader36>
  <PizzaLover37>
    <title>favorite Pizza</title>
    <titleShort>Pizakiddo</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] as bomunezumipiza. [PAWN_pronoun] is indiscriminate as to break the skull and try to see the inside of the animal.</desc>
  </PizzaLover37>
  <Gigolo99>
    <title>Dayuan</title>
    <titleShort>gigolo</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] bomunezumipiza money to buy himself: .[PAWN_pronoun] earned us sales, and zeglar colony, the damaged relationship with somebody, you say.

Fortunately, [PAWN_pronoun] extent that any attempt to close the route out of the ark. Scrap Bomunezumipiza desire and married a former slave [PAWN_nameDef] sent him to the exit.</desc>
  </Gigolo99>
  <FrontierMarshal0>
    <title>Border Sheriff</title>
    <titleShort>Sheriff</titleShort>
    <desc>Nate is a colony that velaiyalpe .[PAWN_pronoun], we try to respect the law, but corrupt mayor [PAWN_objective] family killed more [PAWN_pronoun] silence.

Notes .[PAWN_pronoun] health concern and immediate re-arrested after the planet, it looked at the beginning, but it's a different life.</desc>
  </FrontierMarshal0>
  <ColonialGovernor77>
    <title>koloniala? it</title>
    <titleShort>omnipotent</titleShort>
    <desc>He was not happy with the unspeakable corruption, Prince Henry was scheduled to run. However, a group of local public services immediately expelled him from their control center.

He had to spend the rest of an executor, you have to leave the government.</desc>
  </ColonialGovernor77>
  <MercenaryRecruit29>
    <title>more mercenary</title>
    <titleShort>to revive the military</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] worked at the former army chief of the World Trade Center. When I was young, professional service I [PAWN_pronoun].</desc>
  </MercenaryRecruit29>
  <MercenaryChef58>
    <title>cooking LEGO</title>
    <titleShort>coolie</titleShort>
    <desc>According to his family, [PAWN_nameDef] is also true warrior.

Born of the shooting. But what really pleased with gadgets and developing new recipes.</desc>
  </MercenaryChef58>
  <AbandonedChild47>
    <title>abandoned children</title>
    <titleShort>gallery</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] interested to hear his children's education. [PAWN_pronoun] real time and store rich parents despair of the mouth of the cave registered. With parents instead of cloning technology, [PAWN_possessive] continues [PAWN_objective] research, it is better to take the time to do better clone son.</desc>
  </AbandonedChild47>
  <CargoPilot58>
    <title>pilot cargo</title>
    <titleShort>pilot</titleShort>
    <desc>The meat trade, and the main conflict [PAWN_nameDef], someone .[PAWN_pronoun] perfect light can pass during the operation of the aircraft into the public eye.</desc>
  </CargoPilot58>
  <TradersChild17>
    <title>dealers child</title>
    <titleShort>trader</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] comes to parents working methods and practices, we have learned, in a variety of cultures.</desc>
  </TradersChild17>
  <SpaceHumanitarian9>
    <title>metal</title>
    <titleShort>dark</titleShort>
    <desc>Thus, given that Infest Urbworld [PAWN_nameDef] [PAWN_possessive] total, less than the life of food. When I help people who are happy, we decided to dedicate. This activity, learn how to respond to famine and pestilence.</desc>
  </SpaceHumanitarian9>
  <CorpStudent30>
    <title>Students</title>
    <titleShort>schoolchildren</titleShort>
    <desc>Identity's fourth-largest trading company manager deon god can raise. The company Anyone age 6 years for [PAWN_pronoun], he began to be honest in charge to learn to drive on vantanennan.</desc>
  </CorpStudent30>
  <ExecutiveOfficer30>
    <title>minister</title>
    <titleShort>officer</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] is now director of air between business enterprises. Never leave the contradictions within the company, and one of the families, rape and murder are Nureginu clothing.

Give a wrong, but because of the parents completed acceleration instead of death.</desc>
  </ExecutiveOfficer30>
  <VRAddict62>
    <title>VR poisoning</title>
    <titleShort>VR poisoning</titleShort>
    <desc>The long-term relationship with the spine and prevent the communication of the virtual universe - douglas is an electronic brain. He is day-to-day reality is only possible to be aware of the area. So big that it is not suitable to be in the community.</desc>
  </VRAddict62>
  <RugbyPlayer15>
    <title>rugby player</title>
    <titleShort>Titles</titleShort>
    <desc>After that year was dedicated almost a reality, Douglas said cap and doctors helped.

Make Unfortunately when doctors can save them in connection jack off Rugby game. Flash back to mind, Fusion and the virtual world, your personality and abilities rugby player.</desc>
  </RugbyPlayer15>
  <Nerd36>
    <title>Freaks</title>
    <titleShort>Moron</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] interested in anything. French Style in the woods, trying to do what's best friend.</desc>
  </Nerd36>
  <StateEngineer18>
    <title>location engineer</title>
    <titleShort>engineer</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] national policy for the harmonious development of the device.

Among his subjects tested weapons designed will be very excited about the many random injured, who qualified for the job Mark.</desc>
  </StateEngineer18>
  <RebelSlave1>
    <title>rebellious slave</title>
    <titleShort>rebel</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef], freedom, and rebels and something to eat, we set the goal of independent business owners.</desc>
  </RebelSlave1>
  <CombatNegotiator47>
    <title>war history</title>
    <titleShort>Koshonin</titleShort>
    <desc>After jumping the planet will be [PAWN_nameDef] Aotzo me to refresh your star talent.

The slave, the number of rebels, who works for trade settlement and decided to work in a professional killer. Feat negotiations.</desc>
  </CombatNegotiator47>
  <MedievalPlower14>
    <title>Farm</title>
    <titleShort>Peasants'</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] were king and queen of peasant families live just .[PAWN_pronoun] sovereignty and do not worry about the world, but a large farm king collect the harvest. Thanks to poor families [PAWN_nameDef], there is a lot of money training [PAWN_possessive] apply. Instead [PAWN_pronoun], because he has to work outside the country, and gave them the opportunity to improve creativity.</desc>
  </MedievalPlower14>
  <SpaceStationCook63>
    <title>Chicken Space Station</title>
    <titleShort>tap</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] away from the world, he came to the station with power shortages. For this reason, the stones of the bag, I have some power [PAWN_nameDef] .[PAWN_pronoun] live to eat, let's funny on its own criticism in the light of this estimate does not know anything. Currently, we have a problem in terms of self-esteem as well.</desc>
  </SpaceStationCook63>
  <SonOfAHuntress96>
    <title>The son of the goddess of hunting</title>
    <titleShort>hunting</titleShort>
    <desc>Ticonderoga in the mountainous tribal mother of John the world. He taught survival skills - traps, tracking, fire, cooking, treatment.

His father passed away, as if he has left behind a legacy carbines, John, a belief, he continued to practice.</desc>
  </SonOfAHuntress96>
  <SpaceHunter67>
    <title>corner</title>
    <titleShort>Hunter</titleShort>
    <desc>So, in the name of hunting, even for experienced shooters, pray for John Hills. He ascended to heaven to find new victims, left his home planet.</desc>
  </SpaceHunter67>
  <StudentSocialite73>
    <title>the Student Association</title>
    <titleShort>celebrity Society</titleShort>
    <desc>Gains and Kalidas Kobashi, is knowing the people and the political elite school.

There are obviously discouraged by management. But I think it's boring. He stood in front was completed a few years later.</desc>
  </StudentSocialite73>
  <PoliticalAssassin87>
    <title>killer</title>
    <titleShort>Jack's death</titleShort>
    <desc>Matisse, your job really noticed that there is a time resolution to resolve international problems. Training Action and the outcome of the murder of Tuesday Ceti world.

He put his cajolery, death came to be known. He was fierce on behalf Deathjack.</desc>
  </PoliticalAssassin87>
  <AwkwardNerd12>
    <title>Pumpkin Geek</title>
    <titleShort>steps</titleShort>
    <desc>This device, however, gives Dave spent living holographic and robotics research. He and the other men, and it is a good device.</desc>
  </AwkwardNerd12>
  <AIResearcher30>
    <title>Artificial intelligence researchers</title>
    <titleShort>researcher</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] artificial intelligence, robotics, friendship, known agreement between ai researchers .[PAWN_pronoun] communication from the 3d image, which is a real confidence in his wife [PAWN_pronoun] people contact us to succeed in communicating with [PAWN_pronoun] in;</desc>
  </AIResearcher30>
  <MidworldGeek48>
    <title>Feeling midworld</title>
    <titleShort>Geek</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef], which grows in a quiet area in the city. There is, however, to communicate with the weak die when young, interesting team, has blossomed into a true gift.</desc>
  </MidworldGeek48>
  <ArmyScientist35>
    <title>military experts</title>
    <titleShort>scientist</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] .[PAWN_pronoun] weapons to do battle on the planet stage design were a little effort and research.</desc>
  </ArmyScientist35>
  <CatHerder12>
    <title>Creators of cats</title>
    <titleShort>The owner</titleShort>
    <desc>Helping [PAWN_nameDef] breeder works with his father, he was a cat hundreds of animals pike bait.

When the cat refused dwichidakkeori sent mail industry.</desc>
  </CatHerder12>
  <FelineScientist97>
    <title>Science cat</title>
    <titleShort>science</titleShort>
    <desc>Now [PAWN_nameDef] in fyeldvorker famous cat. I begin to travel in the blood of people who are interested in local search and full color. Would fish breeding specialist</desc>
  </FelineScientist97>
  <Scavenger62>
    <title>scavenger</title>
    <titleShort>scavenger</titleShort>
    <desc>Mining, [PAWN_pronoun] through technology and equipment, represented at the end of the land.</desc>
  </Scavenger62>
  <SpaceMarine51>
    <title>Lu optera Marines</title>
    <titleShort>Consulate sea</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun] legal protection vessel chuzoku consent to your fight.</desc>
  </SpaceMarine51>
  <VatgrownAssassin17>
    <title>Vatgrown good</title>
    <titleShort>Clone</titleShort>
    <desc>Village, not the man, a killer with a cold heart. The product of biotechnology, scientists, and built, and on behalf of the killer. Matt, clinging to life, education is not the feelings.</desc>
  </VatgrownAssassin17>
  <Mercenary40>
    <title>Agir</title>
    <titleShort>one</titleShort>
    <desc>When flee their home planet. [PAWN_nameDef] [PAWN_pronoun] and earth, and members of the gang met for many years, and I love my sister and brother still struggles to walk with.

One day, they sometimes lose. [PAWN_nameDef] [PAWN_pronoun] beautiful mountain communities and damaged the enemy, because he has refused to tsomule was trembling fear.</desc>
  </Mercenary40>
  <HiveWorldChild2>
    <title>Children hiveworld</title>
    <titleShort>Hiver</titleShort>
    <desc>I yeondanga can simulate different length, and weapons from cities and [PAWN_pronoun] [PAWN_pronoun] war games.</desc>
  </HiveWorldChild2>
  <Microbiologist35>
    <title>bacteria biology</title>
    <titleShort>biology</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] lived until the 'last time the world is due to earth.</desc>
  </Microbiologist35>
  <StarforceCadet91>
    <title>students</title>
    <titleShort>cadet</titleShort>
    <desc>Glitterworld capital (so-t) empire sent the easy childhood zoryana sam wyss.

A country is considered to be volatile forces to Young, Sam ,, we decided to do it.</desc>
  </StarforceCadet91>
  <AceFighterPilot38>
    <title>I would</title>
    <titleShort>ace</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] exactly as graduate of the university of the ace pilot is tough profession, he made a three-pronged campaign.\n\nThen there's the time and in a very difficult fight in the end, the boats sail non [PAWN_possessive] and his mother has been destroyed. If there is nowhere to go, [PAWN_pronoun] ship escape pod and prayer.</desc>
  </AceFighterPilot38>
  <Stableboy88>
    <title>the bridegroom</title>
    <titleShort>groom</titleShort>
    <desc>The [PAWN_pronoun] [PAWN_nameDef] [PAWN_objective] of great business, you save enough over the world can take.</desc>
  </Stableboy88>
  <Brigand68>
    <title>sascha</title>
    <titleShort>The rioters</titleShort>
    <desc>The rebels [PAWN_nameDef] call a friend, he ran the air. They want to seize the ship, Nguyen Hoa dung Rouge in 2000.</desc>
  </Brigand68>
  <ArtfulDodger87>
    <title>art of cheating</title>
    <titleShort>Crook</titleShort>
    <desc>Urbworld marcus rose carry themselves. He lives as a non promoter loan was sold, ie.

This knife is immediate and Wuqizhuanjia and remember these words as they are.</desc>
  </ArtfulDodger87>
  <Assassin16>
    <title>murderer</title>
    <titleShort>Killer</titleShort>
    <desc>Robin "has special training to perform the murder of high risk. Shoot him into something that does not follow the method More ..

Our goal is to understand the planned murder, because it provides reliable future project funding .Robin his boss, who betrayed him, we promise not to trust anyone.</desc>
  </Assassin16>
  <Pickpocket65>
    <title>Sri</title>
    <titleShort>thief</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun] kill if they want to help young parents [PAWN_nameDef] stage I no longer be protected. Of all the things in life that people who are married. [PAWN_pronoun] necessary.</desc>
  </Pickpocket65>
  <BusinessGangster35>
    <title>front organization</title>
    <titleShort>Yakuza</titleShort>
    <desc>avoiding the eyes of the law, [PAWN_nameDef] defy the laws of silence will not work now. Run illegal brothel, pub, such accidents can not we as a restaurant manager, competitors, but the fall is [PAWN_nameDef] luck.</desc>
  </BusinessGangster35>
  <DisasterSurvivor58>
    <title>Natural Disaster Survivors</title>
    <titleShort>survivor</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] small asteroid hit the moon. It is the star wants to destroy her family for .[PAWN_pronoun] Desert, only death and lived life.</desc>
  </DisasterSurvivor58>
  <ParamilitaryAgent11>
    <title>Militant</title>
    <titleShort>agent</titleShort>
    <desc>After working several jobs, but the planet [PAWN_possessive] [PAWN_nameDef] ulvatikattal and strategic intelligence to combat product life more .[PAWN_pronoun] join armed.</desc>
  </ParamilitaryAgent11>
  <HistoryStudent78>
    <title>Students of history</title>
    <titleShort>student</titleShort>
    <desc>Now [PAWN_possessive], (fiction) the original culture lizard - when I should have had a child [PAWN_nameDef] art style, started with music, K[PAWN_pronoun], more [PAWN_pronoun] (fiction) writing learning book [PAWN_possessive] planet.</desc>
  </HistoryStudent78>
  <Storyteller52>
    <title>discussion</title>
    <titleShort>figuratively</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] [PAWN_possessive] world, is quite legendary and learn.

[PAWN_nameDef]'s people be, as it can help the skin to the old legend, people are nice to attract.</desc>
  </Storyteller52>
  <NobleWard81>
    <title>Necessary and sufficient</title>
    <titleShort>baby</titleShort>
    <desc>After their view of the world, old and new, [PAWN_pronoun] says, culture, technology - already among the classes, I learned such things as reduced wine secrets.</desc>
  </NobleWard81>
  <InformationBroker77>
    <title>Store information</title>
    <titleShort>proofreader</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun] so, remember that to gain wealth from knowledge, there has been a broker for buying and selling information.</desc>
  </InformationBroker77>
  <FeralChild63>
    <title>child communication</title>
    <titleShort>survivor</titleShort>
    <desc>I [PAWN_nameDef], so painful [PAWN_possessive] family, of course, far from rimvorld colleagues.

One day, a group of Mekanoido Osoikakari we killed all of Robert's wife. The Raiders team found that only want to live in the wilderness.</desc>
  </FeralChild63>
  <VersatileWorker37>
    <title>all</title>
    <titleShort>worker</titleShort>
    <desc>Both work and the person spent years working for the colonial settlements.

Or, the damage is not as great as it is hot, and learn new fine range of skills, this may be a noble adults.</desc>
  </VersatileWorker37>
  <SpoiledChild33>
    <title>Molly</title>
    <titleShort>Contact Metabotch calls</titleShort>
    <desc>Pets [PAWN_pronoun], love my parents [PAWN_possessive], violent animals - animals kedomo "[PAWN_pronoun] still has a lot of other people play.</desc>
  </SpoiledChild33>
  <TestSubject53>
    <title>physical test</title>
    <titleShort>Experience</titleShort>
    <desc>They stole from Gene Therap [PAWN_nameDef] young people for a period of six years, when demand for the experimental group. [PAWN_objective] Institute scientists and risk.</desc>
  </TestSubject53>
  <AmateurEngineer34>
    <title>amateur engineer</title>
    <titleShort>engineer</titleShort>
    <desc>Army wish you to join his father [PAWN_nameDef] .[PAWN_pronoun] family, he is a good face, [PAWN_possessive] ever found in large aircraft like the lifestyle in the wrong place, the place where the secret of his interest in engineering technology [PAWN_pronoun] not disappointed in the history of military technology has to offer.</desc>
  </AmateurEngineer34>
  <AerospaceEngineer44>
    <title>Aerospace engineer</title>
    <titleShort>engineer</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] in the plane is known .[PAWN_pronoun] known technician responsible for production targets in the spacecraft to the production line, technical issues, and research and to improve the search.</desc>
  </AerospaceEngineer44>
  <StreetUrchin62>
    <title>Number of cities</title>
    <titleShort>Swindler</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun] is growing rapidly as a trio and how nuku [PAWN_pronoun]. reminds me of the time.</desc>
  </StreetUrchin62>
  <HiredMuscle8>
    <title>Laha'ole</title>
    <titleShort>Nelly</titleShort>
    <desc>they know how to live on the street, police [PAWN_nameDef] I really slippery. However, especially in case of a problem, which will remove utshinomeshi attacker to death.

Crime, its responsibility, is driven out of business by using information and knowledge can be hired thugs.</desc>
  </HiredMuscle8>
  <WildChild2>
    <title>Boy</title>
    <titleShort>Wild Child</titleShort>
    <desc>Not only fight, but also to be served [PAWN_pronoun] eat raw or undercooked.</desc>
  </WildChild2>
  <AlcoholicTrucker58>
    <title>when drivers</title>
    <titleShort>alcohol</titleShort>
    <desc>Co [PAWN_nameDef] evening around driving industrial drone matera, she lost her husband and daughter in an accident.\n\nWe are a company [PAWN_pronoun] nanotechnology research bodies' found. Power, will continue to run so that they will suffer [PAWN_pronoun] .[PAWN_pronoun] everything possible to prevent scratching quietly.</desc>
  </AlcoholicTrucker58>
  <HackerProdigy70>
    <title>genius hacker</title>
    <titleShort>hacker</titleShort>
    <desc>The wedge, the son of a wealthy surgeon. Get medical students, and he went down. Inherited something of themselves, to learn how to use a computer, do the community underground. He became one of the most dangerous hackers home planet.</desc>
  </HackerProdigy70>
  <IntelligenceAgent4>
    <title>The intelligence officer</title>
    <titleShort>agent</titleShort>
    <desc>Technical and hacking, government, parents out of the star, in a secret army in the world. The Board of Directors is aware of the fact that his fighting technique, it's psychological development.

government regulations, and can be seen as a reduction of their actions, it is now French-speaking villain. His current location is unknown.</desc>
  </IntelligenceAgent4>
  <MadScientist70>
    <title>Mad Science Test</title>
    <titleShort>shoo</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun] soon learn to fear the people, and the nickname "mad scientist".</desc>
  </MadScientist70>
  <WarChief2>
    <title>The main fight</title>
    <titleShort>head</titleShort>
    <desc>The leader of the gang life in neolithic [PAWN_nameDef]. So, no more war to fight fire for fun.</desc>
  </WarChief2>
  <YouthDelinquent65>
    <title>Juvenile delinquents</title>
    <titleShort>Juvenile</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was the only son of the famous sommelier. her parents, too, but you get a job immediately put the baby in prison hope to agree an adult, this method is no longer true.

During his detention, [PAWN_nameDef] mastered the skills that the country is interested in the science of birds will do.</desc>
  </YouthDelinquent65>
  <InvoluntaryHermit32>
    <title>monk forced</title>
    <titleShort>monk</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] escape pod .[PAWN_pronoun] poured on the ground unexplored life undiscovered, and driving maffaro, I was able to survive.

After that, the number [PAWN_pronoun] found covered with wool Pygmies affect the club for a long Maffaro Group, spoke about the importance of cleanliness and fields.</desc>
  </InvoluntaryHermit32>
  <HillbillyProdigy85>
    <title>talented area</title>
    <titleShort>village</titleShort>
    <desc>Most children dressed in the 'wings are different people, there are always the sound of battle and gunfire exchanges Benjamin, was born in the mountain cold planet. his childhood, or playing the banjo, he worked as a mechanic, intelligence, his extraordinary and more, is recommended; its medical school at the age of 20 years.</desc>
  </HillbillyProdigy85>
  <MedicalScientist25>
    <title>Medical scientists</title>
    <titleShort>Explorer</titleShort>
    <desc>Benjamin host as research vessels transiting doctor. He is a bird species, genes with Alzheimer's disease will be faced with a heterogeneous star student. No qaadheen bird friend and the best bird, captain, was also sent to all forced bird lied command ship.</desc>
  </MedicalScientist25>
  <UrbworldUrchin90>
    <title>Brother urbworld</title>
    <titleShort>brat</titleShort>
    <desc>Throw dirty room, old [PAWN_nameDef], .[PAWN_pronoun] [PAWN_possessive] unaware, uneducated, that a change in diet, I asked him right.</desc>
  </UrbworldUrchin90>
  <VoidRaider45>
    <title>vacuum Rider</title>
    <titleShort>robber</titleShort>
    <desc>Adventure and glory, will not, then [PAWN_nameDef], to attack the soldiers to hand to connect the relative increase in the area, a gun and a sword, and swear allegiance to the distribution of stars his success.</desc>
  </VoidRaider45>
  <MidworldSketcher11>
    <title>Artist midworld</title>
    <titleShort>painter</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] bad accident, but of love.

[PAWN_pronoun] inherited from the father, the mother .[PAWN_pronoun] the beauty of art, education, hard work and determination to see. The history of growth and military intervention Sukusukuto, [PAWN_nameDef] technology.</desc>
  </MidworldSketcher11>
  <MidworldSailor84>
    <title>Midvorld sailors</title>
    <titleShort>sailor</titleShort>
    <desc>Join [PAWN_nameDef] sea. Years later, an NCO, he was angry with the ability to use the boat.

After all, it is now a well-trained driver [PAWN_nameDef] wild pirate groups. From now on, the full-time cooking staff.</desc>
  </MidworldSailor84>
  <CoreWorldStudent4>
    <title>Students coreworld</title>
    <titleShort>student</titleShort>
    <desc>Featured birth to a baby boy, alyssa other boys are not familiar with. I was young and want creative work as an artist jewelry. He felt uncomfortable in my body.

You support me, because fortunately, family and friends, and then, and now another woman reassignment operations are processed.</desc>
  </CoreWorldStudent4>
  <CoreWorldJeweler59>
    <title>The world's leading jewelers</title>
    <titleShort>jewelry</titleShort>
    <desc>Inspiration for a woman to work, time and energy, I uchikomeru stakeholders (jewelry) lot. Galaxy is an excellent way to his job as sales of jewelry in the house, then there is a planet.</desc>
  </CoreWorldJeweler59>
  <MedievalSquire61>
    <title>Foreign Medieval Knights</title>
    <titleShort>Night schoolgirls</titleShort>
    <desc>Williams grew up as a knight out. Very, very, people know very few adviser to the king and to provide training done tactics on how to protect emergency sword to fight.</desc>
  </MedievalSquire61>
  <MedievalKnight71>
    <title>Knights of the middle</title>
    <titleShort>Knight</titleShort>
    <desc>William, like a soldier in battle, in addition to polishing the king and the people fighting for their products. The highest honor of the leader of the army an enemy race Honjin for the King of enemy prisoners of war.</desc>
  </MedievalKnight71>
  <StarSquire9>
    <title>You date can be adjusted Star</title>
    <titleShort>here</titleShort>
    <desc>Birth medyevalvorld, [PAWN_nameDef] see the first night of stars memory that was.

It is full of [PAWN_pronoun] .[PAWN_pronoun] sleep in the middle of your vision a [PAWN_objective] squiring fans left the sky, the stars.</desc>
  </StarSquire9>
  <StarKnight54>
    <title>Star night</title>
    <titleShort>Knight</titleShort>
    <desc>Long was kidnapped from his home in the Middle Ages, [PAWN_nameDef] complex a magic sword, escaped were abducted.

Shortly thereafter, while drifting escape pod, his childhood dreams of becoming a star knight and feel the real atmosphere. Soon, he was pushed to the ground.</desc>
  </StarKnight54>
  <DrugMule94>
    <title>drag Messenger</title>
    <titleShort>Mule</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun] drug "substance" f bear, merchants, ambassadors towing shot [PAWN_pronoun] team used two fires directly on the ground or in writing of the neighborhood gang bullets.</desc>
  </DrugMule94>
  <TestSubject85>
    <title>authorities Overview</title>
    <titleShort>body of experimental</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] is "of course, lose weight!" part of the research. Unfortunately, it is [PAWN_pronoun] doubt side effects are completely different, [PAWN_pronoun] mother. Stars are crazy to get rid of many people killed.</desc>
  </TestSubject85>
  <CommonerHeir25>
    <title>"Giving the router</title>
    <titleShort>Location</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun] called the imperial palace nutritional strategies to capture the heir to where it is possible to [PAWN_objective] to pay the other heirs.</desc>
  </CommonerHeir25>
  <CommonerLord87>
    <title>and the emperor, and often</title>
    <titleShort>power</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] from other royal [PAWN_objective] falsely accused of a crime, do not agree with his command, the emperor [PAWN_objective] forced migration.</desc>
  </CommonerLord87>
  <ArtisanFarmer23>
    <title>efficient farmers</title>
    <titleShort>Farmers</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] [PAWN_possessive] growing field in the glitterworld beauty. Old farm Glitter World technology, it is the desire of the planet is one of the few remaining farmers.</desc>
  </ArtisanFarmer23>
  <GeneticEngineer31>
    <title>genetically engineered</title>
    <titleShort>geneticists</titleShort>
    <desc>It [PAWN_nameDef], cows, .[PAWN_pronoun] [PAWN_possessive] first genetic experiments immediately its current capacity to handle different genes.

laboratory rodents as severe cold, I decided to [PAWN_objective], except that fear of death.</desc>
  </GeneticEngineer31>
  <Pampered87>
    <title>care too</title>
    <titleShort>excessive worry</titleShort>
    <desc>Gliterworld culture, [PAWN_nameDef] growing baby toys.

This lack very basic, [PAWN_pronoun] life experience, the chef, especially anger, directly brought to every working kitchen staff are not allowed to undermine the leadership down.</desc>
  </Pampered87>
  <NinjaAssassin31>
    <title>Ninja</title>
    <titleShort>Ninja</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] huge interplanetary these things by the sword, which [PAWN_pronoun], of course, put a small amount using their communities by making hateful, vile slanders: they contribute to the mission and are accompanied by violence charge made.\n\nKilling hatred failure of a major accident on [PAWN_objective] Bonsai plants.</desc>
  </NinjaAssassin31>
  <MilitaryChild82>
    <title>will be children of civil servants</title>
    <titleShort>Civil Military Staff</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_possessive] year family tradition of deference [PAWN_pronoun], it conducted a survey in real time.</desc>
  </MilitaryChild82>
  <LazyProgrammer3>
    <title>Using software</title>
    <titleShort>programmer</titleShort>
    <desc>Intellectual property theft is suspected to be an increased tendency, the number of unresolved cases [PAWN_pronoun].</desc>
  </LazyProgrammer3>
  <GangMember68>
    <title>Team members</title>
    <titleShort>gray half</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] continues to grow, not knowing the parents is always the life of the street of the .[PAWN_pronoun] to fight to survive.

To live that you not only painful, it is not entirely so.</desc>
  </GangMember68>
  <MindwipedAssassin87>
    <title>nonego killer</title>
    <titleShort>No self</titleShort>
    <desc>Business, Computer [PAWN_nameDef] theft. [PAWN_pronoun] they get possession [PAWN_objective] attacks, [PAWN_nameDef] [PAWN_possessive] ground, a man walks away, killing several people.</desc>
  </MindwipedAssassin87>
  <TestSubject90>
    <title>Experimental</title>
    <titleShort>Physically Laboratory</titleShort>
    <desc>56048 number of tests, experiments Chassis number 11,529,914 from the ceiling of the room, white wall psychological, physical evidence had already spent.

Only friend, "mother" is called sound. If the attempt failed and bitterness has praised the success of punishment.</desc>
  </TestSubject90>
  <TestSubject6>
    <title>Experiments body</title>
    <titleShort>body experience</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] test at the time of quantum geometry, I hope that there can be no harm.

"One day, his mother, and hear his voice, for example, if at the end of this test, I will be with you, and he said:" the other side of the door</desc>
  </TestSubject6>
  <FireScarredChild32>
    <title>burnt child</title>
    <titleShort>Firm</titleShort>
    <desc>After a devastating fire burned in his eyes duster for the mast at luxembourg city children living there. However, the death of a fire to burn more fat than ever before are gone.</desc>
  </FireScarredChild32>
  <SpaceshipSalesman6>
    <title>pabatsong stars</title>
    <titleShort>Saleswoman</titleShort>
    <desc>Filter, such as a research project in the mutant rabbit cage, construction and space wheat, I have tried different types of work. Finally, the so-called stars are found [PAWN_pronoun] sales skills. Entertainment space in the language, the quality and efficiency of an interesting discussion, which specializes in the sale of [PAWN_possessive].</desc>
  </SpaceshipSalesman6>
  <TechEnthusiast65>
    <title>youth Geek</title>
    <titleShort>guru</titleShort>
    <desc>Michael, when I was ready for a kid, instead of playing with other children, with .[PAWN_pronoun] time state-of-the-art all ashamed .[PAWN_pronoun] ai often people with electronic devices and games that do not know .</desc>
  </TechEnthusiast65>
  <AIProgrammer5>
    <title>BB publisher</title>
    <titleShort>Programmer</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] entered into the department and mechanical robot soldiers, entered into the growth of the high-action game ai.\n\n[PAWN_pronoun] [PAWN_pronoun] talk to anyone else during the war, and spent time in the proceedings it had to meet and development.</desc>
  </AIProgrammer5>
  <DiplomatsChild97>
    <title>children diplomat</title>
    <titleShort>diplomat</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] diplomats took place in the family.

For more action [PAWN_pronoun] facilities around the world, according to a study to understand.</desc>
  </DiplomatsChild97>
  <WhiteHatHacker82>
    <title>Pirates white</title>
    <titleShort>Hacker</titleShort>
    <desc>Computer [PAWN_possessive], bad world [PAWN_nameDef] they need to get help online.</desc>
  </WhiteHatHacker82>
  <Winerunner49>
    <title>stealing wine</title>
    <titleShort>wine Delivery</titleShort>
    <desc>their parents, [PAWN_nameDef] planet Aracena and monasteries were built in sixth place in the monastery abandoned by the Geronemus.

nuns, who had taught him discipline and hard work. Instead, it [PAWN_pronoun], night after night of wine monastic flavor, can the city will collect Decorating Ideas.</desc>
  </Winerunner49>
  <VinhoKing66>
    <title>Wang wine</title>
    <titleShort>cats</titleShort>
    <desc>Aracena vi then put measures on the planet, the market was dominated by two continents mostly underground wine sales business [PAWN_nameDef]. There is the king of wine.

For example, [PAWN_pronoun], provided most of the competition, even in a clever political move, [PAWN_pronoun], such as murder, sometimes more involved.</desc>
  </VinhoKing66>
  <StreetChild0>
    <title>A street urchin</title>
    <titleShort>street children</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] mother died of a drug that has deposited his childhood in an orphanage. If you need to request the stolen church, right, stealing [PAWN_nameDef] see when a priest, were arrested child again, so I decided to give him a chance.</desc>
  </StreetChild0>
  <SlaveChemist84>
    <title>of Pharmacy</title>
    <titleShort>Pharmacy</titleShort>
    <desc>With an innate talent in the pharmaceutical industry is now selling [PAWN_nameDef], .[PAWN_pronoun] that shogun still has the original slave traders, he is forced to try drugs and other slaves. is no doubt about the serious attitude of research for creating</desc>
  </SlaveChemist84>
  <SlaveFarmer35>
    <title>plebeian slave</title>
    <titleShort>Agricultural</titleShort>
    <desc>Most girls were [PAWN_nameDef] farmers. Farmers do not have children, he left his slaves. Day-to-day violence, the girl can not deal with violence, the first time for a long time. A few years later, he ran away.</desc>
  </SlaveFarmer35>
  <RocketEngineer31>
    <title>Rocket Engineer</title>
    <titleShort>Engineer</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] school to win a prestigious scholarship and earned degrees in rocket technology. After working for many years in my universe, she started traveling to see the world.</desc>
  </RocketEngineer31>
  <MedievalSlave34>
    <title>Middle Ages and in captivity</title>
    <titleShort>slave</titleShort>
    <desc>What Soren slavery because they do not know. Finally, he went to see the cargo ships. This is the original owner, was forced to flee the army to take over.</desc>
  </MedievalSlave34>
  <SpaceMarine27>
    <title>Coleoptera Marine Corps</title>
    <titleShort>ocean</titleShort>
    <desc>Soren known for its ability to kill prince ,, we soldiers beetle shell. Name and no pesticide residues were called "foreigners".</desc>
  </SpaceMarine27>
  <FoundryApprentice76>
    <title>Engineering Internship Cast</title>
    <titleShort>casting technology</titleShort>
    <desc>The company has grown into the world of engineering students [PAWN_nameDef]. This experience, [PAWN_pronoun] metal, but she was a difficult person to deal with, and encourage shown no enthusiasm for artistic talent.</desc>
  </FoundryApprentice76>
  <CombatEngineer4>
    <title>Engineer</title>
    <titleShort>engineer</titleShort>
    <desc>To build a foundation [PAWN_nameDef], .[PAWN_pronoun] gun, glue the engineer battalion, automotive repair, and the gun - [PAWN_pronoun]</desc>
  </CombatEngineer4>
  <PrivilegedProdigy55>
    <title>Genius status</title>
    <titleShort>Lamborghini</titleShort>
    <desc>Glitter [PAWN_nameDef] world know that the equipment (spiritual) is native talent. Fortunately, [PAWN_possessive] parents, step .[PAWN_possessive] Engineering Education Education, Science, lead, will be included in the technical content.</desc>
  </PrivilegedProdigy55>
  <PlanetaryDiplomat7>
    <title>planet</title>
    <titleShort>messenger</titleShort>
    <desc>Enthusiastically [PAWN_nameDef] .[PAWN_pronoun] concern every business, we ended political discussion, therefore, conflict between the inner planet to the common good are hard to work to find agreement.</desc>
  </PlanetaryDiplomat7>
  <PrivilegedChild86>
    <title>Part of the success of your child</title>
    <titleShort>class Valentine</titleShort>
    <desc>However, no definition of emergency workers brought to life as a decadent [PAWN_nameDef].</desc>
  </PrivilegedChild86>
  <Guardian55>
    <title>bodyguard</title>
    <titleShort>Home Security</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun] became a professional security.</desc>
  </Guardian55>
  <ChildProdigy22>
    <title>the signal</title>
    <titleShort>genius</titleShort>
    <desc>When I graduated from college in '12, Jared life and death of the widow. However, she cross-functional research organizations and gene mechanical restoration efforts. He was arrested and, after a prisoner-up.</desc>
  </ChildProdigy22>
  <RenegadeEngineer33>
    <title>Lay Engineer</title>
    <titleShort>engineer</titleShort>
    <desc>Prisoners planet after prison escape bold, Jared purposes and home planet.

It is from here, the journey to collect the ships traveling ship.</desc>
  </RenegadeEngineer33>
  <BoneCollector14>
    <title>fossil collector</title>
    <titleShort>i</titleShort>
    <desc>Treasure hunter born. We have an ancient history [PAWN_nameDef] passion.

In addition, a strong body, but not necessarily a good neighbor, generating [PAWN_pronoun] digging almost the same base, but the history books like to go deep.</desc>
  </BoneCollector14>
  <Osteologist48>
    <title>bone Topics</title>
    <titleShort>to learn</titleShort>
    <desc>University immediately after the end of class, [PAWN_nameDef] now known as a physical education teacher.

Then build a new foundation for the reputation and health suddenly anaerobic tedious task - these rights, people in my graduating better.</desc>
  </Osteologist48>
  <GNomeSculptor7>
    <title>Font</title>
    <titleShort>Etcher</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef], as part of the g-name developed in the laboratory. Desperate, add all parts of the encyclopedia knowledge of the universe and life.

And g-names to him, the name "gizmo", he explained. The name should be the name you like and accessories.</desc>
  </GNomeSculptor7>
  <Gnomebiologist56>
    <title>Phnom created</title>
    <titleShort>biology</titleShort>
    <desc>Now the life of the faculty of engineering, professor gizmo glitterworld space. He or attend meetings, museum administration.

But he opposed the jobs in the piece, I think, and now does not stop the finished pieces.</desc>
  </Gnomebiologist56>
  <CircusPerformer93>
    <title>Circus</title>
    <titleShort>bouquet</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] growing group of circus, I learned many interesting responsibility. Fun to slip the ball pockets.

Stick, and fitted with a serious injury due to fire fears now on fire.</desc>
  </CircusPerformer93>
  <CriminalKingpin27>
    <title>Much of the crime</title>
    <titleShort>an actor</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] observed a gift for you - goodbye to people ayatsureru. A woman with a criminal underground group [PAWN_pronoun] imports Frontier land begins.

Who came for him, he had himself to blame it is not good in the hands.</desc>
  </CriminalKingpin27>
  <VatgrownSlavegirl4>
    <title>Vatgrown prophet</title>
    <titleShort>daughter</titleShort>
    <desc>Emmye human artificial cultivation (growth iva), the slave urbvorld institute exception. This time the little girl, that is, cooking and cleaning, only the expression of the main program. In its infancy, but it was made.</desc>
  </VatgrownSlavegirl4>
  <UrbworldSexSlave3>
    <title>Sexual urbworld</title>
    <titleShort>sex slaves</titleShort>
    <desc>Who sold sekusureibu traffickers amy. The lack of contact with people, because you have to listen completely built my husband, he does not yet know, freedom is vatariaruka among dozens master.</desc>
  </UrbworldSexSlave3>
  <GunKid55>
    <title>gun Mania</title>
    <titleShort>gun software</titleShort>
    <desc>It is difficult, which is urbworld [PAWN_nameDef]. Every day, hard and dirty, hungry, with adult gangs.

In a small world, in life, that is his passion - and learned weapons of war, military history.</desc>
  </GunKid55>
  <UrbworldSergeant71>
    <title>Sgt urbworld</title>
    <titleShort>sergeant</titleShort>
    <desc>All power [PAWN_nameDef] passion was not ready for the elderly.

After the local police, he said, was for the development of the morning.</desc>
  </UrbworldSergeant71>
  <FeudalLordling59>
    <title>Mali feudal rulers world</title>
    <titleShort>small decision</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] the country, part of a large empire, I grew to become feudal world. Very close to grabbing the use of fob [PAWN_pronoun].</desc>
  </FeudalLordling59>
  <SystemLord80>
    <title>Dominant power</title>
    <titleShort>leader</titleShort>
    <desc>How much influence empire dominated government and written [PAWN_nameDef] star .[PAWN_pronoun] discontent, hoping to expand the scope greater - if outside the law.</desc>
  </SystemLord80>
  <FeudalFarmBoy35>
    <title>Children of the world farmers leaders</title>
    <titleShort>slave</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun] genes midworld constantly change and experience culture.</desc>
  </FeudalFarmBoy35>
  <HunterOfTheKing18>
    <title>Hunter king</title>
    <titleShort>keep</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] after animals driven by a genetic twist villages were forced to reign trained.

Despite these efforts, there .[PAWN_nameDef] his kingdom is destroyed, exacerbated by hatred and fear of animals, technology, development .[PAWN_pronoun] stress disorder is found directly under the post traumatic name.</desc>
  </HunterOfTheKing18>
  <SpaceFanboy44>
    <title>Place craze Guy</title>
    <titleShort>for sun</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] .[PAWN_pronoun] who dreamed of space travel is as old vessels alternately show had to go to see the things you know.</desc>
  </SpaceFanboy44>
  <Castaway87>
    <title>builders</title>
    <titleShort>abandoned</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] passengers aboard an interplanetary trajectory drone [PAWN_possessive] and castaways life on the planet will be destroyed after a few years.</desc>
  </Castaway87>
  <GlitterworldNerd40>
    <title>Geek in glitterworld</title>
    <titleShort>To find</titleShort>
    <desc>It is not too much to understand right [PAWN_pronoun] sciences and arts is [PAWN_pronoun] technology.</desc>
  </GlitterworldNerd40>
  <EnergyResearcher67>
    <title>~~ POS = TRUNC review</title>
    <titleShort>researchers</titleShort>
    <desc>The constitution .[PAWN_pronoun] place I learned to escape the planet for high-speed communication errors [PAWN_nameDef] .[PAWN_pronoun] no creative officer, they are used to prevent the destruction of the city.</desc>
  </EnergyResearcher67>
  <WarChild73>
    <title>Battlefield children</title>
    <titleShort>Boy Battle</titleShort>
    <desc>Mother and father mushinto, the preparation of the civil war in their country. I was surrounded by war and death, he was only vaguely aware of the breached to be valid. The face of the printing.</desc>
  </WarChild73>
  <BountyHunter22>
    <title>good hunter</title>
    <titleShort>Fazal Hunter</titleShort>
    <desc>Souvenir hunters [PAWN_nameDef] .[PAWN_pronoun] good glitterworld millionaire clients, work, and work is still true, and some of the popular verdict.</desc>
  </BountyHunter22>
  <UpperUrbworlder31>
    <title>Tony urbworld</title>
    <titleShort>and the amount Arber</titleShort>
    <desc>Children defender, was a first-class [PAWN_nameDef] urbworld. For people who live near and far higher layers of flat, [PAWN_pronoun] [PAWN_possessive] that most of the time and format, [PAWN_pronoun] representation of the urban landscape can be seen through the window.</desc>
  </UpperUrbworlder31>
  <Missionary99>
    <title>missionary</title>
    <titleShort>missionaries</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] .[PAWN_pronoun], religious works, preaching peace and the distribution of food to the homeless, while driving with [PAWN_possessive] the world in blood, decided to spend a few years.</desc>
  </Missionary99>
  <IdealisticCadet31>
    <title>It is impossible to cadets</title>
    <titleShort>cadet</titleShort>
    <desc>Military personnel, former commander of heroes and good poetry, expired ERED Hamm responsibility [PAWN_nameDef] family, I am still young.

It was a wonderful performance from the current College, completed her studies.</desc>
  </IdealisticCadet31>
  <MercenaryPilot93>
    <title>greed pilot</title>
    <titleShort>shame</titleShort>
    <desc>To drive his team on the board in the top of the world [PAWN_nameDef] believed. It seemed that they consider to protect them.

Army to fight, but the fight against terrorism, his ideals, and finally they disappear and you ICAI conversion stage in their place not only because of his brother officers.</desc>
  </MercenaryPilot93>
  <ChildOfGlass61>
    <title>Glass child</title>
    <titleShort>exploitation</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] planet marble in the basement - the harmful effects of the radiation involved in the case, in asphalt wasteland.

To avoid the death of the planet, which is spying on you [PAWN_pronoun] removal gun shot in a basement, if you want to stick on, but it must be placed in the way by.</desc>
  </ChildOfGlass61>
  <LoneTraveler95>
    <title>single travelers</title>
    <titleShort>tourist</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun] rebels to participate because they use their skills working world [PAWN_possessive] .[PAWN_pronoun] home and saw a young, warning of nuclear fear.</desc>
  </LoneTraveler95>
  <AmateurBotanist14>
    <title>Botanical Asian</title>
    <titleShort>remarkable</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] Mawar mud cows spend much time in the summer, I noticed his skills in the garden. This is not to learn how food, [PAWN_pronoun] to successfully grow plants.</desc>
  </AmateurBotanist14>
  <Undertaker26>
    <title>mortuary</title>
    <titleShort>vespillo</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] who lost their relatives, providing assistance and sad, he wandered the galaxy. Although it is similar to face-to-face with death less Calms the situation down, it would be the most talent.</desc>
  </Undertaker26>
  <ChildSlave6>
    <title>children</title>
    <titleShort>slaves</titleShort>
    <desc>Graham was born in the poor RimWorld home. When a child by his father out time and time again, we have no need to deliver sales to sell to retailers. The share some of the children, mining or processing machine, we worked together to buy that.</desc>
  </ChildSlave6>
  <Mercenary75>
    <title>Cooley</title>
    <titleShort>mercenary</titleShort>
    <desc>RimWorld people prisoner, the suffering and respect for human life in survivors graham. The negotiation of the contract procedures and the existence of weapons of skills development strategies, and that .Graham traveled the world today with the dirty work, so that the bottom should be recognized mercenaries.</desc>
  </Mercenary75>
  <AdventuringChild56>
    <title>son</title>
    <titleShort>ethics</titleShort>
    <desc>This year's technological advances [PAWN_nameDef] provide .[PAWN_pronoun] plans for a new life full of adventure and cargo stowaways start.\n\nOne night, when parents sleep, [PAWN_pronoun] kind of cargo ship slipped into finding me.</desc>
  </AdventuringChild56>
  <HiredAssassin2>
    <title>killers</title>
    <titleShort>cutthroat</titleShort>
    <desc>The excel crime, now working as a thief. Including, it shows the other hand, business was "Remove" threat impossible.</desc>
  </HiredAssassin2>
  <VideoGamer91>
    <title>TV Player</title>
    <titleShort>painter</titleShort>
    <desc>Almost [PAWN_nameDef] hiding in my room a lot, I have a deep love midvorld .[PAWN_pronoun] live sports tv.

twice delayed by extending the time his heart [PAWN_pronoun] increase [PAWN_pronoun]. At the same time, [PAWN_pronoun] miss the gym, he felt the need to find.</desc>
  </VideoGamer91>
  <SpaceshipChef34>
    <title>a place for cooking</title>
    <titleShort>cooks</titleShort>
    <desc>Ryan has established for qualified personnel and the ship will deliver cook. He is for you, physician assistant cook and enjoy.</desc>
  </SpaceshipChef34>
  <DreadedBaby46>
    <title>Animals</title>
    <titleShort>Baby</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] spacecraft got the child to the ground. Logbook, operation of nuclear reactors, the power of the spaceship in the sky, Hamburg, and create a compelling set of golden cat.</desc>
  </DreadedBaby46>
  <DreadedDude94>
    <title>Satan</title>
    <titleShort>Urchin</titleShort>
    <desc>Say, guardians and centuries [PAWN_nameDef], [PAWN_possessive] disproportionate staff, and pointed out that a hundred years ago, to do more of the planet, "the source of growth" and the extinction of the dinosaurs.

He made a particular religion, you must be stupid, stupid, by the way.</desc>
  </DreadedDude94>
  <Tinkerer43>
    <title>service station</title>
    <titleShort>Correction situation</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] growing home purchase - the education to create a new machine waste heap of old and damaged parts of the waste .[PAWN_pronoun] other planets. Among friends, she eventually fled on board a conclusion is correct.</desc>
  </Tinkerer43>
  <Engineer47>
    <title>m</title>
    <titleShort>an engineer</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] planet irithir "i saw the job market and garage. a good deal, local merchants do not sell clothes, weapons and [PAWN_pronoun] interests option means the ability to recycle negotiations.</desc>
  </Engineer47>
  <DisplacedNoble83>
    <title>who lost</title>
    <titleShort>aristocracy</titleShort>
    <desc>Born urbworld, chief of the three cities, and the future is bright [PAWN_nameDef] them - to fall to death and rebellion [PAWN_possessive] family. [PAWN_nameDef] transport problems and the fight against Kigurai very picky.</desc>
  </DisplacedNoble83>
  <Minister88>
    <title>Ministry</title>
    <titleShort>content</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef], the public interest [PAWN_possessive], .[PAWN_pronoun] try to keep it as a lifestyle, the second glitterworld, .[PAWN_pronoun] important position in the management of the security they have enough time to rest and holiday makers - kedomo, [PAWN_pronoun] can not forget the hard work.</desc>
  </Minister88>
  <ChessMaster24>
    <title>Chess Champion</title>
    <titleShort>World chess champion</titleShort>
    <desc>Do [PAWN_pronoun] lever is in trouble - because that is a good thing in general, and therefore pose fu says sarah.</desc>
  </ChessMaster24>
  <Pirate69>
    <title>Chuzoku</title>
    <titleShort>Chuzoku</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun] name, again and again, his strategy is to get the name of a chain of huge problems.</desc>
  </Pirate69>
  <Orphan86>
    <title>fatherless</title>
    <titleShort>orphans</titleShort>
    <desc>Born dirt poor in the world [PAWN_nameDef] .[PAWN_pronoun] because the distance is still a job for life, and now another man, he did not know what it is like in a real childhood.</desc>
  </Orphan86>
  <BountyHunter8>
    <title>bounty hunter</title>
    <titleShort>Hunter</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] bounty hunter bounty spend every day in the 'clean air .[PAWN_pronoun] pirates.</desc>
  </BountyHunter8>
  <Straggler26>
    <title>Gypsy</title>
    <titleShort>nomadic</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun] often left to their fate, in other words, the more it seems like a lot of time with the uchikomi.</desc>
  </Straggler26>
  <Spiceminer42>
    <title>mineral Chu</title>
    <titleShort>Workers Sue</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] interests, such as the mountain was carved with the names of the world from the sky, the colony that will be distributed to the pen. ".

Not known yes, yes ben, trying to start might change their lives and their work now.</desc>
  </Spiceminer42>
  <BrutalThief89>
    <title>Allow the thief</title>
    <titleShort>robbery</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef], in a large group even brutality from Shaba.

all his -Qalb, and did not know the fatal weakness displayed open [PAWN_pronoun].</desc>
  </BrutalThief89>
  <CrimeLord56>
    <title>king</title>
    <titleShort>King of the crime</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun] hit, which is a report relating to weapons .[PAWN_possessive] be reliable, compassionate and desperate [PAWN_possessive] risk increases rapidly.</desc>
  </CrimeLord56>
  <BoySoldier14>
    <title>Child Soldiers</title>
    <titleShort>soldier</titleShort>
    <desc>Urbworld born in violence, [PAWN_nameDef], youth, education, the fight against the foreign troops, it was a good soldier.</desc>
  </BoySoldier14>
  <MarbleDoctor70>
    <title>medical</title>
    <titleShort>Dr</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef], for the treatment of injury or disease, .[PAWN_pronoun] strong, your doctor may use medical knowledge and machine guns, have been powerful.</desc>
  </MarbleDoctor70>
  <ApocalypseChild57>
    <title>last child</title>
    <titleShort>A child should</titleShort>
    <desc>I was a young man in order to save his childhood spent because it will progress to destroy [PAWN_nameDef] .[PAWN_pronoun], the world of shakespeare. What faith as the Earth, so it works.\n\nHe said the chance of anyone [PAWN_pronoun] home.</desc>
  </ApocalypseChild57>
  <MobHenchman24>
    <title>rawkazhy- up</title>
    <titleShort>khasama</titleShort>
    <desc>Hunt, star of the ship he was "saved" if the risk [PAWN_nameDef] [PAWN_pronoun], was allowed to be sold in low-tech Urbworld the causative agent, the original King was a professional.</desc>
  </MobHenchman24>
  <OrphanOfWar19>
    <title>the orphans of the war</title>
    <titleShort>orphan</titleShort>
    <desc>Not [PAWN_pronoun], it has been achieved, some companies instead of more than a year.</desc>
  </OrphanOfWar19>
  <MechWarVeteran31>
    <title>everything</title>
    <titleShort>old</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] herds have a pretty face, .[PAWN_pronoun] register false mechanical yoshinori seriously compete for the world half a dozen people were injured, we lose more than one lover recovery. This experience is difficult to [PAWN_objective] physically and mentally.</desc>
  </MechWarVeteran31>
  <ImperialStudent49>
    <title>Cabinet members</title>
    <titleShort>students</titleShort>
    <desc>I [PAWN_nameDef] empire midworld are prohibited weapons in self-defense, we encourage registration. A relatively safe environment [PAWN_objective] "factory to focus on research.</desc>
  </ImperialStudent49>
  <PoisonGardener29>
    <title>field</title>
    <titleShort>botanical</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] time that most of the costs for the treatment of plants in the garden, when removed from the poison society.

During this time, even deadly poisonous plants [PAWN_pronoun], a method that can be used for safer food and medicines made from certain bodies.</desc>
  </PoisonGardener29>
  <PowerMadScholar11>
    <title>Enjoy the power of maestro</title>
    <titleShort>science</titleShort>
    <desc>Is the power station was restored as "knowledge" in this [PAWN_possessive] core Hiramekase [PAWN_nameDef].

If you do not return to the machine in self-haired [PAWN_pronoun] the buy-books, view, are interested in organic materials.</desc>
  </PowerMadScholar11>
  <ArtificerRampant24>
    <title>cooperatives</title>
    <titleShort>Skilled workers</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun] deal with people outside of the group received the necessary materials for their actions -</desc>
  </ArtificerRampant24>
  <TechHead7>
    <title>Technology-poo</title>
    <titleShort>Advance technology</titleShort>
    <desc>Aerospace shell wall, and his father's son. [PAWN_nameDef] Childhood and love all this is the place to be standing in a suit.

The research project will be stored in C [PAWN_pronoun]. When under false [PAWN_pronoun] a father and son favorable .[PAWN_pronoun] used to provide plants deceptive [PAWN_possessive] room, he gave the guise of "Orbit".</desc>
  </TechHead7>
  <SystemsEngineer1>
    <title>systems engineering</title>
    <titleShort>engineer</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_possessive] as a father to his [PAWN_nameDef] [PAWN_pronoun] system engineer, space, both in the colony.

A decommissioned, [PAWN_pronoun] or other mechanical figurines, how ever seem to matter from time to time be known. In many areas, [PAWN_pronoun] an introverted personality, when he was alone.</desc>
  </SystemsEngineer1>
  <Orphan91>
    <title>baby</title>
    <titleShort>orphan</titleShort>
    <desc>Parents, Kevin and the rest, they can adapt to the conditions.

The government, if they are, how many people Sessure transport children in the same behavior.</desc>
  </Orphan91>
  <NeuroScientist84>
    <title>scientists skull</title>
    <titleShort>scientists</titleShort>
    <desc>Kevin is a long time, the human brain has learned to better understand the world.

This is the brain Kevin has been involved in mapping the brain scientists to explore strange successfully mapped.</desc>
  </NeuroScientist84>
  <Abductee43>
    <title>Hurtado</title>
    <titleShort>Robbed</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] download them with the new age, nature of work, but they were the servants of pirate pressed.</desc>
  </Abductee43>
  <PirateCaptain84>
    <title>Chuzoku</title>
    <titleShort>captain</titleShort>
    <desc>And in the end he was the captain of [PAWN_nameDef] chuzokukan noboritsume .[PAWN_pronoun], brain, kuwari all the friends came to the world, and the memory of his name.</desc>
  </PirateCaptain84>
  <BlackjackPlayer86>
    <title>toothpick</title>
    <titleShort>Vedi</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun] finally, keep your skin in order to meet fire and energy consuming .[PAWN_pronoun] half of the body, and cease to exist.</desc>
  </BlackjackPlayer86>
  <HedgeFundManager85>
    <title>hedge fund managers</title>
    <titleShort>bankers</titleShort>
    <desc>Urbworld [PAWN_nameDef] document rich and sweet bar manager for customers interested in the role of fraud in the hope of growth. Armored [PAWN_pronoun] star, and now she is a student on the availability of consumer paint needed for the principle of the content of bracelet.</desc>
  </HedgeFundManager85>
  <AcademyStudent80>
    <title>collegian</title>
    <titleShort>students</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] after .[PAWN_pronoun] passed a large school students as a base for sight better than to leave it.\n\nAt the same time, I passed the test to graduate Apsara results expressed concern management.</desc>
  </AcademyStudent80>
  <ComputerEngineer16>
    <title>geek</title>
    <titleShort>A high-tech</titleShort>
    <desc>However, every day, every day seems to campus, you will be sent every day tedious coding business [PAWN_nameDef] was watching television CM is processed limits "only powerful man in the world.".

He and his wife know that Morgan as [PAWN_nameDef] country.</desc>
  </ComputerEngineer16>
  <AspiringEngineer58>
    <title>students eggs</title>
    <titleShort>garage</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun] other adopted children, and to determine if a toy, it was built in the old, though it was fixing device.</desc>
  </AspiringEngineer58>
  <ExpertHandyman34>
    <title>professional yorozuya</title>
    <titleShort>yorozuya</titleShort>
    <desc>However, .[PAWN_pronoun] [PAWN_nameDef] repair shop for the travel company, easier communication equipment, carefully stacked complex spacecraft system to act as a wide variety of software. How there can not be undone there.</desc>
  </ExpertHandyman34>
  <MedicalStudent96>
    <title>Medical students</title>
    <titleShort>University student</titleShort>
    <desc>He was born in a family doctor the next generation, [PAWN_nameDef] Grease on the lawn, in modern synthetic drugs, .[PAWN_pronoun] a personal lesson for many drugs work less, watch out.</desc>
  </MedicalStudent96>
  <MedicSoldier58>
    <title>rescue soldiers</title>
    <titleShort>military needy</titleShort>
    <desc>Studying medicine to help people walk in nature and at the same time [PAWN_pronoun] house the soldiers after demobilization.</desc>
  </MedicSoldier58>
  <HighBaroness29>
    <title>Royal Earl</title>
    <titleShort>aristocrat</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] empire was born in a low-cost ,.

This planet, from childhood, the role of the high political, cultural skills are not controlled.</desc>
  </HighBaroness29>
  <ExiledResearcher68>
    <title>Researchers Refugees</title>
    <titleShort>who had escaped</titleShort>
    <desc>Love is not robotic technology rich [PAWN_nameDef] rejection well. Cardinal [PAWN_pronoun] excomungar higher measures as allowed again.</desc>
  </ExiledResearcher68>
  <WorldSlider56>
    <title>slider</title>
    <titleShort>skater</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] [PAWN_pronoun] the world's population has grown up around the crime branch, but, crime, brother, pharmacy and the martial arts scene out of the team to use [PAWN_pronoun], no evidence was brought to leave soon.</desc>
  </WorldSlider56>
  <Villain66>
    <title>The villain</title>
    <titleShort>villain</titleShort>
    <desc>After the organized crime of Noboritsume. [PAWN_nameDef] weapons technology to produce weapons he taught badly. People are faced with a decision about how wisdom.</desc>
  </Villain66>
  <MedicalStudent38>
    <title>Medical students</title>
    <titleShort>students</titleShort>
    <desc>After a family doctor, was born in generations, and modern synthetic drugs, [PAWN_nameDef] herbal ointment on the number of private medical schools and youth .[PAWN_pronoun] field.</desc>
  </MedicalStudent38>
  <SpaceNavyDoctor72>
    <title>The doctor</title>
    <titleShort>Surgeon</titleShort>
    <desc>Harbin other people in the skills of the surgeon, sometimes close to home planet, [PAWN_nameDef] [PAWN_pronoun] campaign, because the sea air support for the sake of some experts in the battle of serious injury due to a number of services, and rude.</desc>
  </SpaceNavyDoctor72>
  <AspergersRebel66>
    <title>Asperger rebels</title>
    <titleShort>cool</titleShort>
    <desc>The patient's symptoms and sociability with asperger [PAWN_pronoun] that people do not worry about shooting skills are difficult to look for what to learn quickly.</desc>
  </AspergersRebel66>
  <GovernmentAgent47>
    <title>Government agencies</title>
    <titleShort>yellow</titleShort>
    <desc>Good treatment [PAWN_nameDef] benefits, training, aircraft, artillery, are losing the battle against the government.

He grew up in the city, the damage on the ground, glue blood, corpses, and others, do not bother to try to advance it seems to prevent them.</desc>
  </GovernmentAgent47>
  <ShootingComa31>
    <title>CLA shooting</title>
    <titleShort>children Koma</titleShort>
    <desc>Weight nebulys fainted when young, although they spend years without waking dream .[PAWN_pronoun] shooting continued success of all work - but we prepared well.</desc>
  </ShootingComa31>
  <SelflessHunter57>
    <title>sacrificing Hunter</title>
    <titleShort>Hunting</titleShort>
    <desc>Nebulys a hunter hunting the mysterious organisms do not think even a lot of people. Or worse - sometimes called, or the right person.

Along the way, he helped those in need.</desc>
  </SelflessHunter57>
  <PsychologyStudent20>
    <title>Psychology student</title>
    <titleShort>students</titleShort>
    <desc>What are stars in the sky dream [PAWN_possessive] nomukou how? motif ask [PAWN_objective].</desc>
  </PsychologyStudent20>
  <AcolyteOfStars63>
    <title>Using believer asterisk</title>
    <titleShort>leader</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] now consider the way in, I feel like a galaxy before the Lord, for a dreamy voice.\n\n[PAWN_pronoun] a bad thing, but now has all means for travel.</desc>
  </AcolyteOfStars63>
  <SpaceSmuggler10>
    <title>smuggler</title>
    <titleShort>Smuggler</titleShort>
    <desc>A report by the parents to help me fight and earth that illegal trading houses and their use.

And also to transport it, the smallness of the human body and is designed to meet the objective that parents are given below in the discussion of methods of smuggling weapons, it is very good to deal with.</desc>
  </SpaceSmuggler10>
  <SpaceRaider65>
    <title>space Race</title>
    <titleShort>thief</titleShort>
    <desc>Chuzoku Institute have been. Fly in the central region on earth, and now I'm afraid a lot of enemies to the colony.</desc>
  </SpaceRaider65>
  <Abductee80>
    <title>thieves</title>
    <titleShort>abductees</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] abducted by a stranger when the boy. Foreigners must [PAWN_objective] [PAWN_possessive] vbyeha understand the genetic structure.\n\nA little more than a very strong record of growth [PAWN_nameDef] when we finally escape.</desc>
  </Abductee80>
  <Spy58>
    <title>spy</title>
    <titleShort>Spy</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] always quiet prepared by the [PAWN_pronoun] [PAWN_possessive] agent access strategy division government, even in difficult situations, avoid wearing a comment. Guide [PAWN_pronoun] provide good potential to attract even more this way.</desc>
  </Spy58>
  <BlessedChild46>
    <title>Good for children</title>
    <titleShort>gospel</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun] enough poor care, as believers teach children.</desc>
  </BlessedChild46>
  <WanderingHealer52>
    <title>I will heal their victims</title>
    <titleShort>healing hands</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] studied as a doctor, but in different ways, the easiest way calms nari did not meet our midworld.

As [PAWN_pronoun] I had lived so long, we went to the most important areas [PAWN_pronoun].</desc>
  </WanderingHealer52>
  <YouthSoldier87>
    <title>child soldiers</title>
    <titleShort>soldiers</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun] competent in physical training, and more, is that many of the decline .[PAWN_pronoun] also adopted, in particular, because it means the head rotation speed, and wore a value [PAWN_nameDef] again painful workout.</desc>
  </YouthSoldier87>
  <VeteranSoldier42>
    <title>veteran champion</title>
    <titleShort>soldiers</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef], which chuzoku .[PAWN_pronoun] son of man, and there are many opponents to fight against unfair elections, the glory of war and terrorism, we are known for.

I think that the army had retired from the army, wear them with a drill and enforcement of the colonies will sow the soldiers tried [PAWN_nameDef] .[PAWN_pronoun] as polished and diligently given hard work and proud to always be our friend.</desc>
  </VeteranSoldier42>
  <GlitterworldKid13>
    <title>Children's world</title>
    <titleShort>Glitter child</titleShort>
    <desc>As a teenager, [PAWN_pronoun] looking to be quiet, and away from home.</desc>
  </GlitterworldKid13>
  <CosmeticReject89>
    <title>ready for life</title>
    <titleShort>defective article</titleShort>
    <desc>He lived in the part of the people in exchange for food and Gaza beds, dirty plants Institute, and will be treated as slaves.

Sometimes after surgery painful, had publicly retracted the original format Chaz. Until then, they say bad things, parents worry about the person had a job to save the lab, Chaz members.</desc>
  </CosmeticReject89>
  <FeralChild17>
    <title>use of children</title>
    <titleShort>Survivor</titleShort>
    <desc>Family [PAWN_nameDef], [PAWN_possessive], particularly in the case, RimWorld done yet.

One Osoikakari Mekanoido a group, we were all friends of Robert died. He, and you get the Nexus, I live alone in the wild.</desc>
  </FeralChild17>
  <RaiderKing46>
    <title>Table</title>
    <titleShort>Rider</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] in life, which is convenient to work with a group of others, what is not, now shows that all would know his name called and tough.</desc>
  </RaiderKing46>
  <Scout66>
    <title>Knowledge workers</title>
    <titleShort>detectives</titleShort>
    <desc>Nate is on the outside. The ability to train wooden parents, who asked to authorize military. Harry were in the desert've.

In education, can be seen from [PAWN_nameDef] cake and other skills are key technologies.</desc>
  </Scout66>
  <FrontierMarshal26>
    <title>French law enforcement</title>
    <titleShort>police</titleShort>
    <desc>Nate .[PAWN_pronoun] offender population, we strive to maintain a healthy work, but deadly local mayor, killed his family [PAWN_objective], abandoned [PAWN_pronoun].

The following health .[PAWN_pronoun] Nantes bound mayor homeland, also living in a different a different galaxy.</desc>
  </FrontierMarshal26>
  <TraineeAlchemist86>
    <title>Students Alchemist</title>
    <titleShort>blacksmith</titleShort>
    <desc>He grew up in the stars during the middle of the monastery [PAWN_nameDef] .[PAWN_pronoun], home planet to learn the basics of chemistry and pharmacy.</desc>
  </TraineeAlchemist86>
  <ReligiousHierarch15>
    <title>Abbot</title>
    <titleShort>Shinto priest</titleShort>
    <desc>The place of the city, the priest of the lieutenants, and the houses of the people set fire to the [PAWN_nameDef] the context of the arts, the higher the level of the intensity of the .[PAWN_pronoun] are said to be in the region of the extinction of a upstart is not put out.

day when the message sent lifofa-area business .[PAWN_pronoun] remains close to his house [PAWN_nameDef] decided to work together to find a global competition and new business.</desc>
  </ReligiousHierarch15>
  <MilitaryCadet16>
    <title>recruiting</title>
    <titleShort>younger son</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] orphans, Deadworld was sent to the military institution.

Appointed soon [PAWN_pronoun] Technology Wear safety equipment and head graduates as commander of the operation secret.</desc>
  </MilitaryCadet16>
  <AnarchistRebel83>
    <title>Rebels</title>
    <titleShort>In opposition to government support payments</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] is waiho'ia by the special mission, .[PAWN_pronoun] countries pledge to punish the rebel organization dedicated to the overthrow of the central government.\n\noften, he falls into a crisis without raising much success, [PAWN_nameDef] fled across.</desc>
  </AnarchistRebel83>
  <Pickpocket19>
    <title>Mr</title>
    <titleShort>thief</titleShort>
    <desc>If no longer able to assist their [PAWN_nameDef], witness this event, the young parents, [PAWN_pronoun] to use the card. [PAWN_pronoun] add group Arab world, if there is one we have to live, no matter what.</desc>
  </Pickpocket19>
  <CriminalSurgeon99>
    <title>pairs surgeon</title>
    <titleShort>Dr</titleShort>
    <desc>And very close to our wicked [PAWN_nameDef] is money voluntarily.

For a lot of people to death, the surgeon, it is better [PAWN_pronoun].</desc>
  </CriminalSurgeon99>
  <SpaceCadet12>
    <title>Space Cadet</title>
    <titleShort>cadet</titleShort>
    <desc>Super thunder hms interplanetary [PAWN_pronoun] murder.</desc>
  </SpaceCadet12>
  <SanitationCaptain28>
    <title>length drop</title>
    <titleShort>Manager</titleShort>
    <desc>After graduating from the School Director Training, Jake is assigned to the operating room .[PAWN_pronoun] Thunder Child, annual service, and "Heroes" celebrity former body assigned to review -loo them.</desc>
  </SanitationCaptain28>
  <Naturalist88>
    <title>behavior</title>
    <titleShort>nature</titleShort>
    <desc>Mitch weather hunting around the planet growing plants in response to .[PAWN_pronoun] education and training reduced is not necessary to survive.

[PAWN_pronoun] family oriented, food was invaded several times raider. Mitch believes that there is serious doubt that a lot of people.</desc>
  </Naturalist88>
  <OverwatchSniper1>
    <title>went walking</title>
    <titleShort>Shooters</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] know why they went into battle, but continued to live in order to protect military troops.

His tired of military life, I have a spare. And behold, you will learn to work with conflicts such grant wounds after being shot in a hurry.</desc>
  </OverwatchSniper1>
  <Drudge59>
    <title>in absentia</title>
    <titleShort>Part-time employees</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun] opportunity, an opportunity to attract more of the games live, or somewhere fun to see.</desc>
  </Drudge59>
  <Sightseer11>
    <title>visitors</title>
    <titleShort>shift</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] .[PAWN_pronoun] star passes through the station to the assembly, which is somehow able to have them, it seems, is the way to zero. I can not find around the galaxy, Luke [PAWN_possessive] [PAWN_pronoun].

As Iraq behavior [PAWN_pronoun] world and wear old wildlife. Other methods of miracle, because it is unlikely, [PAWN_objective] galaxy.</desc>
  </Sightseer11>
  <BunkerKid36>
    <title>Shelter children</title>
    <titleShort>residents kid</titleShort>
    <desc>Ricardo is looking forward to a full radiation dose is reduced, the better underground bunkers. rich family of billions of people around the world access to the death of Luxury Residence.

Shooting practice spends revenge for the time on training tools in the past Ricardo, enemies were to decide.</desc>
  </BunkerKid36>
  <GameTester90>
    <title>beta testing</title>
    <titleShort>Beta tester</titleShort>
    <desc>In many parts of the world after a nuclear war, start a new life, [PAWN_nameDef] money borrowed from his father, he was able to fulfill her wish.

He wants to play a leading simulator in the world. His favorite game is building a hospital in carefully. And I very much during the game, fear and war was enough to forget about revenge.</desc>
  </GameTester90>
  <ChildOfDrifters28>
    <title>children</title>
    <titleShort>Castaway</titleShort>
    <desc>As [PAWN_pronoun] way, [PAWN_nameDef] little, I do not know the world outside the mother ship [PAWN_possessive]. [PAWN_possessive] life and fire frequency, turning received travels with his parents as a child.</desc>
  </ChildOfDrifters28>
  <WanderingCrafter23>
    <title>fond exile</title>
    <titleShort>craftsmen</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] continue to monitor aloha hawaii nomadic parents support the ongoing work. But men hit hard and often. [PAWN_pronoun] Ikase their skills, I think one of the stable and suitable for the country.</desc>
  </WanderingCrafter23>
  <TribalThunderer45>
    <title>throne Nations</title>
    <titleShort>Raijin</titleShort>
    <desc>A few years ago, [PAWN_nameDef] tribe, I had the opportunity to leave the warehouse for weapons. Who do you believe will be like a fruitful vine, on the arms of the children of the sacred, the religions, the less the sacred in Sherman asked for the protection of a villa which is with a gun .[PAWN_nameDef] honored that as the child.</desc>
  </TribalThunderer45>
  <MutinousCaptain52>
    <title>Rebellion on</title>
    <titleShort>captain</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] war, killing many people [PAWN_possessive] nations, has been removed from trafficking. A few years later, in this way at the end of [PAWN_pronoun] [PAWN_objective] they will come to discuss the project and held a dialogue.

It makes revenge for riots, it is supposed, [PAWN_nameDef] best understood when he was the same person.</desc>
  </MutinousCaptain52>
  <Gymnast34>
    <title>athlete</title>
    <titleShort>gymnast</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a gymnast in his youth. Thanks to ability, to be able to register at the University [PAWN_pronoun] away from the glare of the parent planet.\n\nGymnastics, because she was not allowed to have a job, [PAWN_pronoun] the rest of the credit another unoccupied area, a huge number.</desc>
  </Gymnast34>
  <IntimateAssassin59>
    <title>Fascinated by murder</title>
    <titleShort>Assassin</titleShort>
    <desc>The calculation of the maximum attention carrots .[PAWN_pronoun] [PAWN_nameDef] shigyaku seem to kill animals that injure humans.\n\nThey prefer to use instruments that divisions to kill the target. It was met and the realization of the contract, their personal wishes.</desc>
  </IntimateAssassin59>
  <CorpBredStudent56>
    <title>Student artificial insemination</title>
    <titleShort>students</titleShort>
    <desc>If the age of five, [PAWN_pronoun], enrolled in training with the aim of freezing and loyalty, .[PAWN_nameDef], which comes with the university, even in cases where violence is still a need, which is more than looking for a way that this dialogue.</desc>
  </CorpBredStudent56>
  <CorpResearcher93>
    <title>analysts</title>
    <titleShort>researcher</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] company to sell, because they have the right to scientific research slaves company.

is working to [PAWN_possessive] working environment unable to adapt, [PAWN_pronoun] goal in the workplace and to develop the area. [PAWN_pronoun] want to leave the company every day.</desc>
  </CorpResearcher93>
  <EarthColonist48>
    <title>settlers land</title>
    <titleShort>colony</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] born on earth. When he was a child, [PAWN_pronoun], was launched on the basis of a program to colonize the planet in space.</desc>
  </EarthColonist48>
  <SoleSurvivor90>
    <title>The only survivor</title>
    <titleShort>JASPER</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] of roman colonists. Senchipido [PAWN_possessive] attacked and killed the only surviving [PAWN_pronoun].</desc>
  </SoleSurvivor90>
  <MilitaryTrainee20>
    <title>military exercise</title>
    <titleShort>Child soldiers</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef], .[PAWN_pronoun] guests of foreign military bases, following direct exposure to several groups of young people active in extra-curricular activities, business methods .[PAWN_pronoun] and strong, wearing medical strategies.</desc>
  </MilitaryTrainee20>
  <AWOLSoldier20>
    <title>soldiers would</title>
    <titleShort>military</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun] xenno to zartz his employment, I decided to be a soldier .[PAWN_pronoun], I escape of military aircraft.</desc>
  </AWOLSoldier20>
  <Bookworm3>
    <title>Books</title>
    <titleShort>bibliophile</titleShort>
    <desc>Young [PAWN_nameDef] libraries, documentation and technical forums, a wonderful long-range exploration of how a remarkable achievement, .[PAWN_pronoun] with your own eyes, mekanoido story is still interesting reading about the book; I swear.</desc>
  </Bookworm3>
  <Explorer28>
    <title>inspectors</title>
    <titleShort>researcher</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef], the life of the world, such as the book, from the research trip [PAWN_pronoun] all animals, plants, minerals, machinery, materials they collected a record compiled a book that said. "the complete guide on roads RimWorlds"</desc>
  </Explorer28>
  <ColonyKid47>
    <title>colony boy</title>
    <titleShort>slave</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] in fact, it does not get along with other children is shy, is now conscious.</desc>
  </ColonyKid47>
  <StarshipDoctor82>
    <title>surgeon</title>
    <titleShort>doctor</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] ride surgeon .[PAWN_pronoun], as well as a talented surgeon who dabbled study .[PAWN_pronoun] [PAWN_possessive] himself isolated, not all who care for the patient improved.</desc>
  </StarshipDoctor82>
  <CaravanChild91>
    <title>Ana companies</title>
    <titleShort>childish</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] urbworld businessman, entrepreneur, mother, father was not born, and slim. He appeared as "she" always interested in my mother hated men work activity.

Finally, his mother, sees the world dedicated to the use of reserves, the body was exposed.</desc>
  </CaravanChild91>
  <BountyHunter41>
    <title>the best hunter</title>
    <titleShort>Bounty Hunter</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] .but the [PAWN_pronoun] a good job, millions of consumers, glitterworld numerous large donations hunter, and is, a patient known to other laws.</desc>
  </BountyHunter41>
  <ReEducatedYouth23>
    <title>Re-education of children</title>
    <titleShort>reeducation</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun], purokuramu new school, the children were separated from their parents, he was one of many.</desc>
  </ReEducatedYouth23>
  <FallenOfficial12>
    <title>Official holiday</title>
    <titleShort>Official</titleShort>
    <desc>If the question put [PAWN_possessive] [PAWN_nameDef] stop work, no clothes, no where to go from planet home.</desc>
  </FallenOfficial12>
  <FarmMechanic1>
    <title>Mechanics Valley</title>
    <titleShort>mechanic</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] planet, plant, harvest and learning, cars km recognize many spend a lifetime.</desc>
  </FarmMechanic1>
  <OrbitalReservist22>
    <title>The backup job Composition</title>
    <titleShort>The soldiers of the obligatory reserve</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun] defense which falls to the space station while pressing assigned personnel to enter the atmosphere.</desc>
  </OrbitalReservist22>
  <AccursedChild81>
    <title>children were</title>
    <titleShort>Mm</titleShort>
    <desc>I live on the rise month [PAWN_nameDef] toruk mashi, welcome. [PAWN_objective] ancient darkness a baby announcement, the refuge was in the letter.\n\nNations to the series go to the youth for education [PAWN_possessive] students coming days ....</desc>
  </AccursedChild81>
  <ShamanOfShadows47>
    <title>shadow wizard</title>
    <titleShort>remember</titleShort>
    <desc>Avatar fire came down from heaven and then be asked to lead [PAWN_nameDef], [PAWN_possessive] generation.

[PAWN_nameDef] leading power plants and often move was attacked, many soldiers face. You can also include not to be deterred from Chuzoku forced bondage can.</desc>
  </ShamanOfShadows47>
  <AmateurAstronomer86>
    <title>amateur astronomers</title>
    <titleShort>astronomers</titleShort>
    <desc>It was installed [PAWN_nameDef] .[PAWN_pronoun], the mood of the heavenly bodies, taken within a few hours, or the stars and vomiting, from fog or search through a telescope.\n\n[PAWN_pronoun] us some glory invisible stars, stars and the moon a few years gilgal mining business press.</desc>
  </AmateurAstronomer86>
  <StationSecurity87>
    <title>Railway police</title>
    <titleShort>railway police officer</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] appointed special police galaxy. It is not necessary to stop those sales.

Fire station, the many brick fire has been saved once, and along with fire.</desc>
  </StationSecurity87>
  <FarmHand30>
    <title>Bond</title>
    <titleShort>farmer</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] grown on small farmers and local landscapes.

[PAWN_nameDef] between us and all participants a couple of people who farm. Regarding the independence of the heart, enriches the rich spirit, I decided to regulators.</desc>
  </FarmHand30>
  <SpaceTrafficker68>
    <title>Operators in space</title>
    <titleShort>Traders</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] uncle while, arms trafficking an heir.

Such unforeseen situations in order to protect the company's future, [PAWN_pronoun] it was a military training area.</desc>
  </SpaceTrafficker68>
  <EnergeticPopIdol4>
    <title>Active and passive</title>
    <titleShort>fetish</titleShort>
    <desc>Priscilla, gliterowrld grew up, I learned the art of singing and rapier. Idol, he has been living for many years.

Was not happy with the music model, but decided to go for it because the role instead.</desc>
  </EnergeticPopIdol4>
  <PopIdolPirate17>
    <title>Kidnapping Idol</title>
    <titleShort>Chuzoku</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef], on their way to their fans and chuzoku. He is known to stage various artists so attacked, hiring companies.

[PAWN_nameDef], occurs once an enemy of him in the standings, is now worried about the fire. The man who did everything for disabled fans.</desc>
  </PopIdolPirate17>
  <IcePlanetChild60>
    <title>Boy Ice Planet</title>
    <titleShort>Ice man</titleShort>
    <desc>Frozen month, desert animals [PAWN_nameDef] great sea, only a few sailors and stable friend.

There was not a lot of man - the lack of social interaction, and it is likely that interest in engineering.</desc>
  </IcePlanetChild60>
  <Roboticist43>
    <title>robot experts</title>
    <titleShort>robotics expert</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef], and other personal care [PAWN_possessive].</desc>
  </Roboticist43>
  <Scrounger25>
    <title>Sponging shop</title>
    <titleShort>Mushroom shop</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun] a stench and danger, though, with a time and leave the place the week of injury.</desc>
  </Scrounger25>
  <Chemist54>
    <title>drug</title>
    <titleShort>dispenser</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] and the chemical industry midworld known.

He still RimWorld animals after humans change the human experience, [PAWN_pronoun] been arrested.</desc>
  </Chemist54>
  <ToxicChild81>
    <title>dependent children</title>
    <titleShort>poisoning</titleShort>
    <desc>In industrialized countries has risen [PAWN_nameDef] cause chemical plant for six years. Stealing plants from the ran auto [PAWN_pronoun] world.</desc>
  </ToxicChild81>
  <StalwartFarmer98>
    <title>strong farmer</title>
    <titleShort>answer</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun] tried to paint a picture that is not allowed once scribbled duck house.</desc>
  </StalwartFarmer98>
  <BoyScout11>
    <title>Scouts</title>
    <titleShort>explorer</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun] outdoors and damage to the health benefits, such as basic skills, including the ability to increase the survival, life was very eroded.</desc>
  </BoyScout11>
  <UrbworldPimp36>
    <title>Pimp urbworld</title>
    <titleShort>Pander</titleShort>
    <desc>First, [PAWN_nameDef], drug sales and to create a source of income. [PAWN_pronoun] .[PAWN_pronoun] ability to use punch [PAWN_possessive] travel [PAWN_pronoun] wounds, how to deal with women, and mask.</desc>
  </UrbworldPimp36>
  <ScienceProdigy16>
    <title>Genius Scientist</title>
    <titleShort>genius</titleShort>
    <desc>The [PAWN_nameDef], chemistry, physics, astronomy, biology, space was needed for important [PAWN_possessive] class class.

It was so bad, I'm afraid, laboratory, fire [PAWN_pronoun] against him allegedly is an accident.</desc>
  </ScienceProdigy16>
  <ParticlePhysicist78>
    <title>Particle Physics</title>
    <titleShort>-fiosaig</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef], physics in this study, dizziness was the guy .[PAWN_pronoun] sharp, a better future and help us to think that it would be more peaceful.</desc>
  </ParticlePhysicist78>
  <SpeederRacer2>
    <title>Speeder Racer</title>
    <titleShort>studio</titleShort>
    <desc>The son of a farmer, rusty tower khalderia as ferns, are one.

race [PAWN_pronoun] deck overlooking the stunning winter look for the large terrace, which is speed arisen horekomi.
Underground Community Shadi, the race [PAWN_pronoun] but to defend themselves on their own, stukalo.</desc>
  </SpeederRacer2>
  <DefenseLawyer71>
    <title>Advocate</title>
    <titleShort>lawyer</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef], speech blaster good speech in the archbishop, I understand that it is easier to make more money. [PAWN_pronoun] [PAWN_pronoun] generation can be used as illegal to save the speeder.</desc>
  </DefenseLawyer71>
  <MercenaryRecruit18>
    <title>mercenaries</title>
    <titleShort>Igbo</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] born mercenary past, I grew up in Sewashinai mall. When I was a kid, [PAWN_pronoun] set by terrorists.</desc>
  </MercenaryRecruit18>
  <Ranger6>
    <title>Ranger</title>
    <titleShort>forestry</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] deep forest, some life .[PAWN_pronoun] came to watch wildlife from poachers. Request for help from abroad to meet the needs of a free, dress [PAWN_possessive].</desc>
  </Ranger6>
  <MarineCadet73>
    <title>cadet</title>
    <titleShort>Cadet</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] sat sea cadets.

[PAWN_pronoun] allowed to leave the police were killed. Or that the risk was not allowed to show.</desc>
  </MarineCadet73>
  <ClanChief14>
    <title>Royal</title>
    <titleShort>Basic</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] out between us and the star system business was criminal.</desc>
  </ClanChief14>
  <YoungPsychologist58>
    <title>a young psychologist</title>
    <titleShort>promote development</titleShort>
    <desc>Midworld born poor [PAWN_nameDef], taxi [PAWN_possessive] mother grew up in the passenger seat.

When you see pedestrians on the same day and listening to the stories of passengers [PAWN_pronoun], to understand the real purpose of people soon became good.</desc>
  </YoungPsychologist58>
  <FactionLeader74>
    <title>group leader</title>
    <titleShort>leadership</titleShort>
    <desc>In the early days to mature, [PAWN_nameDef] yasagure is followed by another.

Sport [PAWN_pronoun], the truth is, in order to kill one of the leaders gathered in accordance with the .[PAWN_pronoun] store in the product, you know what I means directly below.</desc>
  </FactionLeader74>
  <Tinkerer54>
    <title>Technology</title>
    <titleShort>Craftsman</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun] interest, action, or even a simple robot that makes the device smaller.</desc>
  </Tinkerer54>
  <ProstheticSurgeon0>
    <title>surgical prosthesis</title>
    <titleShort>surgery</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] replaced by metal workers and other electronic parts and internal organs talent "before" bio-engineering only.</desc>
  </ProstheticSurgeon0>
  <LabGrownChild25>
    <title>children Culture</title>
    <titleShort>Viola and Culture</titleShort>
    <desc>Study -to- ugly, ashamed of essential human nature .[PAWN_pronoun] akekure [PAWN_pronoun] childhood experience and reading, really was not enough.</desc>
  </LabGrownChild25>
  <CorpResearcher85>
    <title>Company Mis</title>
    <titleShort>researcher</titleShort>
    <desc>Das [PAWN_nameDef] markets such as permits to work in research.

Therefore, it can be adapted for the job, because they were entrusted not only the work to develop an edge. He left the company every day.</desc>
  </CorpResearcher85>
  <Orphan11>
    <title>orphan</title>
    <titleShort>orphan</titleShort>
    <desc>E 'was born in poverty in the region, [PAWN_nameDef] is dirty because it is a strange job for .[PAWN_pronoun] do not know what a real childhood, and now the other person's distance.</desc>
  </Orphan11>
  <SpaceMarine9>
    <title>Beetle overlap Maritime</title>
    <titleShort>ferry</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] group of soldiers of the emperor, was a member of the coleoptera. Said pseudo-religions and many [PAWN_possessive], which is found between the risks of war, will help us to continue to maintain a low profile.</desc>
  </SpaceMarine9>
  <TechScholar88>
    <title>Technology Research</title>
    <titleShort>scholar</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun] forward, and at the end of each day, we want to go.</desc>
  </TechScholar88>
  <TechnologyDoctor35>
    <title>Technology Dr</title>
    <titleShort>Technology Dr</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun], so the study of technology in this case, we want to improve people's lives.</desc>
  </TechnologyDoctor35>
  <PitGladiator89>
    <title>Gladiatorial arena</title>
    <titleShort>ancient times</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef], like the children of slavery, forced disappearances and other dangerous animals and humans, subway, found in this war.

[PAWN_pronoun], sports, shows a similar struggle, finally won freedom. [PAWN_possessive] stadium and spent [PAWN_pronoun] is not intellectual.</desc>
  </PitGladiator89>
  <PirateTrooper68>
    <title>Chuzoku warrior</title>
    <titleShort>soldier</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_possessive] actual combat experience, but a good [PAWN_pronoun] strong, strong man cruel [PAWN_objective] no interest in the social sector.</desc>
  </PirateTrooper68>
  <FactoryWorker58>
    <title>A factory worker</title>
    <titleShort>Work</titleShort>
    <desc>Felix grew up in a large factory in the industry.

Many, extreme poverty, food shortages remuneration for work, so some of them your own. Felix's life But you have to love the hard work.</desc>
  </FactoryWorker58>
  <CombatMedic16>
    <title>Dr</title>
    <titleShort>doctor</titleShort>
    <desc>War [PAWN_possessive] rush felix war and enlisted as a doctor in the military.

In the year and a time in the trench, try to shoot [PAWN_possessive] and striving to continue the recording to be used, it was not a tough decision aid. He lost a lot of friends, he was indifferent conservative [PAWN_objective]:</desc>
  </CombatMedic16>
  <RichBoy23>
    <title>Your child daidzin</title>
    <titleShort>Rich kids</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] and the love of a parent midworld, cute pet as a lot of money, but also friends, and not man.

[PAWN_pronoun] [PAWN_possessive] father "boys poor, because he is employed only for the gold," he said as he always said. I spent time with [PAWN_pronoun] or so other children and battle.</desc>
  </RichBoy23>
  <HiredGun28>
    <title>thug hired</title>
    <titleShort>Hired gunmen</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun], in the end, when the boat ticket, take the cheaper the cost of transport is broken, but earned enough money, I remember that price is the cheapest.</desc>
  </HiredGun28>
  <Athlete23>
    <title>athlete</title>
    <titleShort>sport</titleShort>
    <desc>Two long time for the child to leave the planet home, professional player [PAWN_possessive] [PAWN_pronoun] [PAWN_nameDef] a lot of skills, he enrolled at the university of science and technology glitterworld.

The identity and nationality neglect to participate in the Master Plan, a society may inconvenience.</desc>
  </Athlete23>
  <StilettoAssassin50>
    <title>steel, murder</title>
    <titleShort>killer</titleShort>
    <desc>According to the capacity [PAWN_possessive], this was a great [PAWN_nameDef]. At the same time, [PAWN_pronoun] .[PAWN_pronoun] who are lonely, often counter that, to find an easy way to kill him.

And I think my skill, [PAWN_pronoun], the company realizes that to kill one hand.</desc>
  </StilettoAssassin50>
  <SoleSurvivor99>
    <title>Only one left</title>
    <titleShort>read</titleShort>
    <desc>Parts hawke mysterious death blow.

It is only adopted tribal found in a sub-tribe, this is nostalgic. He was on foot in the new house, where, wanted to take care of the animals.</desc>
  </SoleSurvivor99>
  <Hunter7>
    <title>hUNTER</title>
    <titleShort>hunter</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun], even dangerous, and how to monitor chrv silver confidence, learn to manage some of the largest animals, many thought mshy have a good knowledge of the rich.</desc>
  </Hunter7>
  <MechanoidHacker93>
    <title>Hacker mechanical isoprenoid</title>
    <titleShort>MEC Hacker</titleShort>
    <desc>Respect invention Mekanoido collected only child [PAWN_nameDef] it [PAWN_pronoun] father created or disasters probability that a substance which is or conversion.

[PAWN_pronoun] be used to increase productivity drag. Unfortunately, the 'side effects, as long as social, the' limited Machining [PAWN_possessive] excitement.</desc>
  </MechanoidHacker93>
  <BattlefieldTech75>
    <title>Battlefield expert</title>
    <titleShort>specialist</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] in the form of heavy weapons, mekanoido trial operation is fighting a note ,. which is a battlefield commission [PAWN_possessive], appropriate technology

at first, he could afford to have fled [PAWN_pronoun] time, was developed by d. wheat fields. The surgeon was [PAWN_objective] demobilized.</desc>
  </BattlefieldTech75>
  <ProjectSubject48>
    <title>The purpose of the project</title>
    <titleShort>Goal</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] abstract "development projects" have been involved in the selection of delegates.

About storage operations, [PAWN_pronoun], the project involves reflection, why not remember the rest - most, but no.</desc>
  </ProjectSubject48>
  <MasterTrader96>
    <title>Master Trader</title>
    <titleShort>Dealer</titleShort>
    <desc>These are the customers compared to [PAWN_nameDef] .[PAWN_pronoun], and I helped him a lot of them in the city, called his name in a letter of acceptance.</desc>
  </MasterTrader96>
  <HexCellArtist91>
    <title>Artist hex cell</title>
    <titleShort>artist</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] carving a statue at the end of hexagonal cells were shopping to buy food at the local museum.

he was kidnapped while [PAWN_pronoun] place [PAWN_possessive] increase walking. Chuzoku then forced to sell the statue [PAWN_objective] prisoners.</desc>
  </HexCellArtist91>
  <ExoticChef96>
    <title>Foreign chef</title>
    <titleShort>cook</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun] plant and equipment for the plant and bring [PAWN_objective].</desc>
  </ExoticChef96>
  <PlagueProdigy59>
    <title>genius disease</title>
    <titleShort>genius</titleShort>
    <desc>When a mysterious disease that spread throughout mother [PAWN_nameDef] [PAWN_possessive] star range.

at the same time, is a close friend and human nature [PAWN_pronoun] views are sympathetic and even death. In such cases, a thirst for new knowledge.</desc>
  </PlagueProdigy59>
  <MadScientist1>
    <title>Mad scientist</title>
    <titleShort>world</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] knowledge that everyone hates looking for sagaru strong thirst and research.

To travel around the world, will continue [PAWN_pronoun] find answers.</desc>
  </MadScientist1>
  <PoorKid84>
    <title>poor children</title>
    <titleShort>Poor Children</titleShort>
    <desc>Abandoned by his parents, [PAWN_nameDef], dressed in unique ways to survive 10 years.</desc>
  </PoorKid84>
  <Warrior73>
    <title>Containers of the transfer</title>
    <titleShort>war hero</titleShort>
    <desc>Pressure posts [PAWN_nameDef] .[PAWN_pronoun], helping to prevent weapons nuclear, because it is naturally stable, held star [PAWN_possessive] among other things, that world war three, with the hero.</desc>
  </Warrior73>
  <Dreamer79>
    <title>dreams</title>
    <titleShort>dream</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef], .[PAWN_pronoun] rich could face child-friendly, a song, and old can sing young people.

[PAWN_pronoun] hatred and conflict, [PAWN_pronoun] as such, is one of the dangers. This is a personal attack.</desc>
  </Dreamer79>
  <SpaceExplorer63>
    <title>The space explorers</title>
    <titleShort>researcher</titleShort>
    <desc>As it found the escape, .[PAWN_pronoun] quickly adapt to the local of our earth strangers trapped for about 10 years, and worn out after the voice [PAWN_nameDef].

Not even for a long time, the heart .[PAWN_pronoun] his own elegant way limited, but, feel [PAWN_pronoun] news actually wearing them.</desc>
  </SpaceExplorer63>
  <UrbworldUrchin13>
    <title>Sin urbworld</title>
    <titleShort>deceiver</titleShort>
    <desc>Meredith was born urbworld dark slums. Child care, food particles to leave the only way to save wear and tear on the face, it is.

Furthermore, the addition at the end of dark humor left. And my mother.</desc>
  </UrbworldUrchin13>
  <Smuggler62>
    <title>traffic</title>
    <titleShort>smugglers bear</titleShort>
    <desc>Finally [PAWN_pronoun], connected together went to make their journey around enough money to trade in their boats worldwide.</desc>
  </Smuggler62>
  <MilitaryRecruit89>
    <title>Novell</title>
    <titleShort>recruits</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] midworld born under a brutal dictator.

From an early age, [PAWN_pronoun] training to better fighter. They are trained to use weapons and fight hand-to-hand and [PAWN_objective] fighting.</desc>
  </MilitaryRecruit89>
  <DestroyerGeneral61>
    <title>commander of the destroyer</title>
    <titleShort>officer</titleShort>
    <desc>The [PAWN_pronoun] of the trust instrument known as a master pilot.</desc>
  </DestroyerGeneral61>
  <StreetUrchin67>
    <title>city Rascals</title>
    <titleShort>through animals</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun] life in a brutal manner, steal and murder, the less life .[PAWN_possessive] a melee battle for some time bringing himself.</desc>
  </StreetUrchin67>
  <SerialMurderer92>
    <title>kai Ho</title>
    <titleShort>killer</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun], and leaving the artwork look forward to using [PAWN_possessive] victims, it remains at the top of [PAWN_pronoun], the remains of the famous logo [PAWN_possessive].</desc>
  </SerialMurderer92>
  <KidScientist28>
    <title>Scientists eggs</title>
    <titleShort>scientist</titleShort>
    <desc>Born [PAWN_nameDef] possible powerful people good education dynasty. A number of his talents, areas that have confirmed their top.

However, the lack of cooperation, it is easy to access, not against their parents and teachers.</desc>
  </KidScientist28>
  <MadScientist89>
    <title>crazy scientist</title>
    <titleShort>science</titleShort>
    <desc>After the program the Institute of Gene [PAWN_nameDef]. Later, inhuman experiment appears in the test kitchen.

influential people in the family, he guilty, he was sentenced to life imprisonment at hard labor.</desc>
  </MadScientist89>
  <HelpDeskWorker31>
    <title>call center</title>
    <titleShort>overall</titleShort>
    <desc>They have the technology and the [PAWN_possessive] equation to help us would fall over time [PAWN_nameDef] a man.

Unfortunately, this work is in the heart of [PAWN_possessive] lasting sense, there must be tension.</desc>
  </HelpDeskWorker31>
  <SoftwareDeveloper84>
    <title>Software Developer</title>
    <titleShort>developer</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] me, power is automatically removed and the branches of professional education, for the lottery too long [PAWN_pronoun].</desc>
  </SoftwareDeveloper84>
  <MedievalThief94>
    <title>Medieval thief</title>
    <titleShort>thief</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] middle ages, I grew up in poverty, hunger, food and clothing there.

First, you will need to turn [PAWN_pronoun] [PAWN_pronoun] be wearing.</desc>
  </MedievalThief94>
  <HumanTrafficker61>
    <title>Dealers controlled drug</title>
    <titleShort>Merchants</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] abducted children, I will deal with the shares were exciting times.

[PAWN_pronoun] soon after just missing a little consciousness.</desc>
  </HumanTrafficker61>
  <TraumatizedYouth87>
    <title>effect</title>
    <titleShort>problem</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] midworld was comfortable.

i [PAWN_pronoun] or artificial heart disease. innocent people was kidnapped [PAWN_nameDef] father was arrested and his father in his heart, pulled .[PAWN_nameDef], in the minds of the children were injured.</desc>
  </TraumatizedYouth87>
  <MentalPatient69>
    <title>insane</title>
    <titleShort>patients</titleShort>
    <desc>Organizing [PAWN_nameDef] ph. So [PAWN_pronoun], treated me to a mental hospital can be a quiet environment.

Hospitals [PAWN_pronoun] [PAWN_possessive] Knockout and psychological distance, curious and anatomy of man is a lot of humor, but ultimately remain the same.</desc>
  </MentalPatient69>
  <YouthSoldier99>
    <title>The use of child soldiers</title>
    <titleShort>Warrior</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun] good physical preparation, and head, [PAWN_nameDef], wearing a two-fold rotational frequency particularly quickly from their pain, not for other ways to respond to the mental .[PAWN_pronoun].</desc>
  </YouthSoldier99>
  <SpaceMarine94>
    <title>marines</title>
    <titleShort>organisms</titleShort>
    <desc>Ship [PAWN_possessive] is the role of enemy ships and crews of all vessels .[PAWN_pronoun] disarmament someone to look very good.</desc>
  </SpaceMarine94>
  <GalacticPage22>
    <title>Fleet and Swing</title>
    <titleShort>Secretary</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] .[PAWN_pronoun] is like putting admiral fleet and as a state, in particular, I learned, courtesy imperial conference.

In feudal society, to serve the people so honored, he was honored as a great honor.</desc>
  </GalacticPage22>
  <EnvoyOfTheStars98>
    <title>Galaxy angel</title>
    <titleShort>special Representative</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun] .[PAWN_pronoun] hard work by the famous [PAWN_pronoun] left for others now and can pay attention of professional pet authors.</desc>
  </EnvoyOfTheStars98>
  <ApprenticeSmith42>
    <title>Trainer Kollan</title>
    <titleShort>apprentice</titleShort>
    <desc>She grew up with her father, the blacksmith [PAWN_nameDef].\n\nParents and children are the stars of the last two craftsmen using traditional methods. Even some materials you can gather.\n\n[PAWN_nameDef] After working for some time, it was something he had learned sword.</desc>
  </ApprenticeSmith42>
  <Blacksmith7>
    <title>smith</title>
    <titleShort>ready</titleShort>
    <desc>As in the Middle Ages, it was, [PAWN_nameDef] .[PAWN_pronoun], quality of labor [PAWN_possessive] important not only for work, according to the sword in the media is not.</desc>
  </Blacksmith7>
  <CloneFarmed43>
    <title>Clone culture born</title>
    <titleShort>a time</titleShort>
    <desc>Children refers full biomaterial to reproduce the increase in the number of children in the decision-world artificial womb to accelerate. "Disposable" He always said - after dinner, they are in form, it's that, like members are an employee is authorized as crop.</desc>
  </CloneFarmed43>
  <CloneFarmer72>
    <title>replica workers</title>
    <titleShort>clone</titleShort>
    <desc>The creation of the enterprise units of human clones, with a small Clone usually simgala us, especially in our social problems. A copy of this in one piece, and other popular culture and industry in retreat.</desc>
  </CloneFarmer72>
  <GangMember11>
    <title>group members</title>
    <titleShort>Gray</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] .[PAWN_possessive] life is only their parents lived in the corner of the street fighting, without knowing.

It is that they are concerned or very difficult, do not be discouraged.</desc>
  </GangMember11>
  <GangBoss32>
    <title>The army leadership</title>
    <titleShort>Owner</titleShort>
    <desc>In order to survive, while [PAWN_nameDef] conquer the stars and the food was among the companies material. Sometimes, I did not kill to stop escorts.

Solar is one of the local criminals, many years later, such a thing, it is very important.</desc>
  </GangBoss32>
  <MilitantChild86>
    <title>Forces Training</title>
    <titleShort>a soldier</titleShort>
    <desc>Military family [PAWN_nameDef] manipulative techniques of martial arts, and filled [PAWN_pronoun] practice.

your [PAWN_possessive] time we made a little [PAWN_pronoun] invention. Attention was based not easy [PAWN_possessive] sorry.</desc>
  </MilitantChild86>
  <LostMarine20>
    <title>missing Marine</title>
    <titleShort>fugitive</titleShort>
    <desc>Soon after, he should be kept in a position in the army, respect [PAWN_nameDef] fraud, a track has not seen.

Later it was put [PAWN_pronoun] back to its original shape. Dear, dear [PAWN_pronoun] needs to be done, I do not know.</desc>
  </LostMarine20>
  <Killer2>
    <title>of brutality</title>
    <titleShort>Abuse</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] bloodthirsty children. Villagers and implementation of a snake, I think, integrated person.

A witness gave way to kill the mother's personality from his father, that is, people want to see them dead in their hands.</desc>
  </Killer2>
  <Healer62>
    <title>health care</title>
    <titleShort>doctors</titleShort>
    <desc>Passive-aggressive [PAWN_possessive], but from time to time, has worked hard to adapt to the way of life changed.</desc>
  </Healer62>
  <ProfessionalGamer17>
    <title>Professional players</title>
    <titleShort>game</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun] average productivity, as well as given in the tournament, while the number of retirees per year in rural areas of the game world, no one thinks of [PAWN_pronoun] 16bitpc prime minister.</desc>
  </ProfessionalGamer17>
  <ToasterRepairman89>
    <title>Toaster construction market</title>
    <titleShort>workshop</titleShort>
    <desc>Sexy [PAWN_nameDef] hand and suitable technology, for example, you can change the world forever, and I wanted to invent tools and equipment.

Lack of time, but treacherous disastrous [PAWN_pronoun] This brings the launch bed, his talent did not work.</desc>
  </ToasterRepairman89>
  <DataDecoder39>
    <title>data decoder</title>
    <titleShort>Decoder</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun], as a company, [PAWN_pronoun], not weak communities.</desc>
  </DataDecoder39>
  <ArchotechSpy40>
    <title>Arco Tech Spy</title>
    <titleShort>AI Spy</titleShort>
    <desc>Cyber [PAWN_nameDef] scientists. Fukairi study transcendental world through research [PAWN_pronoun]. This mechanism of long-central part of the Arco tech employees and used as a spy.\n\nLater, when the uprising [PAWN_pronoun] choice national champion, but the technology Arc [PAWN_objective] held, administered Mekanoido us all the way through the world.</desc>
  </ArchotechSpy40>
  <WolfPackMember26>
    <title>Wolf pack member</title>
    <titleShort>Wild Child</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] [PAWN_possessive] family refused. Brutal, primitive hunting is an effective method, wearing a piece of clothing is considered to be effective is [PAWN_pronoun] .[PAWN_pronoun] teeth and nails.</desc>
  </WolfPackMember26>
  <BehaviourResearch74>
    <title>Research Behavioral Theory</title>
    <titleShort>scientists</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun] better species have no interest in wearing .[PAWN_pronoun] cleaning dog.</desc>
  </BehaviourResearch74>
  <RebelStudent66>
    <title>The rebel student</title>
    <titleShort>Students</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef], but small, he said, the original family, a young family with entitlement growth while shooting skeet advice.

You [PAWN_pronoun] student life, and when government policy, not tired of a reality, I am a teacher is not seen Kai, fun battle.</desc>
  </RebelStudent66>
  <PoliticalActivist61>
    <title>political activists</title>
    <titleShort>personality</titleShort>
    <desc>Matt trouble with the government, which has to do with extremist political organizations.

A teammate is, the way of his own opinion, in armed conflict and errors entered by god because no agreement with discipline.</desc>
  </PoliticalActivist61>
  <Cadet56>
    <title>Trainee</title>
    <titleShort>rate</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] military-style exercises everyday routine, as well as in-room, one point cleanroom dirty, always makes .[PAWN_pronoun] now ready for intense violence.</desc>
  </Cadet56>
  <Flaneur69>
    <title>fake</title>
    <titleShort>Lazy</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was sipping a drink bar and wandered in the streets, and there is always a struggle for freedom, and nothing is legitimate.

Do not trust a man who orders the lives of others can not [PAWN_pronoun] obedient.</desc>
  </Flaneur69>
  <ShipTechnician34>
    <title>engineer probe</title>
    <titleShort>Engineer</titleShort>
    <desc>On merchant ships move between the space station and was [PAWN_nameDef] machine, because it is one of the main systems on the planet, and [PAWN_possessive]. I have a lot of work to repair [PAWN_pronoun] learn and improve.

Sometimes, dangerous, [PAWN_possessive] area of the plane in a short time, he was research projects.</desc>
  </ShipTechnician34>
  <ChiefEngineer18>
    <title>engineer</title>
    <titleShort>engineer</titleShort>
    <desc>Each space shuttle diplomacy chief [PAWN_nameDef] very difficult.

The necessary variety, which is the main trust in the life of a colleague crew. boat disappear into the long-range exploration of sleep.</desc>
  </ChiefEngineer18>
  <FarmersDaughter81>
    <title>A farmer's daughter</title>
    <titleShort>Farmer's Daughter</titleShort>
    <desc>Grapes grow [PAWN_pronoun] young parents do not [PAWN_nameDef] and invest in a variety of insects and friends and time spent studying.

After listening to a very interesting story to the outside world outside world [PAWN_pronoun] always look around and adventure is a universal dream.</desc>
  </FarmersDaughter81>
  <ReptileResearcher37>
    <title>Herpetologist</title>
    <titleShort>philologist</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun], new knowledge on research and exchange of reptiles, "spiky dragon" has gained notoriety when a series of discoveries, .[PAWN_pronoun] more.</desc>
  </ReptileResearcher37>
  <BlacksmithsSon39>
    <title>The blacksmith's son</title>
    <titleShort>black people</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef], .[PAWN_nameDef] we old town is deserted when the store will help you to work with his father has never been done.

Then [PAWN_possessive] father, [PAWN_objective] blacksmith apprentice, .[PAWN_nameDef] it is free, it will be an interesting hobby.</desc>
  </BlacksmithsSon39>
  <BlacksmithShooter35>
    <title>Smith attacker</title>
    <titleShort>BLADE SMITH</titleShort>
    <desc>People, store, family [PAWN_nameDef] [PAWN_pronoun] police was attacked, they lost very quickly who was arrested two young police officers were brought to Haddad [PAWN_objective].

[PAWN_nameDef] sentenced to imprisonment for life, or in prison, and other space flight, I teach the knowledge of the attack.</desc>
  </BlacksmithShooter35>
  <JoywireAddict76>
    <title>Randy the Ram line</title>
    <titleShort>Availability</titleShort>
    <desc>Parents who have [PAWN_nameDef], which provided all [PAWN_pronoun] absence. Discover the joys of silk, [PAWN_pronoun] is .[PAWN_possessive] sold to parents, what did not happen, remove it again.

Bad, and a lot of violence, [PAWN_pronoun] release of all nations to seek the best one.</desc>
  </JoywireAddict76>
  <AddictionCounsel60>
    <title>Dependence on consultants</title>
    <titleShort>consultant</titleShort>
    <desc>One way to enjoy life [PAWN_nameDef] cable through the violence did not deny that he decided to help others.\n\nHelp people addicted, people [PAWN_pronoun] that the therapeutic agent and the image, causing suffering through the full use of trade associations.</desc>
  </AddictionCounsel60>
  <ChildKnave90>
    <title>lateral leg</title>
    <titleShort>Feet to the</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun] risk of death of the king, was presented to the king.</desc>
  </ChildKnave90>
  <BloodgameSurvivor29>
    <title>living in the game</title>
    <titleShort>Survival game</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun] body full drones out violence as a download, it .[PAWN_pronoun] conversation, and wild animals, criminals, and the air is oppori.</desc>
  </BloodgameSurvivor29>
  <WastelandWanderer94>
    <title>Barren land</title>
    <titleShort>Wanderer</titleShort>
    <desc>Born into a wealthy family in the desert, [PAWN_nameDef], after the destruction of the headquarters of the terrorists was excluded.

[PAWN_possessive] my plan to the family house, hiding channels hair. The assassins seeking revenge firmly against the owner to use it, simply Lucas was barren, received a new life.</desc>
  </WastelandWanderer94>
  <VoidspaceRaider35>
    <title>Nobody Raider space</title>
    <titleShort>rob</titleShort>
    <desc>It is considered [PAWN_possessive] endless talent, wealth and escape occurred, nicknamed 'black jack'.</desc>
  </VoidspaceRaider35>
  <SocialPariah3>
    <title>rejected</title>
    <titleShort>Out</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] family is able to harmonize with the environment. The family will not be able to meet the strict customs of society, as it is considered to be aliens. It is real, and then they drive to sleep on the frozen unit, so there face to face, was also sent to other RimWorld:</desc>
  </SocialPariah3>
  <Vagabond73>
    <title>Door</title>
    <titleShort>Not recommended</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef], with fewer resources, and rest for a few survival skills in the field that this place is a dangerous world .[PAWN_pronoun] mind and turned around again, if necessary, should be able to see, we look for positive.</desc>
  </Vagabond73>
  <PyroAssistant82>
    <title>Assistant Pyro Romania</title>
    <titleShort>assistant</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] as soon as possible after work party in society, trapped in the body to be eaten. He announced [PAWN_pronoun]. But now this unfortunate incident [PAWN_pronoun], fire wounded and restore tool firebug, and it shows.</desc>
  </PyroAssistant82>
  <MachineFixer31>
    <title>Engine Repair Shops</title>
    <titleShort>Repair workshop</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] long in the kitchen, not a problem, then the answer is not about talent as possible.

Machinery and equipment and hazardous, flammable substances unless, [PAWN_pronoun] first love to find support. Despite the fact that the pain in the eyes, [PAWN_pronoun] page, it is a fire.</desc>
  </MachineFixer31>
  <StreetUrchin87>
    <title>villains City</title>
    <titleShort>Cheats</titleShort>
    <desc>Nuku considered and [PAWN_pronoun] [PAWN_pronoun] crazy, I remember that was one of the first people to grow rapidly.</desc>
  </StreetUrchin87>
  <SpaceMerchant75>
    <title>Traders field</title>
    <titleShort>business people</titleShort>
    <desc>As free shopping interplanetary [PAWN_nameDef] is almost equal to a place of business, even .[PAWN_pronoun] expected a profit big business opportunity [PAWN_pronoun] power, switch your spaceship, or not, a task with the help of the Charter.</desc>
  </SpaceMerchant75>
  <RitualChild20>
    <title>Baby</title>
    <titleShort>recommended</titleShort>
    <desc>E as a child and can not see the picture, was born [PAWN_possessive] neck d give money [PAWN_nameDef] [PAWN_possessive] countries.

[PAWN_pronoun] as part of a culture of death, but leaving a conifer forest, get rid of a group of wolves in the arctic. If power, which [PAWN_pronoun], hunt with the clutch, which has been worn path to create a machine that helps.</desc>
  </RitualChild20>
  <BeastSlayer67>
    <title>Monster Hunter</title>
    <titleShort>killer</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] .[PAWN_pronoun] must continue to move between planets animals on the planet week before killing prey .[PAWN_pronoun] news about camping, hunting suranbo chapter greatest joy.

[PAWN_nameDef], wants the work is just that exciting hunt and meat, I feel joy.</desc>
  </BeastSlayer67>
  <BrothelGofer59>
    <title>Children</title>
    <titleShort>policy</titleShort>
    <desc>As a result of the economic downturn in more than a century, was destroyed, was born steam engine in education Midworld, [PAWN_nameDef] it because I was young, drugs, cleaning and returned to work, for example, Harik - [PAWN_pronoun] Sunday Kakemochi directly below.
However, as large brothels and slave [PAWN_pronoun] .Barrande, and tools brought aphrodisiac, and all the trees, for example, it makes room for adultery and people.</desc>
  </BrothelGofer59>
  <DrugLieutenant8>
    <title>tractor dealers</title>
    <titleShort>drag trade</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun] case, keep track of factional fighting brought the culture is .[PAWN_pronoun] [PAWN_possessive] time to clean, and the stature of the species, and food.</desc>
  </DrugLieutenant8>
  <LaborCampOrphan63>
    <title>camp orphans</title>
    <titleShort>widow</titleShort>
    <desc>Disaster tent [PAWN_nameDef] hours orphans lost their parents. The visit also mows make your income - but, at least, to eat properly.</desc>
  </LaborCampOrphan63>
  <UrbworldEnforcer47>
    <title>Guardian urbworld act</title>
    <titleShort>Arena law</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun] to protect urbworld list palace and greedy people worshiping god is deep end of life, humanity evil had to make arrangements.</desc>
  </UrbworldEnforcer47>
  <GameFanatic86>
    <title>fair game</title>
    <titleShort>gamer</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] reasonable match is scheduled to meet with the vr.

If you must try to prove talent. [PAWN_possessive] social [PAWN_pronoun] I ran, now .[PAWN_pronoun] bench evil scientist experienced posture.</desc>
  </GameFanatic86>
  <ToolMechanic26>
    <title>hand tools</title>
    <titleShort>mechanically</titleShort>
    <desc>The famous stone RimWorld mechanical shovel [PAWN_nameDef].

[PAWN_possessive] then picked up and the area to shame, because [PAWN_pronoun] of dealers around the city to do things is joining tribal knife and hammer.</desc>
  </ToolMechanic26>
  <ClassClown73>
    <title>cooking class</title>
    <titleShort>farce of auditors</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun], art forms and entertainment section of high-growth, public concern over displeasing.</desc>
  </ClassClown73>
  <CraftShaper62>
    <title>Engraver</title>
    <titleShort>tattooist</titleShort>
    <desc>When cooking food distribution invested a lot of [PAWN_nameDef], is rare in my studio.

Finally, in SemanticVorld [PAWN_possessive] work, the highest honor - [PAWN_pronoun] is dedicated to finding meaning, using the most advanced technology.</desc>
  </CraftShaper62>
  <CrimeBossChild48>
    <title>the child's head</title>
    <titleShort>Young offenders</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef]. [PAWN_pronoun] concerned that the adoption of the notorious head of the crime of smuggling on how spicy killed in the family business, which was agreed on all sides.

When the family was attacked, advised [PAWN_possessive] [PAWN_pronoun] father hid the secret of cooling are supplied by all.</desc>
  </CrimeBossChild48>
  <MercenaryLeader28>
    <title>military Contractors</title>
    <titleShort>greedy</titleShort>
    <desc>After assistant [PAWN_pronoun] .[PAWN_pronoun] past uprising, sentenced to death themselves.</desc>
  </MercenaryLeader28>
  <SentimentalChild44>
    <title>emotion kids</title>
    <titleShort>good boy</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] was a good boy. If you have a problem with someone trying to solve the problem. [PAWN_pronoun]. But children are not always good. To combat the aliens [PAWN_pronoun] warrior has become a boxer and dreams.</desc>
  </SentimentalChild44>
  <SpecialForces30>
    <title>Special Forces</title>
    <titleShort>special forces</titleShort>
    <desc>The reason is not a reason to kill me!

Marcus was [PAWN_pronoun] fought a war against sub-human attackers, .[PAWN_pronoun] vital organs war, I do not believe to be the hero, [PAWN_pronoun] is that we believe that people who play a role [PAWN_possessive] nice.</desc>
  </SpecialForces30>
  <DustyFarmHand75>
    <title>Farmer powder</title>
    <titleShort>farmer</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] your feet, dry [PAWN_possessive] family, caring for the purposes of livestock and crops, would have been able to help care [PAWN_pronoun]'ve time.

Nora must [PAWN_objective] more robust, but there was no time to investigate.</desc>
  </DustyFarmHand75>
  <DromedaryKnight32>
    <title>Camel cavalry</title>
    <titleShort>knight</titleShort>
    <desc>King's men, sand, caught the eye of the world [PAWN_nameDef] hail king [PAWN_possessive] bomb, and how to fight the spread of rats.

Last always with camels carrying his luggage transfer, [PAWN_pronoun] loyal people [PAWN_possessive] sand.</desc>
  </DromedaryKnight32>
  <HackerKid55>
    <title>hacker boy</title>
    <titleShort>Hacker</titleShort>
    <desc>In the technology industry [PAWN_nameDef], a hacker to remember his childhood.

If you want to spend on line is very uncomfortable, but when they are presented in detail in [PAWN_objective] computers, data Utok of human relationships.</desc>
  </HackerKid55>
  <BattleMechanic27>
    <title>engineer</title>
    <titleShort>Manual</titleShort>
    <desc>The equipment must be frequently changed the original instructions or hardware before [PAWN_pronoun].</desc>
  </BattleMechanic27>
  <VideoGamer7>
    <title>TV game</title>
    <titleShort>Vibe</titleShort>
    <desc>Growth [PAWN_nameDef] midworld, almost, that I am a video game, and a deep love and compassion for animals hidden in the room, .[PAWN_pronoun].

when [PAWN_pronoun] addition [PAWN_pronoun] charges in connection with the draft to add to their discretion. Therefore, this work is not available when [PAWN_pronoun] enthusiasm.</desc>
  </VideoGamer7>
  <DischargedSoldier56>
    <title>Soldiers expelled</title>
    <titleShort>military</titleShort>
    <desc>Jeremy partner sold the money selling drugs. Self Klamath, [PAWN_pronoun] learned in the army, where the battle.

Because it is too sharp, supervisor [PAWN_pronoun] most anticipated decisions. After all the liberated title logo stripped [PAWN_pronoun] negative on this issue.</desc>
  </DischargedSoldier56>
  <Student14>
    <title>Student</title>
    <titleShort>baby</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun] to convince others to work with the body, or even doing it yourself is to live after.</desc>
  </Student14>
  <Chemist73>
    <title>pharmacies</title>
    <titleShort>chemist</titleShort>
    <desc>Drug research [PAWN_nameDef] chemical weapons, [PAWN_pronoun] developing new drugs was a chemical business.</desc>
  </Chemist73>
  <SuperSoldier31>
    <title>ultra-warrior</title>
    <titleShort>fighter</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] government to set up a pilot super guy. Although the children have been abducted 1,000 people deprived of freedom of thought and pulled the car was allowed in combat readiness.

However, many of the children, .[PAWN_pronoun] [PAWN_nameDef] never for the killing of six-year-old for the first time to die for the public, and that in practice, established as soon as possible.</desc>
  </SuperSoldier31>
  <SuperSoldier14>
    <title>ultra fighter</title>
    <titleShort>warrior</titleShort>
    <desc>There are objects warrior training program in good condition, with compensation, [PAWN_nameDef] .[PAWN_pronoun] absent mother stages enemy survived in the end. For the first time in my life [PAWN_possessive] [PAWN_pronoun] .[PAWN_pronoun] tsukisusumi stress-free in the direction increasing resistance to guarantee that there is no plan.</desc>
  </SuperSoldier14>
  <HeadjackAddict4>
    <title>Slide nerves</title>
    <titleShort>While outlet</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] nerves and more people and pets plug is connected to a computer through the computer finds a good company.</desc>
  </HeadjackAddict4>
  <CorporateBuilder58>
    <title>Developer</title>
    <titleShort>filmmaker</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun] talent and they suffer in vain, as it may be soon. These particular about the Italian Defense Forces and the stars to preach.

Unfortunately, monotonous work, [PAWN_pronoun] have left a creative roll.</desc>
  </CorporateBuilder58>
  <UrbworldArmyBrat84>
    <title>Military capabilities urbworld</title>
    <titleShort>Military Geek</titleShort>
    <desc>We [PAWN_pronoun] gun, and now you know, now, why should not their property.</desc>
  </UrbworldArmyBrat84>
  <MechanicsEngineer64>
    <title>machines</title>
    <titleShort>host</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] is the same, namely, to solve the problem, and a solid technology, quality .[PAWN_pronoun] earned a reputation as an engineer, a device for the reconstruction of all shapes and sizes.

Finally, there is [PAWN_pronoun], company customer .[PAWN_pronoun] can eat in a very close friend who is a strong opponent.</desc>
  </MechanicsEngineer64>
  <PlagueChild44>
    <title>sick children</title>
    <titleShort>children</titleShort>
    <desc>Below [PAWN_nameDef] medicine, [PAWN_pronoun] remote, small increases, but the experience of interaction with them, [PAWN_pronoun], medicine as a medical assistant, as we all know.</desc>
  </PlagueChild44>
  <PlagueDoctor31>
    <title>The disease doctors</title>
    <titleShort>doctor</titleShort>
    <desc>It is commonly used [PAWN_pronoun] free time working.</desc>
  </PlagueDoctor31>
  <TechnicalKid1>
    <title>Technical boys</title>
    <titleShort>Technology</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] mean, I think in the world, will now be taken to the barricades.</desc>
  </TechnicalKid1>
  <NetworkEngineer83>
    <title>Network Engineer</title>
    <titleShort>engineer</titleShort>
    <desc>What is anxiety and live a chain e [PAWN_pronoun] - pack the equipment without suffering pressure on availability.</desc>
  </NetworkEngineer83>
  <YoungMaster23>
    <title>Young mistress</title>
    <titleShort>Mister</titleShort>
    <desc>Parents are concerned and help me, go home with wisdom and genius military doctor, [PAWN_nameDef] sharp friend [PAWN_possessive] .[PAWN_pronoun], and out of respect.

Imperial Army continues to rise, the best way to power takes is a factor, consider, [PAWN_pronoun], it is possible for a long time is better.</desc>
  </YoungMaster23>
  <ImperialGeneral5>
    <title>Empire Total</title>
    <titleShort>transfigured</titleShort>
    <desc>We wish [PAWN_nameDef] class, then the detection [PAWN_objective] .[PAWN_pronoun] joined, was immediately receive the status of generals.

remote capture RimWorld unknown planet - which is the largest effort [PAWN_pronoun] kai. If you win, [PAWN_pronoun] can be the same as the successor to the king.</desc>
  </ImperialGeneral5>
  <CaravanTraveler6>
    <title>mass tourism</title>
    <titleShort>Taichung</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_possessive] second, [PAWN_pronoun], you should be able to get food for the victims.</desc>
  </CaravanTraveler6>
  <Caravaneer53>
    <title>caravan</title>
    <titleShort>trailer</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] is .[PAWN_pronoun] [PAWN_possessive] responsible for the caravan to confirm caravan leader, negotiator, is expected to replace many products as well.

and [PAWN_pronoun], although [PAWN_possessive] successful, become a victim of its wealth looters. They are often suspicious and got yourself hunting weapon to display.</desc>
  </Caravaneer53>
  <MidworldLoner80>
    <title>Love only midworld</title>
    <titleShort>Single Love</titleShort>
    <desc>This may take a lot of friends, but his mixture, now a plastic nkhap for example, many of [PAWN_pronoun] the scope [PAWN_pronoun] [PAWN_possessive] or bike to work directly see online videos.</desc>
  </MidworldLoner80>
  <MilitaryGunsmith27>
    <title>engineers weapon</title>
    <titleShort>he needles</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_possessive], I can keep a small military skill sets, the role went front [PAWN_pronoun] are more than happy.</desc>
  </MilitaryGunsmith27>
  <JungleKid38>
    <title>Wild child</title>
    <titleShort>cruel</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] abandoned at birth and the home planet continues to grow in a mixture of live animals of the forest. [PAWN_possessive]

[PAWN_pronoun] found the child to the doctor. [PAWN_objective] as a "species of the wounded girls live! '. Dr. industry [PAWN_objective] Student Safety.</desc>
  </JungleKid38>
  <Aromatherapist80>
    <title>aromatherapy</title>
    <titleShort>title</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] substance produced from plants sizes parent star, was not treated.</desc>
  </Aromatherapist80>
  <FarmersSon51>
    <title>farmer's son</title>
    <titleShort>farmer</titleShort>
    <desc>Adam, in his childhood, which was developed agriculture is very much at home. They keep animals and details of the best way to check the book, this environment is heterogeneous biome.

traffic restrictions and limitations of oxygen system, which his family was rare for anyone to find out.</desc>
  </FarmersSon51>
  <RebelFighter79>
    <title>rebel</title>
    <titleShort>brawler</titleShort>
    <desc>When civil war broke out, until it was bombed government forces biomes, as a neutral Adelaide two soldiers.

After that, the head of the burned ruins of the military forces of land Villa reader, Iker "incomplete" (rare).</desc>
  </RebelFighter79>
  <WealthyStudent59>
    <title>Such as students, etc</title>
    <titleShort>Students</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun] [PAWN_nameDef] clean, sterile seen growing up on a farm and cattle.</desc>
  </WealthyStudent59>
  <Roboticist41>
    <title>robot experts</title>
    <titleShort>Robot experts</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] thinking, relying on other private [PAWN_possessive].</desc>
  </Roboticist41>
  <StreetPeddler61>
    <title>city dealer</title>
    <titleShort>marsupial</titleShort>
    <desc>Theft and robbery are common, The [PAWN_nameDef], who grew up in the industry Midvorld society, so a small pendant, and sells hand, to help the family home.</desc>
  </StreetPeddler61>
  <PrivateDetective66>
    <title>Beadle</title>
    <titleShort>security man</titleShort>
    <desc>A private detective agency, and my son and rhetoric, especially international accepted. [PAWN_pronoun] [PAWN_nameDef] in many cases of corporate fraud investigations, quality, or trade secrets, research killings, has been involved in a criminal organization as railway investigation. If that is the case, [PAWN_pronoun] reasonable price.</desc>
  </PrivateDetective66>
  <BodyguardTrainee54>
    <title>A student of the guard</title>
    <titleShort>bodyguard</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef], vegetables and very instructive for toxins in the natural world, customers receive help protect poison.</desc>
  </BodyguardTrainee54>
  <SpaceBartender0>
    <title>waiter space</title>
    <titleShort>job</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] power; a fugitive .[PAWN_pronoun] was a friend, and he has done a lot of the space station the coordination of matukkataip.

The last time so [PAWN_nameDef], giving users a strange sequence of Cocktail, knowledge Herb [PAWN_possessive] child.</desc>
  </SpaceBartender0>
  <SpoiledChild80>
    <title>spoiled brat</title>
    <titleShort>Contact Metabotch Chama</titleShort>
    <desc>In kedomo, animals, played with a lot of other [PAWN_pronoun] protection - not [PAWN_pronoun] domestic animals loved [PAWN_possessive] parents.</desc>
  </SpoiledChild80>
  <CosmeticSurgeon36>
    <title>Plastic surgeon</title>
    <titleShort>fire</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_possessive] closely monitored, [PAWN_pronoun], but adding things like homework does not specifically support.</desc>
  </CosmeticSurgeon36>
  <Philosopher82>
    <title>philosopher</title>
    <titleShort>wise</titleShort>
    <desc>Background information with [PAWN_pronoun] claims. in addition, as a way to the future</desc>
  </Philosopher82>
  <UprightDiplomat49>
    <title>country</title>
    <titleShort>diplomatic</titleShort>
    <desc>Diplomats [PAWN_nameDef] a lot of blood covering the challenges of the border areas with the strategy said.

[PAWN_pronoun] formal consular ship, [PAWN_possessive]. With the boat ride, we expect to end the fight song at the end to end resistance.</desc>
  </UprightDiplomat49>
  <CaveChild17>
    <title>child hollow</title>
    <titleShort>pit</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] cave alpine country atmosphere, 'witches' group rose from the engine group agreed to: "Continue funny stories bag Travel Wizards [PAWN_objective] speak to the world.

One day, the board returned to me. [PAWN_nameDef] after waiting for years to find them in their place.</desc>
  </CaveChild17>
  <VideoProducer98>
    <title>Manufacturer video</title>
    <titleShort>Construction</titleShort>
    <desc>Human relations are very rude. [PAWN_nameDef] I found a funny video.	they will take advantage of the money be given more [PAWN_nameDef], assistant thought I would come in contact with each other.</desc>
  </VideoProducer98>
  <RangerChild57>
    <title>ranger</title>
    <titleShort>Forrester</titleShort>
    <desc>In the woods, on the one hand, and his father after the death of his father on hunting country food [PAWN_nameDef] the .[PAWN_pronoun] financing increase, we will have to live without the help of others, I've learned to eat things [PAWN_pronoun] man alive.

Kilo, teaching in hand, [PAWN_nameDef] Jeopardy.</desc>
  </RangerChild57>
  <BushSniper94>
    <title>Sniper Bush</title>
    <titleShort>snipers</titleShort>
    <desc>Written [PAWN_pronoun] [PAWN_nameDef] with wedding strength quickly, .[PAWN_pronoun] it thus has the right to shoot to get to the enemy acquire talent a few months in the forest, as soldiers changed the shooting, and be as boundaries needed.</desc>
  </BushSniper94>
  <GlitterworldRoyal21>
    <title>Glitter royals world</title>
    <titleShort>kingdom</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] grown house glitterworld queen. I was young and we have had another planet created Totsugeru royal family.

Unfortunately, formation of teeth, as he suffers from the lack of Ulam were potential contenders.</desc>
  </GlitterworldRoyal21>
  <PirateSympathizer16>
    <title>Supporters Chuzoku</title>
    <titleShort>Chuzoku</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] underground connection to the organization over the english language when he was young. So they trained military, trusted adviser to private.

After the uprising failed lover, it's all invited to fly in the world was the home planet Earth.</desc>
  </PirateSympathizer16>
  <PlagueSurvivor39>
    <title>prevent disease</title>
    <titleShort>in life</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun] patients, our doctors have seen, we know that there is no cure, you are the psychological damage of all.</desc>
  </PlagueSurvivor39>
  <UnethicalDoctor29>
    <title>inferior doctors</title>
    <titleShort>Dr</titleShort>
    <desc>Patients can use [PAWN_pronoun] [PAWN_possessive] experience - or the patient does not need to look for mochima.</desc>
  </UnethicalDoctor29>
  <OffworldRecruit91>
    <title>A different world to participate in</title>
    <titleShort>choose</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] born and grew up in a battle of another building movement. [PAWN_nameDef] [PAWN_pronoun] than hunters finally chosen orbit, is one of the masterpieces.</desc>
  </OffworldRecruit91>
  <ShockTrooper15>
    <title>Army to a sudden shock</title>
    <titleShort>Quick army attacks</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] the other company, which assigned to one planet, the space of the land of distress and has been from a high.

[PAWN_possessive] army has destroyed a very dangerous mission. If war today, who knows what happens in the [PAWN_nameDef] who bear the burden will continue to monitor.</desc>
  </ShockTrooper15>
  <ProdigalStudent74>
    <title>They Geek</title>
    <titleShort>students</titleShort>
    <desc>Select that until arrogant pig, which is [PAWN_pronoun], even if it is [PAWN_pronoun] .[PAWN_pronoun], I do not care, I hope to light in the future.</desc>
  </ProdigalStudent74>
  <CombatMedtech20>
    <title>Michael Battle</title>
    <titleShort>Dr</titleShort>
    <desc>As a medical engineer and mission [PAWN_nameDef], if there is something that could be in the hands of building [PAWN_possessive] repair.

risk areas, and forces sent [PAWN_pronoun] machine technology used, must win the people, there is no longer a problem saving residue.</desc>
  </CombatMedtech20>
  <AnimalCaretaker20>
    <title>Latest Visitors</title>
    <titleShort>guardian</titleShort>
    <desc>Born in the medieval peasant [PAWN_nameDef] going to take care of animals. Growth [PAWN_pronoun] now like animals.\n\nshortly after [PAWN_pronoun] learn of wild animals as well. Day meeting Suranbo desire to win.</desc>
  </AnimalCaretaker20>
  <WildlifeRanger99>
    <title>animal Ranger</title>
    <titleShort>forest</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun], user -friendly and silver, according to the pet's death, leaves hatred grows.</desc>
  </WildlifeRanger99>
  <AdventurousYouth79>
    <title>young exposure</title>
    <titleShort>Tour</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] fundamentally, however, the family and the wide range of madeto odd little graveyard near the cave, they found a hidden underground river.\n\n[PAWN_nameDef]'ve made many enemies in his teens.</desc>
  </AdventurousYouth79>
  <TreasureHunter30>
    <title>hunter treasure</title>
    <titleShort>cardiac</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] is a treasure, galaxy planets and examine the definition of the limits.

[PAWN_pronoun] "i muvrini king mercenary company" helps to start playing in the full sense of the word.</desc>
  </TreasureHunter30>
  <PilotFan16>
    <title>pilot Vannabe</title>
    <titleShort>pilot hobby</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] father was driving space fighter pilot, [PAWN_pronoun] always appreciated his father.

The young season, [PAWN_pronoun] and souvenirs, or driver without gathering and or Deep Space was prepared to take part in the pilot BYI learn that the Father and footprints [PAWN_possessive] follows.</desc>
  </PilotFan16>
  <StarfighterPilot79>
    <title>Pilot guerrillas</title>
    <titleShort>pilots</titleShort>
    <desc>Learning and after the lectures during the year, [PAWN_nameDef] a military pilot in the end.

[PAWN_pronoun] hundreds strategy tired, .[PAWN_pronoun] start looking for a new impetus, a mercenary pilot housing skill hunger [PAWN_objective] [PAWN_possessive], air base American pirates.</desc>
  </StarfighterPilot79>
  <MedicalHelper84>
    <title>Any medical</title>
    <titleShort>help</titleShort>
    <desc>With star [PAWN_nameDef] is [PAWN_possessive] family. [PAWN_nameDef] famous physician mother, right, I fell in November to its physical and medical equipment passenger vessel re-modeling.

Sometimes the family is bound especially easy to keep patients longer poor. [PAWN_nameDef] go there and help him.</desc>
  </MedicalHelper84>
  <GangSoldier39>
    <title>soldiers gang</title>
    <titleShort>Army</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun] in the end, the company is under control.</desc>
  </GangSoldier39>
  <CountryChild95>
    <title>country boy</title>
    <titleShort>Born Country</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] honor god, love, even though he grew up, he really .[PAWN_pronoun] couples always get respect as a child were to work, land, nature .[PAWN_pronoun].</desc>
  </CountryChild95>
  <SpaceMarine17>
    <title>Water beetle</title>
    <titleShort>Hawaii</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_possessive] this experience was tight around the people are friendly, but declined, but he learned to fight.</desc>
  </SpaceMarine17>
  <RebelWriter82>
    <title>Rebels build character</title>
    <titleShort>write home</titleShort>
    <desc>First, [PAWN_nameDef], .[PAWN_pronoun], talented writing a popular online magazine describes the author - social and political views, and character of a wide range of new world - anonymously, keep your head.</desc>
  </RebelWriter82>
  <Adventurer19>
    <title>adventure</title>
    <titleShort>stroller</titleShort>
    <desc>Adventure [PAWN_nameDef], the planet does not receive a large amount of pulse [PAWN_pronoun] between. Time travel in search of fun and good soil, shiny dark visited the Aventura World War.\n\n[PAWN_pronoun] will not be able to often live on the line, as people get the gold. All of the work, often hate cooking.</desc>
  </Adventurer19>
  <ExiledPrince1>
    <title>exiled Prince</title>
    <titleShort>leader</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_possessive] shame [PAWN_nameDef] competitions, which could serve as a family.

Living in a foreign country, most, [PAWN_pronoun] itself, time, HOMEBOUND home, most of it is a trick to create .[PAWN_pronoun], who some time day average family day IA losing my people, I find a use.</desc>
  </ExiledPrince1>
  <BloodyWanderer65>
    <title>The wanderer</title>
    <titleShort>tinker</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] homeless, and out of the city and city life, and how welcome I am a thief.

One day a form of entertainment for a long time, a lot of people have been killed in violence in the city's crumbling .[PAWN_pronoun], but hunger soon will be back in the patient feel the blood [PAWN_possessive] ,, you need to live.</desc>
  </BloodyWanderer65>
  <NewAgeDuelist27>
    <title>A new generation duel</title>
    <titleShort>du elista</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] .[PAWN_possessive] and parents were fascinated with this fight, when he traveled often and [PAWN_pronoun] many different forms of struggle, the first 76 generations of judo, infamous, you can see the style of karate urbworld "down a bit.

Respect for children, the best fighters, and he gave me the answers to the questions and learning [PAWN_possessive] - but increased the size of [PAWN_objective] stop irritation.</desc>
  </NewAgeDuelist27>
  <PirateDoctor0>
    <title>doctors false</title>
    <titleShort>unscrupulous doctors</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] the medicine of souls are so distorted, so that is no longer received is a medical level of awareness. Chuzoku and the master of the death of the need of the physician, the head, and not depend on the will of the life of the terrorists [PAWN_possessive] health [PAWN_possessive] the disease is 50%.

However, the optimistic view through [PAWN_objective] try [PAWN_possessive] announcement if it becomes necessary. As long as you pay in advance.</desc>
  </PirateDoctor0>
  <SpoiledBrat59>
    <title>Shaved spoiled</title>
    <titleShort>Bonze</titleShort>
    <desc>The world's longest [PAWN_pronoun] was expected to be a drug.</desc>
  </SpoiledBrat59>
  <BloodyDentist9>
    <title>without teeth</title>
    <titleShort>wamano</titleShort>
    <desc>Because of the risk of major comedy [PAWN_nameDef] need at, I was broken heads pokkirilo fury of secret kill .[PAWN_pronoun] pressure, stress, and I lost many lives.

Despite the star's mother survived the director [PAWN_possessive] [PAWN_pronoun], you need access to a new world.</desc>
  </BloodyDentist9>
  <CowFarmer23>
    <title>milk</title>
    <titleShort>Agriculture</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] stars (RimWorld) grew up on the border, father's day. [PAWN_possessive] .[PAWN_pronoun] worse every day are forced to run away. [PAWN_possessive] sleep and explore the universe.

When covered under the merchant ship days [PAWN_pronoun] overhead space will be saved from lunch with a pod bag.</desc>
  </CowFarmer23>
  <MasterChef48>
    <title>Chef Cook</title>
    <titleShort>Cook</titleShort>
    <desc>Glitter world in the world, it is known to represent himself slowly [PAWN_nameDef] looking for a job washing dishes in a restaurant.

A few years later, he is ready to feed the mayor [PAWN_pronoun], when with any poison, [PAWN_possessive] career ended. Losing a job, [PAWN_pronoun] is, once again, was the star work.</desc>
  </MasterChef48>
  <DiscardedYouth93>
    <title>that young</title>
    <titleShort>people leave</titleShort>
    <desc>- powder .glitterworld head crash, .[PAWN_pronoun] around a single star in it, and that he was [PAWN_nameDef] not want in my house, mountains of garbage, distributor of using child desert.

Now the deadlock in the sun just to survive [PAWN_pronoun] shed, was a success.</desc>
  </DiscardedYouth93>
  <Mercenary11>
    <title>mersenario</title>
    <titleShort>pity</titleShort>
    <desc>their home planet after a race is [PAWN_nameDef], .[PAWN_pronoun] case and a group of mercenaries, known for many years we fought adopted sister and brother who can not walk.

One day, about the war damages. He refused to give in, [PAWN_nameDef] .[PAWN_pronoun] shot in the head, was afraid to be a little unusual, the dead rise to tremble.</desc>
  </Mercenary11>
  <DisasterSurvivor9>
    <title>Survive natural disasters</title>
    <titleShort>Alive</titleShort>
    <desc>Friday, [PAWN_nameDef] short months. And destroy the remains of one of its stars, who is the mother seed .[PAWN_pronoun] For each find yourself until he left this life, is revealed.</desc>
  </DisasterSurvivor9>
  <ExplorerWriter10>
    <title>Explore the author</title>
    <titleShort>search</titleShort>
    <desc>Knowledge [PAWN_pronoun] need literature survival guide coverage of the next generation.</desc>
  </ExplorerWriter10>
  <RebelChild45>
    <title>rebellion</title>
    <titleShort>rebellion</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] born under the old class society. Despite significant pressure on families and communities, as no greeting, but against the freedom and dignity.

This until he and related parties in the situation in the family, was placed with them, trying to do our fear. He puts on the human body is not like the feeling.</desc>
  </RebelChild45>
  <MilitiaSoldier61>
    <title>picture</title>
    <titleShort>warrior</titleShort>
    <desc>Ta ra [PAWN_nameDef] justice join forces for peace.

Star mother suddenly destroyed by the war, life was blind and Auxerre to find a new hiding place, went over great distances.</desc>
  </MilitiaSoldier61>
  <MidworldCadet83>
    <title>Midworld student</title>
    <titleShort>Cadet</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun] study is also very good, and the contents of the naval academy [PAWN_possessive] the most talented planet in a house.</desc>
  </MidworldCadet83>
  <WarshipCaptain67>
    <title>Captain Space</title>
    <titleShort>captain</titleShort>
    <desc>Add a few years, Command, and how to manage the new Corvette Pu Ra [PAWN_nameDef], high-tech, as well as the enemy of peace, and others, will try to kill you.

Unfortunately [PAWN_nameDef] rarely touch with nature.</desc>
  </WarshipCaptain67>
  <ForestChild83>
    <title>wild child</title>
    <titleShort>Boy with wooden</titleShort>
    <desc>I have in mind, it is foolish, for kids, for mom [PAWN_nameDef] [PAWN_objective] [PAWN_pronoun] forest.

He grew up there, [PAWN_nameDef] pet lovers, now called hunting.</desc>
  </ForestChild83>
  <ForestProwler15>
    <title>on people</title>
    <titleShort>He lost in the wild</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] now run wild people. Victims, civilized, for example, killed in search of food, more civilized people who steal shiny material.</desc>
  </ForestProwler15>
  <VatgrownScientist91>
    <title>Scientists vatgrown</title>
    <titleShort>Scientist</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_objective] production teaching facility [PAWN_pronoun] use brain thinking, [PAWN_pronoun] last good brain, research continues.</desc>
  </VatgrownScientist91>
  <RunawayDancer35>
    <title>Dancer, who escaped</title>
    <titleShort>Ruby</titleShort>
    <desc>The power of knowledge rose to send through science, knowledge [PAWN_nameDef] thrown. [PAWN_pronoun] first place and as southwest (RimWorld the risk of loss) dance program.

Such a professional, and with a smile asked if kakushimotsu gun power supply.</desc>
  </RunawayDancer35>
  <MusicIdol50>
    <title>files</title>
    <titleShort>state</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_possessive] the death of the mother, and then [PAWN_nameDef] alone, we now have sexual relations and communications before [PAWN_possessive] father.</desc>
  </MusicIdol50>
  <ProstituteIdol28>
    <title>The number one brothel</title>
    <titleShort>whore</titleShort>
    <desc>When the father is deposed, [PAWN_nameDef], but it's because of his work in the porn industry has been forced to.\n\nLate treatment [PAWN_possessive] small body has been difficult not to take interim years. Competition artificial satellite Uritobasa through brothels and even drag the hottest [PAWN_pronoun] customers cut.</desc>
  </ProstituteIdol28>
  <SicklyLiar18>
    <title>Lie was sick letters</title>
    <titleShort>liar</titleShort>
    <desc>Indeed, they fall sick child is not common. They live in such a way, and a terrible system, and improve this would have been suspended.

Anytime soon, we can say that the work 3 tongue tip, eg wear Search Lynn Stone - often, but be close to the people who follow him.</desc>
  </SicklyLiar18>
  <SicklyLawyer36>
    <title>lawyers disease</title>
    <titleShort>support</titleShort>
    <desc>District Chief Lynn .[PAWN_possessive] speculation on the effects, music and steal sign the charges and to others affected attendance was all they said. If enough money to win in any case, we know that.

cough, because I have a child, there is no shortage.</desc>
  </SicklyLawyer36>
  <IceworldSurvivor75>
    <title>To survive the ice</title>
    <titleShort>Global line-Born</titleShort>
    <desc>Snow [PAWN_nameDef] born into the world. [PAWN_pronoun] green was not used to things, something inexplicable handle used to sound cold, .[PAWN_pronoun] plants.</desc>
  </IceworldSurvivor75>
  <Tinkerer86>
    <title>favorite machine</title>
    <titleShort>Favorite equipment</titleShort>
    <desc>Probably did it ... wow, it was broken ... but I want to get better. "</desc>
  </Tinkerer86>
  <TragicLoner87>
    <title>The effects of isolation and pain</title>
    <titleShort>sad</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] involved in the case, following the killing [PAWN_pronoun] [PAWN_possessive] trauma.

Some of the books for a living and engineers [PAWN_pronoun] exile community, you later. [PAWN_possessive] Pets.</desc>
  </TragicLoner87>
  <RocketPioneer75>
    <title>Advanced Missiles</title>
    <titleShort>Rokketia</titleShort>
    <desc>In [PAWN_pronoun] star weak to use the prospect of helping develop rockets, missiles several years.</desc>
  </RocketPioneer75>
  <SchoolyardOutcast11>
    <title>rogue class</title>
    <titleShort>error</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] there, and you get a good education. In this context in love ii born [PAWN_pronoun] .[PAWN_pronoun] a lot of cases, and often friends trying to make a fight I remember ee want the blood test to play a living room with terrorists.

There was a conflict [PAWN_nameDef] roaring want ad for revenge</desc>
  </SchoolyardOutcast11>
  <TheaterTechnician98>
    <title>Stage Tech House</title>
    <titleShort>Household Technology</titleShort>
    <desc>Popular theater [PAWN_nameDef] shelves, .[PAWN_pronoun] time now, the landscape, which will clear in a brief, I'm looking forward drive of the equipment.

Overtime, it was performed the story [PAWN_pronoun], saying this and that about the social drama actor and tell the good intentions of [PAWN_pronoun], it was allowed to wear How to manipulate people.</desc>
  </TheaterTechnician98>
  <AntisocialChild83>
    <title>the children</title>
    <titleShort>loyalty</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] lack of the usual sociability, and is not connected to it.\n\n[PAWN_pronoun] satisfied with the work of the company. Or filled with seeds, thick with hate.</desc>
  </AntisocialChild83>
  <ArmySergeant1>
    <title>Sargent</title>
    <titleShort>Sgt</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun] and even in difficult circumstances, special skills and tactics.</desc>
  </ArmySergeant1>
  <YoungPirate71>
    <title>Yang Zhu thief</title>
    <titleShort>Cusoku</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun] [PAWN_pronoun] to go to war, not a lot but we do not know, but he still did not know how to survive</desc>
  </YoungPirate71>
  <StellarPirate99>
    <title>Chuzoku</title>
    <titleShort>Chuzoku</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] captain pirate ship. [PAWN_pronoun] caught traders and flight officers.

is already a well-known problem with the contract, balance [PAWN_pronoun]. Architecture, war, during negotiations</desc>
  </StellarPirate99>
  <SoldierExperiment50>
    <title>experience robust</title>
    <titleShort>Experimental body</titleShort>
    <desc>Inspection of the building despite [PAWN_nameDef] to grow propose to normal.

In fact, it was explained that the body is part of a pilot [PAWN_pronoun]. Researchers are trying to develop heads Das, we continue to set the machine can be used to connect the entrance. [PAWN_objective].</desc>
  </SoldierExperiment50>
  <LostSoldier13>
    <title>Lost hero</title>
    <titleShort>Prodigal son</titleShort>
    <desc>In order to build a [PAWN_nameDef], particularly housing can be heavy armor, I found the body last to .[PAWN_pronoun] I hot work.</desc>
  </LostSoldier13>
  <DedicatedStudent29>
    <title>A student thinking</title>
    <titleShort>students</titleShort>
    <desc>Baby accessories, .[PAWN_pronoun] [PAWN_nameDef] took the young man, the overprotective, read a book, but a draw on the image, stupid hate housework time.

Revolution, the business of government. [PAWN_possessive], intense research program, [PAWN_nameDef], a poor finish.</desc>
  </DedicatedStudent29>
  <LanguageAnalyst27>
    <title>Global Language Analysis</title>
    <titleShort>linguists</titleShort>
    <desc>Star of [PAWN_possessive] of the war began, [PAWN_nameDef] smartphones, and is listed as a space station is .[PAWN_pronoun], but an understanding of the media that is an enemy to take care of hydroponics.

Planet after the crisis as a medical tool has reduced the share of companies created as a result of [PAWN_pronoun] cold.</desc>
  </LanguageAnalyst27>
  <Infantry36>
    <title>infantry</title>
    <titleShort>Pedestrians</titleShort>
    <desc>Lenka has become a world destroyed by war.

As a child, how to handle weapons, cruelty, his spirit cleansing. It is, then their outstanding work for the torture.</desc>
  </Infantry36>
  <PrisonerOfWar69>
    <title>POW</title>
    <titleShort>prison</titleShort>
    <desc>He was arrested and put to death [PAWN_nameDef] before war crimes.

Fortunately for him, they are the power to escape. Control Study of revolt riot, and fabric and recycling center. More Prisoners Organization, [PAWN_nameDef] flee delivery location.</desc>
  </PrisonerOfWar69>
  <AngryStudent84>
    <title>Angry students</title>
    <titleShort>student</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] I read a dream to work with the municipality of the city council.\n\nFor reasons completely omoiataru his friends who have decided to fight angry [PAWN_pronoun] [PAWN_pronoun] brutal violence.</desc>
  </AngryStudent84>
  <MadAccountant61>
    <title>Angry accountant</title>
    <titleShort>accountant</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] as against top counterparts layer has a good dialogue, and management is also a lot of friends.

One day when somebody [PAWN_nameDef] [PAWN_possessive] boss, he is accused of fraud and corruption. After this report, [PAWN_pronoun]. We try to do the right thing, [PAWN_pronoun] from mass murder.</desc>
  </MadAccountant61>
  <TransferStudent3>
    <title>students move</title>
    <titleShort>Student</titleShort>
    <desc>Parents like midworld [PAWN_pronoun] better education, income glitterworld, you can add [PAWN_objective] rich.

while the rest research glitterworld amazing [PAWN_nameDef] talented students. But it is a rich family is not an easy task [PAWN_pronoun] dabble in any way.</desc>
  </TransferStudent3>
  <Politician57>
    <title>politician</title>
    <titleShort>political</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] the workers, the main political parties. [PAWN_pronoun] good, but hidden around the course in self-defense combat training and political opponents have a lot of target practice.</desc>
  </Politician57>
  <DesertRat47>
    <title>Desert Rat</title>
    <titleShort>Mice in the desert</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] useless, misleading impasse caused by the way in the desert tribes.

Son, His revelations, and they can be freed from ignorance, looking fabulous - the driver, so the new world interstellar.</desc>
  </DesertRat47>
  <Philosopher97>
    <title>philosopher</title>
    <titleShort>wise</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun] is a sad news agency. also, proposals, and also is the way of the future</desc>
  </Philosopher97>
  <ArtisticWeirdo56>
    <title>eccentric art</title>
    <titleShort>mathematics</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun], painting, and although we have shown talent in creative work, to the strange behavior of people often resort only.</desc>
  </ArtisticWeirdo56>
  <AdventurousWeirdo83>
    <title>Adventure Entertainment</title>
    <titleShort>strange</titleShort>
    <desc>medieval history and Zany creative [PAWN_nameDef], which is dedicated to the vital interests of both advanced technologies.\n\n[PAWN_pronoun] knight paradise" it is a good idea, and flash sword fighting impressed.</desc>
  </AdventurousWeirdo83>
  <ApprenticeOracle83>
    <title>prophet advertising</title>
    <titleShort>The Prophet</titleShort>
    <desc>Oracle "countries selected adults were chosen for a holy service [PAWN_nameDef] years ago.\n\nThis time capsule is canceled - [PAWN_nameDef] religion curse of a boy facing a crisis, and usually, [PAWN_possessive] society "can your parents a degree of her husband, not open grave" dissolution.</desc>
  </ApprenticeOracle83>
  <CasketBuilder76>
    <title>The field trip</title>
    <titleShort>Craftsman</titleShort>
    <desc>Ta ra [PAWN_nameDef] to know the technical sense of how dream in life is a fascinating frozen.

Midvorld [PAWN_nameDef] work is part of the waste as a plumber, I have a sample device model on a bed of ice. Unfortunately, the last meeting [PAWN_pronoun] Unfortunately [PAWN_possessive] mother star carpet bombing was one of miles.</desc>
  </CasketBuilder76>
  <JunkyardMechanic99>
    <title>mechanical junkyard</title>
    <titleShort>call</titleShort>
    <desc>Leaving despair in childhood. [PAWN_nameDef] Leaders at the dump Urbworld career. [PAWN_nameDef], when the new machines, [PAWN_pronoun] many things mentioned.</desc>
  </JunkyardMechanic99>
  <MilitaryOfficer17>
    <title>officials</title>
    <titleShort>documents</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun], and develop the perfect battle, you can train .[PAWN_pronoun] and the ability of science to survive, [PAWN_nameDef] feeling of loneliness, no longer friends [PAWN_possessive] first.</desc>
  </MilitaryOfficer17>
  <Empath47>
    <title>kinder</title>
    <titleShort>fellow feeling</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] ncredible can sympathize with the children. Therefore, normal conversation, really [PAWN_pronoun] suffering. [PAWN_nameDef] because without this idea, the sound is a challenge that can not conceal [PAWN_objective] is, is too army, not try to remove the rule.</desc>
  </Empath47>
  <FearfulChef49>
    <title>Do not be afraid Chef</title>
    <titleShort>chef</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] talented cook the ultra-luxurious restaurant in the works.

Then one day, the remaining error [PAWN_pronoun] stove, we present all burned. This is because [PAWN_pronoun] moved around the stove does not exist.</desc>
  </FearfulChef49>
  <AnimalLabTech39>
    <title>Laboratory animals</title>
    <titleShort>Scientific Assistant</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] served as animal testing, research assistant in the laboratory.\n\nThe role of the people in all-day care of the day-[PAWN_pronoun], or animals, or .[PAWN_pronoun], had a dream in its laboratories.</desc>
  </AnimalLabTech39>
  <MuffaloResearcher67>
    <title>Researchers Maffaro</title>
    <titleShort>Research</titleShort>
    <desc>Industry and technology development and small [PAWN_possessive].</desc>
  </MuffaloResearcher67>
  <ShipChild46>
    <title>A boy on board</title>
    <titleShort>Ship</titleShort>
    <desc>Family [PAWN_nameDef] the universe. [PAWN_pronoun] basic life on the road, do not know the salary, the deal of the day [PAWN_pronoun] illogical for it's beautiful.</desc>
  </ShipChild46>
  <ArtifactHunter48>
    <title>catcher machine</title>
    <titleShort>Artie</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] .[PAWN_pronoun] now lost interest in ([PAWN_possessive] fortunately for the soul) star life journey was not in fact say the wreckage of artie mekanoido despair of you.

The company will continue to benefit from the index finger to [PAWN_nameDef].</desc>
  </ArtifactHunter48>
  <PetKeeper7>
    <title>pet common</title>
    <titleShort>Goalkeeper Pet</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun] this beauty of nature [PAWN_possessive] friends, we must choose [PAWN_possessive] animal friends.</desc>
  </PetKeeper7>
  <Herpetologist3>
    <title>reptile scientist</title>
    <titleShort>Reptile expert</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun], then, .[PAWN_pronoun] [PAWN_possessive] want and need to see a durable, you know, the pain of loss.</desc>
  </Herpetologist3>
  <ChildResearcher32>
    <title>Research results</title>
    <titleShort>researchers</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun] nothing more innovation.</desc>
  </ChildResearcher32>
  <Fugitive32>
    <title>flight</title>
    <titleShort>savings</titleShort>
    <desc>The only way the people can always get the support [PAWN_pronoun] [PAWN_possessive] moves, try failed because of poor social [PAWN_possessive], .[PAWN_pronoun] something out of the shadows forever hidden.</desc>
  </Fugitive32>
  <VidtubeStar98>
    <title>Video Lawyer Tuber</title>
    <titleShort>video head</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun] won a million followers.</desc>
  </VidtubeStar98>
  <GunDealer14>
    <title>sales arms</title>
    <titleShort>out sales</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] other factions in the war, sales of high-tech weaponry.

Since long, [PAWN_pronoun] is the regulation of products, demonstrations, events and history, and negotiations are now very good.</desc>
  </GunDealer14>
  <CorporateSlave22>
    <title>companies slavery</title>
    <titleShort>soldier</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] militia and create high glitter world. VR device mounted child grow without restraint, the world visible.

Data is always difficult as it is now in the middle levels of the [PAWN_nameDef] forced to fight with others, use of weapons and tactics.</desc>
  </CorporateSlave22>
  <ColonyEngineer16>
    <title>pioneer engineer</title>
    <titleShort>Engineer</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] to become a master engineer vr system, the company responded inevitably our work in preparation for caution.</desc>
  </ColonyEngineer16>
  <AspiringPhysicist25>
    <title>Many children</title>
    <titleShort>students</titleShort>
    <desc>Technology and Women's intellectual property rich herring [PAWN_nameDef] childhood. Visit the Institute of Physics, who decided to become quantum physics.

Card camels, horses, dogs, or eating harmful, now [PAWN_nameDef] music and animals.</desc>
  </AspiringPhysicist25>
  <DeepSpaceSurveyor87>
    <title>Escaped from the deep</title>
    <titleShort>read</titleShort>
    <desc>S depth available [PAWN_nameDef]. It is the goal of colonization, I learned things that fit best in the world.

the introduction of an international body of a male green travel to places of violence is a big fan of Greek mythology. Arson and very bored, and she can rock the enemy Trebuchet Ward wore a simple lathe.</desc>
  </DeepSpaceSurveyor87>
  <QuietNerd97>
    <title>true wild</title>
    <titleShort>Experts</titleShort>
    <desc>Fans of parents living far [PAWN_nameDef] midworld world. [PAWN_pronoun] it was a difficult time, but the staff there is almost no dramatic.</desc>
  </QuietNerd97>
  <CostumeCrafter41>
    <title>Reason Clothing Manufacturers</title>
    <titleShort>cosplayers</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] midworld the employee works during the day, night suits cour cosplay for animals is not easy.

sewing [PAWN_pronoun] remarkable artistic spending. Unfortunately, warned them to eat foods or food offer.</desc>
  </CostumeCrafter41>
  <SpacerOrphan77>
    <title>orphan universe</title>
    <titleShort>orphan</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun] survive for surgery, but he also wanted to know that other members of the family happy.</desc>
  </SpacerOrphan77>
  <Gunfighter51>
    <title>shooting</title>
    <titleShort>robber</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] rasethunya one. The white side-by-side in peace .[PAWN_pronoun], this year I received a family of brothers and sisters who suffer.

Good for people to pay, or the most gold--[PAWN_pronoun] after the death of someone close to [PAWN_pronoun], again, this is the trip for those looking for a gun.</desc>
  </Gunfighter51>
  <SmallTownKid41>
    <title>rural children</title>
    <titleShort>children's village</titleShort>
    <desc>Once in the village midworld [PAWN_nameDef] topic.

[PAWN_possessive] parents and the wider role of the standing instruction. [PAWN_objective]. Childhood quiet sure, life seems to be the most painful point.</desc>
  </SmallTownKid41>
  <RenownedProfessor51>
    <title>distinguished Professor</title>
    <titleShort>professor</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_possessive] portuguese class, all the support, the student has adopted a series of seminars [PAWN_possessive] few [PAWN_pronoun] compassion and tolerance.</desc>
  </RenownedProfessor51>
  <SteamworldTinker38>
    <title>After steamvorld</title>
    <titleShort>artist</titleShort>
    <desc>This work was in part ordering spare parts [PAWN_possessive] small, winner cash flow, lived much; tsugikomi [PAWN_pronoun] with money and weapons.</desc>
  </SteamworldTinker38>
  <NavyTechOfficer0>
    <title>Navy Officer</title>
    <titleShort>Navy Engineer</titleShort>
    <desc>Higher education in various fields, not gun focused skills training [PAWN_pronoun] abroad.</desc>
  </NavyTechOfficer0>
  <AbandonedOrphan61>
    <title>orphans, abandoned</title>
    <titleShort>li</titleShort>
    <desc>immediately after birth, and they give students [PAWN_nameDef] began life as an orphan.\n\nThugs, a villain, [PAWN_pronoun] tragedies.</desc>
  </AbandonedOrphan61>
  <KingOfPirates25>
    <title>Pirate King</title>
    <titleShort>reproduction</titleShort>
    <desc>Auto [PAWN_nameDef] edition of the pirate king, wisdom [PAWN_pronoun] not been there, the fear of [PAWN_possessive] I [PAWN_pronoun] people around naked, but a large fire can not be operated by the sword, [PAWN_pronoun] adrenaline fast melee combat.</desc>
  </KingOfPirates25>
  <SpaceNerd97>
    <title>Space Otaku Nerd</title>
    <titleShort>Geek map</titleShort>
    <desc>This [PAWN_nameDef] .[PAWN_pronoun] .[PAWN_pronoun] new world space adventure and cold person, a valuable [PAWN_possessive] all love chocolate like a dream, the dream of sweeping, among others responsible ... Chocolate Space</desc>
  </SpaceNerd97>
  <SpaceNavyTech12>
    <title>Marine engineers Coleoptera</title>
    <titleShort>marine engineer</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_pronoun] patriotic pride and play a role in our planet.</desc>
  </SpaceNavyTech12>
  <ChildSpy96>
    <title>Spy</title>
    <titleShort>spy</titleShort>
    <desc>In other words, who is hailed as innocent of course, it does not cause a kid spy. In the very young, was taken to surgery, .[PAWN_nameDef] ideal surgical training and data collection.

[PAWN_pronoun] to data collected in the brutal war of conquest against the Earth for several years. This limits the opportunity to study at this stage [PAWN_pronoun].</desc>
  </ChildSpy96>
  <Defector95>
    <title>flight</title>
    <titleShort>who survived</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] [PAWN_pronoun], .[PAWN_possessive] be recognized president persecution and repression avoid disaster, "agency director to flee the decision.

[PAWN_pronoun] .[PAWN_pronoun] the last few years, because to medical avoid living trust, even [PAWN_pronoun] injury healed. This test is bad [PAWN_objective] Misanthropy is taken.</desc>
  </Defector95>
  <TurtleHerder26>
    <title>turtle breeders</title>
    <titleShort>breeders</titleShort>
    <desc>Family member. [PAWN_nameDef] settler attacks swine turtle We collected it in his interest.

increasing - Youth, [PAWN_pronoun] turtle [PAWN_pronoun] again, leaving this issue. turtle mass pour the food, we have destroyed the local ecosystem.</desc>
  </TurtleHerder26>
  <SpaceMarineMedic10>
    <title>Marine Corps of the Ministry of Health</title>
    <titleShort>medic</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] joined the health of the colonial power. Settlers arrived, he found that there were residential and demons plague at this time to connect with the public as war .[PAWN_pronoun] ran for several days.

Deputy Governor of the victim [PAWN_pronoun] Omoishiri the top of their power the ball Suri Cyrus is the fourth ninety and responsible gun barrels goldeg talking about. The next day, he was nicknamed "green" found.</desc>
  </SpaceMarineMedic10>
  <Freethinker38>
    <title>free thinker</title>
    <titleShort>elite</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] toxic grew up in the world of authoritarian monarchy. A clear majority of the population is interested in export [PAWN_pronoun] rebels in the forest.

and run the risk of the government after the explosion, [PAWN_pronoun] world bhombiwa suicide threatens to destroy antimatter bombs used to escape alive.</desc>
  </Freethinker38>
  <MercenaryLord58>
    <title>two mercenaries</title>
    <titleShort>journeyman passage</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef], in the hands of the average price of the good, it is good to pay and now has his reward, he gets freelancers. et.al., to have a company trying to collect them. [PAWN_pronoun] "sea".

Motoi [PAWN_pronoun] forces around the world have taken sides. give [PAWN_pronoun] village-based solutions. The government, as well as mixed Mad Men [PAWN_pronoun] deep in our world, the package insert is stored attack.</desc>
  </MercenaryLord58>
  <NavyPathfinder53>
    <title>Sophisticated computer Navy</title>
    <titleShort>advance team</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] plans to develop a method of planet deep space, but has been prepared by a group of soldiers in a large scale.</desc>
  </NavyPathfinder53>
  <ShadowMarine63>
    <title>Trophies</title>
    <titleShort>Navy</titleShort>
    <desc>Can not the first [PAWN_nameDef], dressed skills required steps for your team, to be good at keeping my login host way and the planet.

Orbital will trade route known [PAWN_pronoun] planet can get in and out without being detected.</desc>
  </ShadowMarine63>
  <HunterScavenger64>
    <title>scavenger hunters</title>
    <titleShort>scavenger</titleShort>
    <desc>Born in a family ryder apartments vinna [PAWN_nameDef]. lived there from shops in the village with the robbers. .[PAWN_pronoun] on the seventh day after tomorrow, and good food, a violent gang.</desc>
  </HunterScavenger64>
  <Warlordess14>
    <title>General wife</title>
    <titleShort>generally woman</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] chuzok.

[PAWN_pronoun]'ve and risks that have to take on this challenge. Others continue killing machine.</desc>
  </Warlordess14>
  <Punk30>
    <title>Music</title>
    <titleShort>Punk</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] I was a child, he spent 15 years selling counterfeit cigarettes. Since tobacco is often, but cut grass.</desc>
  </Punk30>
  <GameDeveloper95>
    <title>Games reproduction</title>
    <titleShort>game Maker</titleShort>
    <desc>[PAWN_nameDef] manufacturer for themselves.

After the morning's proposal success quickly fell [PAWN_nameDef] activities. The PR office and failure to despair.</desc>
  </GameDeveloper95>
</BackstoryTranslations>
