<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <MultiAnalyzer.label>Analyzer</MultiAnalyzer.label>
  <MultiAnalyzer.description>you can run the level of research to increase the speed of learning can create many analysts.</MultiAnalyzer.description>
  <GroundPenetratingScanner.label>research cut</GroundPenetratingScanner.label>
  <GroundPenetratingScanner.description>Drilling Solid as those available from the surface source can cover the scanner.Production requires advanced components.</GroundPenetratingScanner.description>
  <DeepDrilling.label>Deep hole drilling machines</DeepDrilling.label>
  <DeepDrilling.description>You can make a deep drilling machine for the extraction of resources from the depths of the earth's crust.Confectionery reader to find the resources you need.</DeepDrilling.description>
  <VitalsMonitor.label>critical</VitalsMonitor.label>
  <VitalsMonitor.description>Set aside in a hospital bed, you'll be able to improve the performance of the treatment to follow.</VitalsMonitor.description>
  <Fabrication.label>production assembly</Fabrication.label>
  <Fabrication.description>From Congress to the construction of armor power, you'll be able to create complex production can run high-tech projects.</Fabrication.description>
  <AdvancedFabrication.label>Advanced design program</AdvancedFabrication.label>
  <AdvancedFabrication.description>Components were and other products, will not be able to handle the additional elements.</AdvancedFabrication.description>
  <Cryptosleep.label>Hibernation capsule</Cryptosleep.label>
  <Cryptosleep.description>Animation biological condition of the work was interrupted, you can create a hibernation capsule.</Cryptosleep.description>
  <PoweredArmor.label>power tools</PoweredArmor.label>
  <PoweredArmor.description>A warrior, and cheat -. You [e] can hope for salvation advanced component necessary to create jobs.</PoweredArmor.description>
  <ChargedShot.label>power of the gun</ChargedShot.label>
  <ChargedShot.description>They commanded that they should be able to make weapons to provide additional images to send to the vibrating strings loss. [Notes] This is the advanced components.</ChargedShot.description>
  <Bionics.label>robot</Bionics.label>
  <Bionics.description>Lost limbs and eyes will be able to create high-tech artificial body.The growing importance of health care workers.</Bionics.description>
  <SniperTurret.label>Dome uranium slag</SniperTurret.label>
  <SniperTurret.description>You can create uranium turret armor to protect access lines.Uranium metal slug has quite closely the results, but the card pairs entered ball.</SniperTurret.description>
</LanguageData>
