<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <Peaceful.label>Gentle (sorry)</Peaceful.label>
  <Peaceful.description>We have a small garden, the environment and local communities.\n\nBaseball and public RimWorld those who want to focus on, we are encouraged\n\nThis mode is no longer active, the major crisis events, or disease, mental decline, such as the remains of animals in a riot.</Peaceful.description>
  <Easy.label>The foundation of the house (easy)</Easy.label>
  <Easy.description>If you are enjoying a threat, you can create a colony.\n\nThe first in this game, which will be comfortable and Games: People like to offer.\n\nThreat, but other ways nothing. Some events terrifying fear.</Easy.description>
  <Medium.label>Normal (average)</Medium.label>
  <Medium.description>You can create a colony, when the threat.\n\nI recommend that you want people to play RimWorld first experience with a game plan, but RimWorld experience, satisfied the goals away and hide\n\nYes and prosperity, but there is no change in the planet risk.</Medium.description>
  <Rough.label>Heavy (Balaji)</Rough.label>
  <Rough.description>And surgery and surgical world tried to escape.\n\nRecommended RimWorld experience, you want the person assigned to the gaming experience of history, existence.\n\nPerfect game day, the wound would have been possible to fight against the problems can survive some damage, and recovery will be needed for life.</Rough.description>
  <Hard.label>Sharp (m)</Hard.label>
  <Hard.description>We are facing a violent struggle for a living. This is a blood test which is a shame.\n\nWanted recommended: experience, people who want harder way\n\nYou have a strategy for a particular application on Eve's kind of power failure If you want to be successful at this level before. Sometimes the weight and quality of the crisis will be taken from the combination of the sequence.</Hard.description>
  <Extreme.label>Prize (D)</Extreme.label>
  <Extreme.description>from the terrible suffering, to survive, and it is possible to use all the features of grace it is not a fair world.\n\nThey want advice, live and running, trying to escape from the loss of all want to face the situation that brings vicious people skills\n\nmay not be a perfect match. It is you and you will spend a lot of time victims of war damages to be included gives you the ritual of death and restore needs.</Extreme.description>
</LanguageData>
