<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <FlagstoneSandstone.label>paving grout</FlagstoneSandstone.label>
  <FlagstoneSandstone.description>Rough edges of the slate tiles. But that has changed, and it is not suitable for spring. But at night, and, for paving stones.</FlagstoneSandstone.description>
  <FlagstoneGranite.label>granite pavers</FlagstoneGranite.label>
  <FlagstoneGranite.description>Rough slate tiles on the ground. However, it is not suitable for pleasure roads and paths. If this does not decrease its sidewalks.</FlagstoneGranite.description>
  <FlagstoneLimestone.label>feel powerless cement</FlagstoneLimestone.label>
  <FlagstoneLimestone.description>Jagged edges of the slate tiles. But the best way because travel is not perfect. And not even make the rock removal xaareysa.</FlagstoneLimestone.description>
  <FlagstoneSlate.label>The stone cobbles</FlagstoneSlate.label>
  <FlagstoneSlate.description>This is a rough edge on the slate tiles. But it is nice and comfortable, and walking. What does not remain even if the degradation of the pavement.</FlagstoneSlate.description>
  <FlagstoneMarble.label>Repair Granite</FlagstoneMarble.label>
  <FlagstoneMarble.description>Shale box rough edges. But the beauty and perfect for relaxation. Do not disassemble and stone.</FlagstoneMarble.description>
  <!-- ================= Tile ================= -->
  <TileSandstone.label>Sandstone</TileSandstone.label>
  <TileSandstone.description>A mixed structure is kept to be a different brick. It looks good, but it takes time to create.</TileSandstone.description>
  <TileGranite.label>granite tiles</TileGranite.label>
  <TileGranite.description>To reach the castle tile collection is divided in mind. Sehwag, but it takes time to put on.</TileGranite.description>
  <TileLimestone.label>cement slabs</TileLimestone.label>
  <TileLimestone.description>Made entitled castle carefully difference. Sounds good, but it takes time for bed.</TileLimestone.description>
  <TileSlate.label>slate tile</TileSlate.label>
  <TileSlate.description>The castle theme, tile, which have been carefully placed in isolation. Looks good, but it takes time to build.</TileSlate.description>
  <TileMarble.label>Marble Tiles</TileMarble.label>
  <TileMarble.description>But the structure of the castle, which is analyzed and designed the Mosaic Law. Sehwag, but it is time to set.</TileMarble.description>
</LanguageData>
