<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <Crashlanded.label>不時着</Crashlanded.label>
  <Crashlanded.description>Capsule winter, friends, knew that the sound of the bells of the boat and brakes.Spaceship to Shisan matter of time I think escape pod and was able to recover.Time, thanks guys, I RimWorld confirmed.</Crashlanded.description>
  <Crashlanded.scenario.name>不時着</Crashlanded.scenario.name>
  <Crashlanded.scenario.summary>If one emergency landing, the three survivors - RimWorld indulge me the model of the world.</Crashlanded.scenario.summary>
  <Crashlanded.scenario.description>Sleeping with the sound bells and you burst out of the box after attending off-site, and Hur least three children.Before you has been your personal review, I finally fled iPod.RimWorld who you talk a little toast not confirmed.</Crashlanded.scenario.description>
  <TheRichExplorer.label>rich Explorer</TheRichExplorer.label>
  <TheRichExplorer.description>Brilliant life, I am calling on you or anything crazy, you want to look at the stars - Last Simulator to consider others.Also on the table will not be traveling with the long hibernation.RimWorld do not know any country; The time has come, according to the source.</TheRichExplorer.description>
  <TheRichExplorer.scenario.name>rich Internet Explorer</TheRichExplorer.scenario.name>
  <TheRichExplorer.scenario.summary>How happy funds, and one in Indonesia.</TheRichExplorer.scenario.summary>
  <TheRichExplorer.scenario.description>Was a big world, I call them "stupid", always take the fear to the stars - to find out what other similar tests.Now, in the end, despite the long journey to the sleeping pills frozen.Land Unknown RimWorld, it's time to make sure the eye.</TheRichExplorer.scenario.description>
  <TheRichExplorer.scenario.parts.GameStartDialog.text>Euro Holo simulation games, etc., but not satisfaction.You mentioned in historical texts is the same value and lifetime, the point of impact being.\n\nThe end of the cold ground of the road after awake for 10 years, met rimvorld.Your true story awaits.</TheRichExplorer.scenario.parts.GameStartDialog.text>
  <LostTribe.label>the lost tribes</LostTribe.label>
  <LostTribe.description>God destroyed remove your group, but only five people survived.Now is the time to build a new home.</LostTribe.description>
  <LostTribe.scenario.name>lost Tribe</LostTribe.scenario.name>
  <LostTribe.scenario.summary>Efforts to restore the area.</LostTribe.scenario.summary>
  <LostTribe.scenario.description>God's people, but nothing has been destroyed not only five survivors.Time now for the restoration of the house is new.</LostTribe.scenario.description>
  <LostTribe.scenario.parts.GameStartDialog.text>He was very angry.Bloodbath parking in the evening.\nThey set fire to the bush for the city, hell, into the fire blade.\n\nA few times, you need to escape.\nTibia's visit after, and asked a close friend, now in the desert, when the mother and father, Sunil came to construct a new location</LostTribe.scenario.parts.GameStartDialog.text>
  <NakedBrutality.label>naked</NakedBrutality.label>
  <NakedBrutality.description>Are simple to operate, a deep sleep to fall anesthesia.You're in the planet's atmosphere, escapes and pods, and quickly.Only you all the assets, naked.If you can stay alive\n\n[NOTE]: In this situation, you do not have high expectations for all - very simple and absolutely nothing to do with death.</NakedBrutality.description>
  <NakedBrutality.scenario.name>he is not</NakedBrutality.scenario.name>
  <NakedBrutality.scenario.summary>Naked, without preparing them completely.If you save? It's unfair, it is very difficult.</NakedBrutality.scenario.summary>
  <NakedBrutality.scenario.description>Because you want to do a simple product into a deep sleep.This means that we wake up in the rescue capsule, the atmosphere of a distant planet entered.naked and alone, which is belonged to.Live\n\nit is very difficult for those who die from - [name] In this situation, you do not need all expectations.</NakedBrutality.scenario.description>
  <NakedBrutality.scenario.parts.GameStartDialog.text>I think this is easy.I think that this is a real-time anesthesia should be provided.\n\nAt the moment you get the boat into the border stars RimWorld.\n\nSince that cover the whole body is hidden near the surface, without any preparation being naked and without literature, we have no tools.Either can be saved</NakedBrutality.scenario.parts.GameStartDialog.text>
</LanguageData>
