<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <OutlanderCivil.label>Outlander Union (Min)</OutlanderCivil.label>
  <OutlanderCivil.description>Or live a few dozen people here for nearly a century, most of it was removed from the technology. And, to further protect your hands and likely to explode to be a dead simple way to do.\n\nThey are practical enthusiasm and confidence to live.\n\nThis amazing group believes that the character is very dignity respect. </OutlanderCivil.description>
  <OutlanderCivil.pawnSingular>state</OutlanderCivil.pawnSingular>
  <OutlanderCivil.pawnsPlural>country people</OutlanderCivil.pawnsPlural>
  <OutlanderCivil.leaderTitle>Chief Adviser</OutlanderCivil.leaderTitle>
  <OutlanderRough.label>Eclipse Alliance (thickness)</OutlanderRough.label>
  <OutlanderRough.description>About a hundred people living here, or a few years, has lost that many technologies. Typically, the explosive nature of advanced single-chip gun, we work with the opposition.\n\nInterest rate is variable and reliable.\n\nThis special group of malignant. </OutlanderRough.description>
  <OutlanderRough.pawnSingular>party</OutlanderRough.pawnSingular>
  <OutlanderRough.pawnsPlural>foreign</OutlanderRough.pawnsPlural>
  <OutlanderRough.leaderTitle>Chief of the Defense Council</OutlanderRough.leaderTitle>
  <TribeCivil.label>Barb cradle (low)</TribeCivil.label>
  <TribeCivil.description>When people here for a long time. Your ancestors thousands of years, do not crash. And maybe eliminate technology and culture, overcame several natural disasters. In all cases, the use of primitive tools and weapons, most of which in the worst nomads.\n\nClearly, even though the poor old technology, equipment information technology, energy, the barbarians and dangerous enemy, and to find a friend called.\n\nThis particular disease, we stay peaceful lifestyle. See, a stranger, in the commercial and contract in full, and open the door. </TribeCivil.description>
  <TribeCivil.pawnSingular>as violent</TribeCivil.pawnSingular>
  <TribeCivil.pawnsPlural>All other countries, and so on</TribeCivil.pawnsPlural>
  <TribeCivil.leaderTitle>head</TribeCivil.leaderTitle>
  <TribeRough.label>Indian Chief</TribeRough.label>
  <TribeRough.description>People are here for the long contract. Perhaps dating back to thousands of years. Perhaps, technology and the destruction of civilization, I have overcome the natural disaster. In any case, the use of traditional tools and weapons, the most nomadic population.\n\nOf course, despite the fact that the poor in technology, the ability inferior weapons, and dismantle large, dangerous barbarian enemies, who also received an important friend.\n\nThis particular blood, we appreciate the legal battle. giving them the Allies seem so difficult. </TribeRough.description>
  <TribeRough.pawnSingular>Wild</TribeRough.pawnSingular>
  <TribeRough.pawnsPlural>Barbarii et al</TribeRough.pawnsPlural>
  <TribeRough.leaderTitle>president</TribeRough.leaderTitle>
  <Pirate.label>Chuzoku</Pirate.label>
  <Pirate.description>Club entrenched sexual union without being part of an attack, we agree that the main conflict of outsiders.\n\nChuzoku not sowing the seed, not here, there will be a line of business. They have disappeared, the price of the drug in the blood and a culture dedicated, more neighbors and robbery of their attacks.\n\nSkill level, and often, because they at the same time? It depends. Indeed weapon, but is ready to bring the victim closely. </Pirate.description>
  <Pirate.pawnSingular>Chuzoku</Pirate.pawnSingular>
  <Pirate.pawnsPlural>Chu theft</Pirate.pawnsPlural>
  <Pirate.leaderTitle>head</Pirate.leaderTitle>
</LanguageData>
